<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>VDagama Product Feed</title>
    <link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com</link>
    <description>Facebook Product Feed</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>2024-new-fashion-womens-soft-leather-retro-fashion-high-grade-single-crossbody-messenger-bag-bamboo-handle-bag-shoulder-purse</g:id>
      <g:title>2024 New fashion Women's soft leather Retro Fashion High-grade Single crossbody Messenger Bag Bamboo handle Bag Shoulder Purse</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: DKQWAITOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongLining Material: Organic CottonMain Material: Microfiber Synthetic LeatherPlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvincePlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvinceShape: Casual ToteOccasion: VersatileExterior: noneModel Number: 665652Closure Type: zipperDecoration: AppliquesHardness: SOFTGender: WOMENPattern Type: SolidStyle: fashion</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-new-fashion-womens-soft-leather-retro-fashion-high-grade-single-crossbody-messenger-bag-bamboo-handle-bag-shoulder-purse</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S062a747324a84b5fa35c8c22aec9472aw.webp?v=1724763205</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>58.24 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2024-new-niche-minimalist-tote-advanced-spring-summer-large-capacity-commuter-single-shoulder-underarm-fashion-trend-soft-bag</g:id>
      <g:title>2024 New Niche Minimalist Tote Advanced Spring Summer Large-capacity Commuter Single Shoulder Underarm Fashion Trend Soft Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: NoEnName_NullHign-concerned Chemical: NoneHandbags Type: Shoulder BagsTypes of bags: Shoulder &amp; HandbagsMain Material: PULining Material: NoneShape: Half MoonPlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvincePlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvinceOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongDecoration: noneGender: WOMENStyle: fashionNumber of Handles/Straps: twofashion element: sewing threadCLOSED WAY: magnetic snap 


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-new-niche-minimalist-tote-advanced-spring-summer-large-capacity-commuter-single-shoulder-underarm-fashion-trend-soft-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S70f5905006444adcb8acb3d1e3aa5765G.webp?v=1725203476</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>15.25 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>airy-luxe-merino-tee</g:id>
      <g:title>Airy Luxe Merino Tee</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the perfect blend of comfort and elegance with this oversized, relaxed-fit women's top crafted from 100% premium fine wool. Designed to drape effortlessly over your silhouette, this lightweight top offers unmatched breathability and softness, making it ideal for year-round wear. Whether you're layering it on chilly days or wearing it solo in warmer weather, its natural temperature-regulating properties keep you cozy and comfortable.

Material: Wool

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/airy-luxe-merino-tee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama-2025-01-14T140006.529.png?v=1736858336</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>all-match-mens-cool-outdoor-slippers-mens-hollow-out-summer-sandals-leather-thick-soled-beach-shoes-non-slip-handmade-sandals</g:id>
      <g:title>All-match Men's Cool Outdoor Slippers Men's Hollow Out Summer Sandals Leather Thick-soled Beach Shoes Non-slip Handmade Sandals</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONS
Brand Name: YEISNDOO
Upper Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Upper-Genuine Leather Type: Cow Leather
Sandal Type: basic
Style: Concise
Origin: Mainland China
Occasion: Casual
Outsole Material: RUBBER
Heel Height: Flat (≤1cm)
Pattern Type: Solid
Insole Material: EVA
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Model Number: 9696
Lining Material: none
Closure Type: SLIP-ON
Item Type: sandals
Fashion Element: Sewing
Department Name: ADULT






 Tips:1. This is NOT Standard EUR Size. The foot length is the only standard for choose size.2. Insole length should be 1-1.5cm bigger than your foot length.3.Order is without shoes box. 






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/all-match-mens-cool-outdoor-slippers-mens-hollow-out-summer-sandals-leather-thick-soled-beach-shoes-non-slip-handmade-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sec2d552eac9241d5adb9ac218fe271577.webp?v=1720362858</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>28.78 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>alpaca-royale-oversized-coat</g:id>
      <g:title>Alpaca Royale Oversized Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>True inner beauty deserves to be mirrored by something equally exquisite on the outside. This oversized alpaca wool fur coat is a testament to refined luxury and timeless elegance. Expertly crafted from 100% premium alpaca wool—renowned for its unparalleled softness and natural warmth—it offers a plush texture and sophisticated design that radiates prestige. As the saying goes, "Style is a way to say who you are without speaking," and this coat speaks volumes. It transforms the woman who wears it into a vision of grace and power, seamlessly blending comfort with unmatched sophistication.
Material: Alpaca Wool +98%
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/alpaca-royale-oversized-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_23.png?v=1733773290</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>490.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>alpine-chill-jacket</g:id>
      <g:title>Alpine Chill Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and stylish this winter with our casual duck down jacket, designed for warmth and everyday comfort. Featuring a lightweight, shorter design and a snug hood, this jacket is perfect for casual outings or layering on colder days. Made with premium duck down filling, it ensures excellent insulation without the bulk. The relaxed fit and minimalist style make it a versatile piece that complements any outfit while keeping you warm in effortless fashion.
Material: Polyester-White duck down
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/alpine-chill-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_14_46d00421-cca8-44ff-aa6d-1051939ef4a6.png?v=1731946383</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>amara-luxe-robe</g:id>
      <g:title>Amara Luxe Robe</g:title>
      <g:description>"Wow..." It's the first thing you'll say when you touch this beauty for the first time. This long cashmere knit cardigan, inspired by Japanese minimalism, features a modern hooded design and a waist tie for a flattering silhouette. Crafted from 100% pure baby cashmere, it offers unmatched softness and warmth, making it a must-have for cooler days. The intricate woven patterns add a unique, contemporary touch, making it perfect for women who value sophistication and comfort. Created for modern, confident women, this piece effortlessly blends casual sophistication with refined elegance.

Material: +30% Baby Cashmere -70% Wool
Size: One Size-Fits all
Length 40.16 Bust  47.24 Sleeve Length 27.56inch



 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/amara-luxe-robe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_97.png?v=1736445255</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>390.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>qyckaby-mens-2024-summer-men-soft-eva-sole-sandals-breathable-anti-skid-casual-shoes-outdoor-beach-fashion-fishing-sandals-male</g:id>
      <g:title>Amsterdam</g:title>
      <g:description>When it comes to fashion, we're always one step ahead! Get ready to hit the beach in style with our New Sandal-Shoe without worring about water. These ultra-practical sandals feature a soft EVA sole for all-day comfort and superior anti-skid technology &amp; 100% breathable design. Perfect for outdoor adventures or a day of fishing, these sandals are one of a cind. 
Material: Eva



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-mens-2024-summer-men-soft-eva-sole-sandals-breathable-anti-skid-casual-shoes-outdoor-beach-fashion-fishing-sandals-male</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/RUNNING_2_IN_1_SHORTS_3.png?v=1721209359</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>26.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>arctic-chic</g:id>
      <g:title>Arctic Chic</g:title>
      <g:description>Winter can be harsh, but with the right accessories, you can conquer it in style. This luxurious fur hat, complete with detachable ear covers, combines cozy warmth with a sleek, versatile design. Created to keep you comfortable in the coldest weather, it’s an essential piece that doesn’t just protect—it elevates your winter wardrobe with elegance and sophistication.
Material: Velvet Rayon
Size: One Size fits all
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/arctic-chic</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winteeredit_4.png?v=1731353341</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>11.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>arctic-chic-skirt</g:id>
      <g:title>Arctic Chic Skirt</g:title>
      <g:description>Puffer Style Women's SkirtThis unique and modern puffer-style skirt is a standout piece for the colder months. Designed with an elastic waistband for ultimate comfort, it provides a flattering fit for every silhouette. Made from premium, insulated materials, it offers exceptional warmth without compromising on style. Whether paired with a chic sweater or a sleek jacket, this skirt is perfect for casual outings or city strolls, keeping you cozy and effortlessly fashionable.

Material: Polyester - Polyester fiber


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/arctic-chic-skirt</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vascodagama_79.png?v=1735562281</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>evoke-loose-fit-down-coat</g:id>
      <g:title>Aria Asymmetrical Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience ultimate warmth and unique style with this exceptional women's down jacket. Crafted with a loose fit and asymmetrical cuts, this jacket offers a bold, contemporary look that stands out. The distinctive design combines a cozy, relaxed silhouette with a snug, knitted finish on the cuffs, adding a touch of elegance and comfort. Made with high-quality down insulation, it ensures exceptional warmth even on the coldest days. Perfect for those who value style without compromising on functionality, this jacket is a must-have for the winter season.

Materials: Polyester-White duck down
Size: One Size fits-all


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/evoke-loose-fit-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_68.png?v=1735424765</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>aria-hooded-down-jacket</g:id>
      <g:title>Aria Hooded Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into the latest fashion trend with this oversized, long down jacket designed for both warmth and style. Featuring a cozy hood and a luxurious down filling, this jacket envelops you in comfort while adding an effortlessly chic touch to your winter wardrobe. The generous, oversized fit offers freedom of movement and a modern silhouette, making it the ultimate choice for style-conscious women who refuse to compromise on warmth. Embrace the new season’s trend with a coat that’s both functional and fashion-forward, perfect for braving the cold in style.

Materials: Premium ACETATE - White duck down

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


 


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/aria-hooded-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_72_249c13d0-aeb0-4abc-825f-09626c60048b.png?v=1735425849</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>aristella-signature-fur-coat</g:id>
      <g:title>Aristella Signature Fur Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Are you someone who loves to stand out? Do you thrive on breaking the mold and making bold, unforgettable fashion statements? If so, this jacket was made for you.
Introducing our Signature Down Jacket, a true masterpiece crafted to elevate your winter wardrobe. Designed with 100% pure Mink fur, this jacket redefines luxury with its unparalleled softness and natural elegance. The plush, imposing fur collar exudes sophistication, while the medium-length silhouette strikes the perfect balance between comfort and style.
Every detail of this design is a celebration of exclusivity and refinement. From the irresistibly soft mink fur to the precision tailoring, this jacket is more than outerwear—it’s a statement of individuality and elevated taste.

Features:

Luxuriously soft 100% Mink fur for a touch of natural opulence
+95% White duck down (fill power)
100% Polyester Fabric
Bold fur collar that enhances warmth and makes a striking statement

Signature design for women who dare to stand out

 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/aristella-signature-fur-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_55.png?v=1738774701</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>229.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>arty-cotton-dress</g:id>
      <g:title>Arty Cotton Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and effortlessly stylish with this beautiful long women's dress, designed for both comfort and versatility. The relaxed, slightly loose fit makes it flattering on all body types, while its minimalist design exudes casual, artistic charm.
Crafted from high-quality cotton sweatshirt fabric, it offers exceptional warmth and softness, making it ideal for fall and winter. The high elastic collar and elastic cuff trim add a refined touch, while the wide side pockets enhance practicality and comfort. Whether you're heading to a casual outing or simply relaxing at home, this dress effortlessly combines style and functionality.
Key Features:

High elastic collar for added warmth and style
Wide side pockets for convenience
Elastic cuff trim for a polished look
Relaxed fit, suitable for all body types
Made from soft, warm, cotton sweatshirt fabric
Casual, artistic style for everyday wear
Matterial: 70% Cotton 30% Polyester

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/arty-cotton-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_95.png?v=1736705485</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>37.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>knitted-bag-for-women-with-large-capacity-2024-new-autumn-versatile-single-shoulder-crossbody-bag-woven-bucket-bag</g:id>
      <g:title>Autumn Grace Shoulder Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>You don't need much to impress. Featuring a cute and classic design, this simple yet stylish bag offers the perfect size and large capacity for all your essentials. Ideal for the autumn season, it’s a versatile single shoulder crossbody woven bucket bag that effortlessly complements your wardrobe. Let this timeless piece become your go-to accessory for a chic and sophisticated look.

Size: 13*3.94*11.81inch / 33*10*30cm

Material: wool








                      


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/knitted-bag-for-women-with-large-capacity-2024-new-autumn-versatile-single-shoulder-crossbody-bag-woven-bucket-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_1e5867e0-20ae-40de-ba7e-798e8969eb63.png?v=1731598914</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>avant-garde-asymmetry-down-jacket</g:id>
      <g:title>Avant-Garde Asymmetry Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>This luxurious women's down jacket combines modern style with exceptional warmth, crafted to be both fashionable and functional. Designed with a unique asymmetrical cut and distinctive button closures, this long, coat-style jacket stands out for its bold, contemporary look. Its sleek, high collar adds a layer of elegance, while the premium down filling ensures warmth and comfort, even on the coldest days. A perfect balance of high-fashion aesthetics and practical design, this jacket is made for those who seek a statement piece that offers both coziness and refinement.
Material: Polyester-White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/avant-garde-asymmetry-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_80.png?v=1736686234</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>high-end-rhombus-tote-bag-large-capacity-armpit-bag-suede-shoulder-bag-portable-bucket-bag-for-women-2023-new-winter</g:id>
      <g:title>Bahia Blanca Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>We told you we’d always surprise you, and here it is! Our new addition to the 2024 Autumn collection, the High-end Rhombus Tote Bag, is the perfect blend of style and functionality. With its large capacity and laid-back, yet chic design, this suede shoulder bag is an essential for the season. Whether you're running errands or heading to a casual outing, this tote combines premium craftsmanship with practicality, making it your go-to accessory for staying organized and effortlessly stylish this Automn.

Size: 13.78*11*5.51inch  35*28*14cm
Material: Soft PU Leather




 
  


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/high-end-rhombus-tote-bag-large-capacity-armpit-bag-suede-shoulder-bag-portable-bucket-bag-for-women-2023-new-winter</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/1_5414a8df-b40f-49ce-ba2b-aba9fed2746b.webp?v=1725972443</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>43.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>qinnxer-mens-stylish-computer-bag-pu-trendy-middle-high-school-college-students-laptop-leisure-multifinonal-travel-backpack</g:id>
      <g:title>Boston</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience the perfect fusion of comfort, style, and advanced design with our High-Quality Ultralight Backpack for Men &amp; Women! Made from top-tier, anti-scratch Oxford polyester, this backpack stands out with its premium feel and stunning color that shifts subtly with the light. The high-quality material isn't just eye-catching—it's also 100% waterproof, making it ideal for any weather conditions. Inside, you'll find a padded compartment tailored for laptops up to 15.6 inches, featuring a secure clasp to keep your device safe from scratches. Plus, the backpack is equipped with a discreet anti-theft pocket at the back, providing extra security for your valuables. Elevate your daily commute and travel with this exceptional accessory!
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qinnxer-mens-stylish-computer-bag-pu-trendy-middle-high-school-college-students-laptop-leisure-multifinonal-travel-backpack</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Se69f436b575f4ba1a77c47306e6376e6F.webp?v=1724688747</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>31.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>women-men-clogs-thick-platform-slippers-indoor-outdoor-slippers-couple-diy-cartoon-slides-garden-sandals-casual-beach-flip-flops</g:id>
      <g:title>Bravous 69</g:title>
      <g:description>Unleash Creativity: The Heartbeat of Innovation and Progress! Get ready to turn heads with our latest clog sandals. Combining soft, comfortable materials with a eva high-quality, non-slip sole, these clogs are designed for ultimate wearability. Our unique designs represent the latest in fashion innovation, making them a standout addition to your wardrobe.  
Exclusively from our online store.
SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: EVA
Sandal Type: Ankle-Wrap
Style: Concise
Origin: Mainland China
Occasion: Casual
Heel Height: High (5cm-8cm)



Note:Please buy according to the foot length,fat feet suggest buying a big size！


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-men-clogs-thick-platform-slippers-indoor-outdoor-slippers-couple-diy-cartoon-slides-garden-sandals-casual-beach-flip-flops</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024collection_15.png?v=1720286800</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>womens-simple-official-document-tote-bag-computer-bag-commuting-file-bag-niche-hand-bill-of-lading-shoulder-slung-bag</g:id>
      <g:title>Brussels</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our new in at our collection, crafted for those who value both style and functionality. With a clean, structured design and timeless appeal, this bag is perfect for professionals who require a sophisticated yet practical accessory.
It offers ample space for your laptop, documents, and all the essentials you need to keep your day running smoothly. Made from high-quality genuine leather, its durable and refined finish ensures it will stand the test of time while maintaining a polished, professional look. Ideal for those who appreciate classic design and efficient organization.


SIZE: 13.58 x 2.76 x 11.81 inches / 34.5 x 7 x 30 cm.

Material: PU Leather





                   

 
  

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/womens-simple-official-document-tote-bag-computer-bag-commuting-file-bag-niche-hand-bill-of-lading-shoulder-slung-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S658c9bb3d74d4baaaca0295f4ca63ed79.webp?v=1725208280</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>26.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>small-retro-contrasting-color-bucket-bag-for-women2024-new-high-end-tote-bag-large-capacity-fashionable-single-shoulder-crossbod</g:id>
      <g:title>Busan</g:title>
      <g:description>Carry your essentials in style with our Small Retro Bucket Bag. With its trendy contrasting colors, 2024 high-end design, and spacious interior, this bag is perfect for your everyday needs. Don't miss out on this fashionable single shoulder crossbody bag!
Lining Material: POLYESTER
Main Material: PU







null
null


null
null


null
null


null
null


null
null

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/small-retro-contrasting-color-bucket-bag-for-women2024-new-high-end-tote-bag-large-capacity-fashionable-single-shoulder-crossbod</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/6_c58c12fb-2480-419f-a5a4-cb727ae34f73.png?v=1725023604</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>ca-59-luxury-sashes-spliced-sleeves-90-white-duck-down-woman-down-jacket-women-down-coats-for-winter-womens-down-coats-clothes</g:id>
      <g:title>CA-59 Luxury Sashes Spliced Sleeves 90% White Duck Down Woman Down Jacket Women Down Coats For Winter Women's Down Coats Clothes</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: NoEnName_NullPattern Type: PatchworkStyle: CasualOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongSeason: Autumn/WinterAge: MIDDLE AGEClothing Length: long（26+inch）Filling: White duck downMaterial: woolDown Weight: &lt;100gHooded: NoHign-concerned Chemical: NoneSleeve Length(cm): FullModel Number: 23CA-59Craft of Weaving: knitRelease Date: Autumn 2024Thickness: ThickDown Content: 55%Gender: WOMENWeight: 0.811gPlace Of Origin: China (mainland)Detachable Part: noneType: Asymmetric LengthDecoration: RuchedDecoration: CHAINSDecoration: SplicedDecoration: Adjustable WaistChoice: yessemi_Choice: yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/ca-59-luxury-sashes-spliced-sleeves-90-white-duck-down-woman-down-jacket-women-down-coats-for-winter-womens-down-coats-clothes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S0a7a44372d3b4803abc571bea3642a90h.webp?v=1725201324</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>153.70 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>mo-dou-thick-sole-summer-clogs-for-women-outdoor-mule-shoes-for-girls-fashion-wrapped-toe-slippers-waterproof-beach-shoes</g:id>
      <g:title>California</g:title>
      <g:description>Slip into summer with cozt Clogs! These fashion-forward mules feature a super soft and lightweight design that will keep you comfortable all day long. With a wrapped toe and waterproof construction, they're perfect for any outdoor adventure. Get ready to make a statement in these quirky and stylish clogs.


Upper Material: EVA


Heel Height: Flat (2 inch)

If your foot is a bit wide or you are on the borderline, choose the next size up.











</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mo-dou-thick-sole-summer-clogs-for-women-outdoor-mule-shoes-for-girls-fashion-wrapped-toe-slippers-waterproof-beach-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-13T150159.824.png?v=1720872141</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>high-quality-men-ultralight-backpack-for-male-soft-polyester-fashion-school-backpack-laptop-waterproof-travel-shopping-bags-hot</g:id>
      <g:title>California</g:title>
      <g:description>

Discover the ultimate blend of comfort, style, and innovation with our High-Quality Ultralight Backpack for Men &amp; Women! Crafted from premium anti-scratch Oxford polyester, this backpack offers unparalleled durability and a truly magical color that shifts with the light, making it as unique as you are. Not just stylish, it's 100% waterproof, ensuring your belongings stay safe in any weather. Inside, you'll find a secure, padded compartment designed specifically for laptops up to 15.6 inches, complete with a secure clasp to keep your device protected from scratches and impacts. Elevate your travel and daily commute with this must-have, one-of-a-kind accessory!




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/high-quality-men-ultralight-backpack-for-male-soft-polyester-fashion-school-backpack-laptop-waterproof-travel-shopping-bags-hot</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S762a6824b0254b12929745b32e3b6e09w.webp?v=1724688732</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>27.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cascade-cashmere</g:id>
      <g:title>Cascade Cashmere</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience elegance and comfort with our luxurious Cashmere Dress. This exquisite piece features a flattering cinched waist that enhances your silhouette, offering a slimming effect that exudes effortless grace. The unique asymmetrical neckline adds a sweet and sophisticated touch, making it a standout in any wardrobe. Crafted from the finest cashmere, this dress feels incredibly soft against the skin and offers unparalleled comfort. Its versatile design transitions seamlessly from casual outings to special occasions, ensuring you stay chic and cozy wherever you go.
Material: Cashmere 30% - Wool 70%
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cascade-cashmere</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_59.png?v=1734549762</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cascade-collar-coat</g:id>
      <g:title>Cascade Collar Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>This stylish and versatile long coat is the perfect blend of fashion and functionality, designed to keep you warm while making a bold statement. Featuring an asymmetrical button-up collar, it adds a touch of modern elegance and sophistication. The coat's full-length silhouette ensures maximum coverage for cold days, while the adjustable waist tie with a sleek cord belt flatters your figure and creates a customized fit. Crafted from high-quality, insulating materials, it provides exceptional warmth without compromising style. Ideal for both casual outings and formal occasions, this coat redefines winter fashion.

Material: Cotton Kashmire-White Duck down
Size: Please carefully consult the size chart


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cascade-collar-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Premium_5.png?v=1731772539</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>179.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>women-summer-eva-non-slip-slippers-ladies-7-5cm-thick-sole-hole-garden-shoes-female-fashion-outdoor-beach-sandals</g:id>
      <g:title>Chaos</g:title>
      <g:description>Take your summer fashion to the next level with these Women Non-slip Platforms! With a thick 2,9inch/7.5cm sole and unique hole design, these sandals are perfect for fashion-forward ladies who like to spread chaos (in the best way possible). Step out in style and confidence with these beauties!
SPECIFICATIONS
Features:: anti-slip, soft, comfort, odorless
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Platform Height: 3 inch
Upper Material: EVA
Insole Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA



Material: Friendly Environmental EVA material, lightweight and durable.Non-Slip Sole: EVA non-slip sole and sole lines increase increase the friction between the shoes and the ground. showers, Camps, Outdoors, etc.Seasons: Summer, Spring, AutumnSize:35/36-39/40Colors: 3 colors for choice



         


         


      


About Shipment1.If you choose to ship from China, we ship by the AliExpress Standard Shipping2.Your order is generally shipped within 72h or 48h, please kindly be more patient to wait.3.Anything please feel free to let me know,we will solve it for you as soon as possible.About Service1. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. And we will reply in 24 hours except weekends.2. If any problems comes to you, please don't worry. You can contact us first. We promise we will try everything possible to help you.3. Please pay attention to the time difference between us. We work in China.About Feedback1.Your confirmation will be highly appreciated after receiving the items. Once you have received the product, hope you could leave us a positive feedback(4 or 5 stars).2.BEFORE you leaving the negative feedback. PLEASE contact us at first, and we can help you solve the problem.3.We strive to do better and make you feel satisfied!




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-summer-eva-non-slip-slippers-ladies-7-5cm-thick-sole-hole-garden-shoes-female-fashion-outdoor-beach-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_20_e142f9eb-a7e1-4c6a-9cfb-0f19ba87999e.png?v=1721161151</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>chic-crop</g:id>
      <g:title>Chic Crop</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your wardrobe with this chic sleeveless cropped jacket, designed for the modern trendsetter. With its sleek lines and contemporary silhouette, this jacket is the perfect blend of sophistication and edge. Crafted from high-quality materials, it offers both style and comfort, making it an ideal layering piece for any season.
Material: Nylon - Polyester fiber
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.
Whether you pair it with a flowy dress for a fresh, feminine look or with tailored pants for a polished ensemble, this jacket effortlessly enhances any outfit. Its versatile design and striking details ensure you'll stand out in any crowd. Embrace a bold, fashion-forward style with this must-have addition to your collection!
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/chic-crop</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_42.png?v=1738582228</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>chic-switch-reversible-coat</g:id>
      <g:title>Chic Switch Reversible Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this long, elegant, dual-sided down coat featuring a refined stand collar and a chic silhouette. Its reversible design offers you two stunning color combinations in one—perfect for those days when you just can't decide on the right shade to match your look. From classic outings to casual strolls, this coat seamlessly complements every occasion with its sophisticated style and versatility. Why settle for one look when you can have two in one?

Material: Nylon-Polyester

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/chic-switch-reversible-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Certificate_of_Completion_9.png?v=1731171320</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>36.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>chicfit-pique-cap</g:id>
      <g:title>ChicFit Piqué Cap</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into the latest fashion trend with this chic and sophisticated hat, meticulously crafted from premium piqué fabric. Its refined texture adds a unique touch of elegance, making it a must-have accessory for women with an eye for style. Designed to enhance your presence, this hat exudes a sense of prestige and confidence, perfect for those who appreciate haute couture.
Whether you're dressing up for a special occasion or adding a statement piece to your everyday look, this versatile hat effortlessly complements almost any outfit. Made for the modern woman who values both fashion and quality, it's a timeless addition to your wardrobe that seamlessly blends luxury with contemporary trends.
The cap's adjustable fit ensures it comfortably suits 99,9% of head sizes, offering both style and a perfect fit for almost everyone.


FABRIC: Cotton

COLOR: See details

SIZE: One Size (Αdjustment Cord)  
Head circumference: 22.05-23.62 inches (56-60 cm) ,
Hat depth: 4.33 inches (11 cm),
Brim width: 2.17 inches (5.5 cm).

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/chicfit-pique-cap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_5.png?v=1742498730</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2023-summer-womens-two-buckle-slippers-pu-leather-flats-sandals-for-women-retro-fashion-garden-mule-clog-slides-casual-shoes</g:id>
      <g:title>Cibon</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into luxury with the all-new 2024 VdaGamas Collection. These chic and trendy flats are designed to add a touch of sophistication to any outfit. Crafted with premium PU leather, each pair promises not only style but also durability and comfort. Whether you're dressing up for a special occasion or elevating your everyday look, the VdaGamas flats are your perfect companion. Experience the blend of elegance and modern design that defines the 2024 VdaGamas Collection and transform your wardrobe with these exquisite pieces.
SPECIFICATIONS


Platform Height: 1.6 inch


Upper Material: PU


Insole Material: RUBBER



Inner material: PU


If you are not sure about  the number, beat it up one size

  

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2023-summer-womens-two-buckle-slippers-pu-leather-flats-sandals-for-women-retro-fashion-garden-mule-clog-slides-casual-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_63.png?v=1721330158</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>classic-fit-turtleneck-sweater</g:id>
      <g:title>Classic Fit Turtleneck Sweater</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and stylish with this chic turtleneck sweater, designed for a more fitted and slightly shorter look than traditional oversized knits. Crafted from a soft, warm fabric, it features subtle side slits for ease of movement and a sophisticated silhouette. The turtleneck adds a touch of elegance, making it perfect for layering under coats or wearing on its own for a polished winter look. 
Material: 100% Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/classic-fit-turtleneck-sweater</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/35_7e1edbe6-3306-43ad-b5a5-143512ab94aa.png?v=1731246176</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>thick-bottom-sandals-for-women-black-white-slippers-outdoor-fashion-pearl-luxurious-diamond-diy-garden-sandals-clogs-water-shoes</g:id>
      <g:title>Clog 21</g:title>
      <g:description>Step out in style with these Thick Bottom Sandals! The classic design and standard fit will have you feeling luxurious with every step. Perfect for any activitie, these sandals feature pearls and diamonds that you can DIY for a personalized touch. They're also versatile enough to be worn as clogs or water shoes. Upgrade your footwear game today!


Material: EVA


Heel Height: High (3,14inch)



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/thick-bottom-sandals-for-women-black-white-slippers-outdoor-fashion-pearl-luxurious-diamond-diy-garden-sandals-clogs-water-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_49.png?v=1721213271</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>qyckaby-summer-hole-shoes-women-baotou-outdoor-sole-beach-slides-home-outdoor-wear-comfortable-soft-sole-non-slip-garden-sandals</g:id>
      <g:title>Clog 323</g:title>
      <g:description>Put your best foot forward this summer with this Clogs. These baotou style slides feature a classic design and a comfortable fit, perfect for long hours on your feet. Whether you're at the beach, in the garden or at work, the soft non-slip sole will keep you feeling supported and stylish. 
SPECIFICATIONS


Upper Material: EVA


Heel Height: Med ( Up to 1,9 inch)


Insole Material: EVA













</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-summer-hole-shoes-women-baotou-outdoor-sole-beach-slides-home-outdoor-wear-comfortable-soft-sole-non-slip-garden-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sd6196e9a988040f282e1d5c165e282d1i.webp?v=1720431574</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cloudburst-puffer</g:id>
      <g:title>CloudBurst Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay warm and stylish with this ultra-padded women's puffer jacket, designed for sporty yet chic looks. Featuring a generously filled design for maximum warmth, a sleek silhouette, and a functional hood to shield you from the elements, it’s the ultimate choice for winter adventures. Perfect for casual outings, outdoor activities, or layering over your favorite athleisure outfit, this jacket combines comfort and cutting-edge style effortlessly. Available in versatile colors to match any wardrobe.

Material: Polyester/Polyester Fiber
Size: Please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cloudburst-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_49.png?v=1738583145</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>colorblend-plaid-pullover</g:id>
      <g:title>ColorBlend Plaid Pullover</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover our new woolen women’s sweater featuring a timeless plaid design in stunning color combinations. This oversized, stylish casual piece is perfect for everyday wear or relaxed outings. Crafted from high-quality materials for warmth and softness, it’s a must-have for women who want to make an effortless style statement.

Material: Wool -30% - Acrylic +70%

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/colorblend-plaid-pullover</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_45_0902c442-18b2-48b2-8efb-62ab70e518c9.png?v=1738583450</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>comunale-tote-bag</g:id>
      <g:title>Comunale Set. Tote Bag/Neseser</g:title>
      <g:description>Suede Classic Monochrome Bag Set
This elegant suede bag offers a timeless, monochrome design that effortlessly complements any outfit. With its spacious interior, it’s perfect for carrying all your daily essentials. The set includes a matching pouch, ideal for organizing smaller items like keys, makeup, or your phone. Whether you're heading to work or a casual outing, this classic bag set combines style with functionality for the modern individual.
SIZE: 14.7*12.2*5.1inch / 36*31*13cm
MATERIAL: POLYESTER / CASTOR
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/comunale-tote-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vdaga_24_d5d4537c-aa4b-4244-8135-0f34fcc21d7b.png?v=1726321419</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>contrast-core-long-vest</g:id>
      <g:title>Contrast Core Long Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover a stylish and versatile addition to your wardrobe with this long, sleeveless women's jacket. Designed with a cozy hood and a belt at the waist for a flattering silhouette, this jacket offers a unique touch with its contrasting inner lining. The inner color subtly peeks through, creating a striking look that sets this piece apart. Perfect for layering in cooler weather, this jacket combines practicality with contemporary style.

Material: Polyester - White duck down


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/contrast-core-long-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_52.png?v=1738590712</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>79.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cotton-cloud-puffer</g:id>
      <g:title>Cotton Cloud Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and stylish with this sporty, short-length cotton down jacket. Featuring a unique knit-like texture for a modern look, this jacket combines exceptional warmth with lightweight comfort. Its premium down filling ensures superior insulation, making it perfect for chilly days. Designed to be versatile and trendy, it’s a must-have piece for layering or wearing on its own. Ideal for everyday wear or outdoor adventures, this jacket is the perfect blend of functionality and fashion.
      Material:

Cotton 75% 
Polyester 25% 
White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cotton-cloud-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama.jpg?v=1733234794</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>couture-crown-hat</g:id>
      <g:title>Couture Crown Hat</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with our timelessly elegant women's hat, designed for those who appreciate sophistication and flair. Crafted with impeccable attention to detail, this chic accessory features a structured yet soft silhouette that complements any outfit. Whether paired with a tailored coat for a refined look or worn with casual outerwear for effortless glamour, this hat is the perfect blend of classic design and modern appeal. A must-have for women who value style and versatility in every season.

Material: Polyester
Size: One Size - Adjustable

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/couture-crown-hat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_41_39bb0623-2e7c-4169-ac25-35c3023f218d.png?v=1734464589</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>11.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>couture-grandeur-down-coat</g:id>
      <g:title>Couture Grandeur Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>This women’s long down coat exudes timeless elegance and sophistication. Crafted to perfection, it features an exceptionally high collar that not only enhances its sleek silhouette but also offers superior warmth and protection against the cold. Filled with premium down, this coat is both lightweight and incredibly insulating, making it ideal for chilly weather. Its streamlined design and graceful length make it a standout piece that seamlessly combines luxury with modern style. Designed for those who appreciate uniqueness in every detail, this coat is an embodiment of refined taste and class.
Material: Acetate - White duck down
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/couture-grandeur-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_56.png?v=1738591861</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cozy-luxe-turtleneck</g:id>
      <g:title>Cozy Luxe Turtleneck</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in effortless elegance with our oversized knit turtleneck sweater. Designed with a relaxed silhouette and long, cozy sleeves, this timeless piece is both stylish and versatile. The soft turtleneck adds warmth and sophistication, making it perfect for layering or wearing on its own during cooler days.
Material: Acrylic
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cozy-luxe-turtleneck</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winter_edi_21.png?v=1733918077</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cozy-side-slit-turtleneck-sweater</g:id>
      <g:title>Cozy Side-Slit Turtleneck Sweater</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in cozy elegance with this long, relaxed-fit turtleneck sweater. Designed for style and comfort, it features side slits for effortless movement and a touch of sophistication. This sweater’s soft knit fabric and chic turtleneck make it perfect for layering or wearing on its own for a laid-back yet polished look. Ideal for pairing with jeans, leggings, or even skirts, it’s a versatile addition to any fall and winter wardrobe.
Material: 100% Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cozy-side-slit-turtleneck-sweater</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/28_43223dea-6b9f-4ae0-8c9a-e0355eef2090.png?v=1731244672</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>crestar-platform-soft-eva-slippers-for-women-men-fashion-comfortable-unisex-home-sandals-bathroom-non-slip-slides-beach-shoes</g:id>
      <g:title>Crestar Platform</g:title>
      <g:description>Step up your comfort game with Crestar Platform Soft Eva Slippers! These slippers feature a super soft and cozy design that will make you feel like you're walking on a cloud. The platform adds a stylish touch while providing extra support. Perfect for wearing at home or on the beach, these slippers are non-slip and unisex, making them a must-have for any wardrobe.


Material: Eva





</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/crestar-platform-soft-eva-slippers-for-women-men-fashion-comfortable-unisex-home-sandals-bathroom-non-slip-slides-beach-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-16T222423.029.png?v=1721210148</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>qyckaby-2024-summer-new-style-women-outer-sandals-ladies-casual-slippers-diy-decoration-thick-bottom-work-and-party-garden-shoes</g:id>
      <g:title>Cuba Clogs</g:title>
      <g:description>Stepping forward in life is the only way to survive.. 
Versatile sandals feature an anti-bacterial material, perfect for all-day wear. Add your own unique touch with DIY decorations, and enjoy the thick bottom for added support. 


Exclusively at VdaGama.com

SPECIFICATIONS
With Platforms: Yes
Sandal Type: clogs
Occasion: Casual
Upper Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA
Fit: Fits smaller than usual. Please check this store's sizing info
Style: LEISURE
Lining Material: none
Insole Material: EVA



















</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-2024-summer-new-style-women-outer-sandals-ladies-casual-slippers-diy-decoration-thick-bottom-work-and-party-garden-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_20.png?v=1721159824</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cuff-signature</g:id>
      <g:title>Cuff Signature</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience effortless style with this refined women's dress, designed to blend simplicity with sophistication. Ιts classic, streamlined silhouette ensures a timeless appeal. The highlight of this dress is the four signature buttons on the cuffs—an understated yet striking detail that adds a unique touch of character.

Material: Alasi

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cuff-signature</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_59.png?v=1738592683</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>echelon-longline-vest</g:id>
      <g:title>Echelon Asymmetrical Longline Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your wardrobe with our luxurious sleeveless puffer vest, a perfect blend of sophistication and functionality. Crafted to complement any outfit with ease, this vest boasts a high collar and an elegantly tailored longline silhouette, exuding timeless style. A striking asymmetrical design subtly conceals the zipper beneath an overlapping panel, ensuring a sleek, uninterrupted look while providing enhanced wind protection for your chest.
Meticulously crafted from premium materials, this vest offers not only exceptional warmth but also an indulgent sense of comfort. Its versatile design makes it ideal for layering, effortlessly transitioning between casual and refined ensembles. Whether worn on a crisp morning stroll or as an elevated addition to your chic winter wardrobe, this piece epitomizes understated elegance and superior craftsmanship. A true statement of sophistication, this puffer vest is an essential for those with a discerning eye for style and quality.

Material: Polyester

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/echelon-longline-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_57_a7907ac1-1f92-4cf1-a7f8-0253b16a7e72.png?v=1738594005</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>43.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>cloud-bag-bag-for-women-fashion-pleated-small-bag-wooden-handle-simple-tote-bags-for-ladies</g:id>
      <g:title>Eclipse Grandeur Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience unparalleled sophistication with our exquisitely chic hand-shoulder bag. Designed for the modern woman with a taste for timeless elegance, this bag features a stunning wooden handle that adds a unique and luxurious touch. Its sleek design and high-quality craftsmanship make it the epitome of refined style, ensuring you’ll make a statement of elegance wherever you go.

Size: 9.84*0.89*7inch / 25cmx2x18cm

Main Material: PU LEATHER              

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cloud-bag-bag-for-women-fashion-pleated-small-bag-wooden-handle-simple-tote-bags-for-ladies</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/23.webp?v=1726396930</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>edgeflow-knit</g:id>
      <g:title>EdgeFlow Knit</g:title>
      <g:description>Unleash your style with a modern twist. This loose, long turtleneck sweater redefines comfort and elegance. Featuring unique, artistic cutouts, it adds a bold and contemporary edge to a classic design. Its relaxed fit offers effortless movement, while the high neckline brings a touch of sophistication. Perfect for layering or wearing as a statement piece, this sweater is a go-to for women seeking versatile and chic wardrobe staples.

Material: Acrylic

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/edgeflow-knit</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/60_52ce764a-bb63-41c1-a907-7b1e5b7548e9.png?v=1733938236</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>eleve-quilted-down-jacket</g:id>
      <g:title>Elevé Quilted Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in ultimate warmth and effortless style with this luxurious women's down jacket. Featuring a loose-fit design for a relaxed, sporty look, this ultra-thick and cozy piece is perfect for chilly days. Its refined high collar and unique piqué-textured fabric set it apart, showcasing a high-fashion aesthetic that's both sophisticated and practical. A true statement of elevated craftsmanship, this jacket is a premium investment in comfort and elegance.
      Material:

Polyester
White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/eleve-quilted-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winteredi.png?v=1733762426</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>