<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>VDagama Product Feed</title>
    <link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com</link>
    <description>Facebook Product Feed</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445288542472</g:id>
      <g:title>2024 New fashion Women's soft leather Retro Fashion High-grade Single crossbody Messenger Bag Bamboo handle Bag Shoulder Purse</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: DKQWAITOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongLining Material: Organic CottonMain Material: Microfiber Synthetic LeatherPlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvincePlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvinceShape: Casual ToteOccasion: VersatileExterior: noneModel Number: 665652Closure Type: zipperDecoration: AppliquesHardness: SOFTGender: WOMENPattern Type: SolidStyle: fashion</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-new-fashion-womens-soft-leather-retro-fashion-high-grade-single-crossbody-messenger-bag-bamboo-handle-bag-shoulder-purse</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S062a747324a84b5fa35c8c22aec9472aw.webp?v=1724763205</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>58.24 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450776658184</g:id>
      <g:title>2024 New Niche Minimalist Tote Advanced Spring Summer Large-capacity Commuter Single Shoulder Underarm Fashion Trend Soft Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: NoEnName_NullHign-concerned Chemical: NoneHandbags Type: Shoulder BagsTypes of bags: Shoulder &amp; HandbagsMain Material: PULining Material: NoneShape: Half MoonPlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvincePlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvinceOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongDecoration: noneGender: WOMENStyle: fashionNumber of Handles/Straps: twofashion element: sewing threadCLOSED WAY: magnetic snap 


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-new-niche-minimalist-tote-advanced-spring-summer-large-capacity-commuter-single-shoulder-underarm-fashion-trend-soft-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S70f5905006444adcb8acb3d1e3aa5765G.webp?v=1725203476</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>15.25 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9613923942664</g:id>
      <g:title>Airy Luxe Merino Tee</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the perfect blend of comfort and elegance with this oversized, relaxed-fit women's top crafted from 100% premium fine wool. Designed to drape effortlessly over your silhouette, this lightweight top offers unmatched breathability and softness, making it ideal for year-round wear. Whether you're layering it on chilly days or wearing it solo in warmer weather, its natural temperature-regulating properties keep you cozy and comfortable.

Material: Wool

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/airy-luxe-merino-tee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama-2025-01-14T140006.529.png?v=1736858336</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9372590145800</g:id>
      <g:title>All-match Men's Cool Outdoor Slippers Men's Hollow Out Summer Sandals Leather Thick-soled Beach Shoes Non-slip Handmade Sandals</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONS
Brand Name: YEISNDOO
Upper Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Upper-Genuine Leather Type: Cow Leather
Sandal Type: basic
Style: Concise
Origin: Mainland China
Occasion: Casual
Outsole Material: RUBBER
Heel Height: Flat (≤1cm)
Pattern Type: Solid
Insole Material: EVA
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Model Number: 9696
Lining Material: none
Closure Type: SLIP-ON
Item Type: sandals
Fashion Element: Sewing
Department Name: ADULT






 Tips:1. This is NOT Standard EUR Size. The foot length is the only standard for choose size.2. Insole length should be 1-1.5cm bigger than your foot length.3.Order is without shoes box. 






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/all-match-mens-cool-outdoor-slippers-mens-hollow-out-summer-sandals-leather-thick-soled-beach-shoes-non-slip-handmade-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sec2d552eac9241d5adb9ac218fe271577.webp?v=1720362858</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>28.78 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9582603108616</g:id>
      <g:title>Alpaca Royale Oversized Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>True inner beauty deserves to be mirrored by something equally exquisite on the outside. This oversized alpaca wool fur coat is a testament to refined luxury and timeless elegance. Expertly crafted from 100% premium alpaca wool—renowned for its unparalleled softness and natural warmth—it offers a plush texture and sophisticated design that radiates prestige. As the saying goes, "Style is a way to say who you are without speaking," and this coat speaks volumes. It transforms the woman who wears it into a vision of grace and power, seamlessly blending comfort with unmatched sophistication.
Material: Alpaca Wool +98%
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/alpaca-royale-oversized-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_23.png?v=1733773290</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>490.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9556064829704</g:id>
      <g:title>Alpine Chill Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and stylish this winter with our casual duck down jacket, designed for warmth and everyday comfort. Featuring a lightweight, shorter design and a snug hood, this jacket is perfect for casual outings or layering on colder days. Made with premium duck down filling, it ensures excellent insulation without the bulk. The relaxed fit and minimalist style make it a versatile piece that complements any outfit while keeping you warm in effortless fashion.
Material: Polyester-White duck down
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/alpine-chill-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_14_46d00421-cca8-44ff-aa6d-1051939ef4a6.png?v=1731946383</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585359454472</g:id>
      <g:title>Amara Luxe Robe</g:title>
      <g:description>"Wow..." It's the first thing you'll say when you touch this beauty for the first time. This long cashmere knit cardigan, inspired by Japanese minimalism, features a modern hooded design and a waist tie for a flattering silhouette. Crafted from 100% pure baby cashmere, it offers unmatched softness and warmth, making it a must-have for cooler days. The intricate woven patterns add a unique, contemporary touch, making it perfect for women who value sophistication and comfort. Created for modern, confident women, this piece effortlessly blends casual sophistication with refined elegance.

Material: +30% Baby Cashmere -70% Wool
Size: One Size-Fits all
Length 40.16 Bust  47.24 Sleeve Length 27.56inch



 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/amara-luxe-robe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_97.png?v=1736445255</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>390.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370193953032</g:id>
      <g:title>Amsterdam</g:title>
      <g:description>When it comes to fashion, we're always one step ahead! Get ready to hit the beach in style with our New Sandal-Shoe without worring about water. These ultra-practical sandals feature a soft EVA sole for all-day comfort and superior anti-skid technology &amp; 100% breathable design. Perfect for outdoor adventures or a day of fishing, these sandals are one of a cind. 
Material: Eva



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-mens-2024-summer-men-soft-eva-sole-sandals-breathable-anti-skid-casual-shoes-outdoor-beach-fashion-fishing-sandals-male</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/RUNNING_2_IN_1_SHORTS_3.png?v=1721209359</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>26.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9549254230280</g:id>
      <g:title>Arctic Chic</g:title>
      <g:description>Winter can be harsh, but with the right accessories, you can conquer it in style. This luxurious fur hat, complete with detachable ear covers, combines cozy warmth with a sleek, versatile design. Created to keep you comfortable in the coldest weather, it’s an essential piece that doesn’t just protect—it elevates your winter wardrobe with elegance and sophistication.
Material: Velvet Rayon
Size: One Size fits all
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/arctic-chic</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winteeredit_4.png?v=1731353341</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>11.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9600048890120</g:id>
      <g:title>Arctic Chic Skirt</g:title>
      <g:description>Puffer Style Women's SkirtThis unique and modern puffer-style skirt is a standout piece for the colder months. Designed with an elastic waistband for ultimate comfort, it provides a flattering fit for every silhouette. Made from premium, insulated materials, it offers exceptional warmth without compromising on style. Whether paired with a chic sweater or a sleek jacket, this skirt is perfect for casual outings or city strolls, keeping you cozy and effortlessly fashionable.

Material: Polyester - Polyester fiber


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/arctic-chic-skirt</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vascodagama_79.png?v=1735562281</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9546700947720</g:id>
      <g:title>Aria Asymmetrical Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience ultimate warmth and unique style with this exceptional women's down jacket. Crafted with a loose fit and asymmetrical cuts, this jacket offers a bold, contemporary look that stands out. The distinctive design combines a cozy, relaxed silhouette with a snug, knitted finish on the cuffs, adding a touch of elegance and comfort. Made with high-quality down insulation, it ensures exceptional warmth even on the coldest days. Perfect for those who value style without compromising on functionality, this jacket is a must-have for the winter season.

Materials: Polyester-White duck down
Size: One Size fits-all


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/evoke-loose-fit-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_68.png?v=1735424765</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9532886221064</g:id>
      <g:title>Aria Hooded Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into the latest fashion trend with this oversized, long down jacket designed for both warmth and style. Featuring a cozy hood and a luxurious down filling, this jacket envelops you in comfort while adding an effortlessly chic touch to your winter wardrobe. The generous, oversized fit offers freedom of movement and a modern silhouette, making it the ultimate choice for style-conscious women who refuse to compromise on warmth. Embrace the new season’s trend with a coat that’s both functional and fashion-forward, perfect for braving the cold in style.

Materials: Premium ACETATE - White duck down

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


 


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/aria-hooded-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_72_249c13d0-aeb0-4abc-825f-09626c60048b.png?v=1735425849</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9586333417736</g:id>
      <g:title>Aristella Signature Fur Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Are you someone who loves to stand out? Do you thrive on breaking the mold and making bold, unforgettable fashion statements? If so, this jacket was made for you.
Introducing our Signature Down Jacket, a true masterpiece crafted to elevate your winter wardrobe. Designed with 100% pure Mink fur, this jacket redefines luxury with its unparalleled softness and natural elegance. The plush, imposing fur collar exudes sophistication, while the medium-length silhouette strikes the perfect balance between comfort and style.
Every detail of this design is a celebration of exclusivity and refinement. From the irresistibly soft mink fur to the precision tailoring, this jacket is more than outerwear—it’s a statement of individuality and elevated taste.

Features:

Luxuriously soft 100% Mink fur for a touch of natural opulence
+95% White duck down (fill power)
100% Polyester Fabric
Bold fur collar that enhances warmth and makes a striking statement

Signature design for women who dare to stand out

 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/aristella-signature-fur-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_55.png?v=1738774701</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>229.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9611098292488</g:id>
      <g:title>Arty Cotton Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and effortlessly stylish with this beautiful long women's dress, designed for both comfort and versatility. The relaxed, slightly loose fit makes it flattering on all body types, while its minimalist design exudes casual, artistic charm.
Crafted from high-quality cotton sweatshirt fabric, it offers exceptional warmth and softness, making it ideal for fall and winter. The high elastic collar and elastic cuff trim add a refined touch, while the wide side pockets enhance practicality and comfort. Whether you're heading to a casual outing or simply relaxing at home, this dress effortlessly combines style and functionality.
Key Features:

High elastic collar for added warmth and style
Wide side pockets for convenience
Elastic cuff trim for a polished look
Relaxed fit, suitable for all body types
Made from soft, warm, cotton sweatshirt fabric
Casual, artistic style for everyday wear
Matterial: 70% Cotton 30% Polyester

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/arty-cotton-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_95.png?v=1736705485</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>37.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9444314120456</g:id>
      <g:title>Autumn Grace Shoulder Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>You don't need much to impress. Featuring a cute and classic design, this simple yet stylish bag offers the perfect size and large capacity for all your essentials. Ideal for the autumn season, it’s a versatile single shoulder crossbody woven bucket bag that effortlessly complements your wardrobe. Let this timeless piece become your go-to accessory for a chic and sophisticated look.

Size: 13*3.94*11.81inch / 33*10*30cm

Material: wool








                      


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/knitted-bag-for-women-with-large-capacity-2024-new-autumn-versatile-single-shoulder-crossbody-bag-woven-bucket-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_1e5867e0-20ae-40de-ba7e-798e8969eb63.png?v=1731598914</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533320691976</g:id>
      <g:title>Avant-Garde Asymmetry Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>This luxurious women's down jacket combines modern style with exceptional warmth, crafted to be both fashionable and functional. Designed with a unique asymmetrical cut and distinctive button closures, this long, coat-style jacket stands out for its bold, contemporary look. Its sleek, high collar adds a layer of elegance, while the premium down filling ensures warmth and comfort, even on the coldest days. A perfect balance of high-fashion aesthetics and practical design, this jacket is made for those who seek a statement piece that offers both coziness and refinement.
Material: Polyester-White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/avant-garde-asymmetry-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_80.png?v=1736686234</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450796187912</g:id>
      <g:title>Bahia Blanca Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>We told you we’d always surprise you, and here it is! Our new addition to the 2024 Autumn collection, the High-end Rhombus Tote Bag, is the perfect blend of style and functionality. With its large capacity and laid-back, yet chic design, this suede shoulder bag is an essential for the season. Whether you're running errands or heading to a casual outing, this tote combines premium craftsmanship with practicality, making it your go-to accessory for staying organized and effortlessly stylish this Automn.

Size: 13.78*11*5.51inch  35*28*14cm
Material: Soft PU Leather




 
  


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/high-end-rhombus-tote-bag-large-capacity-armpit-bag-suede-shoulder-bag-portable-bucket-bag-for-women-2023-new-winter</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/1_5414a8df-b40f-49ce-ba2b-aba9fed2746b.webp?v=1725972443</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>43.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9444183703816</g:id>
      <g:title>Boston</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience the perfect fusion of comfort, style, and advanced design with our High-Quality Ultralight Backpack for Men &amp; Women! Made from top-tier, anti-scratch Oxford polyester, this backpack stands out with its premium feel and stunning color that shifts subtly with the light. The high-quality material isn't just eye-catching—it's also 100% waterproof, making it ideal for any weather conditions. Inside, you'll find a padded compartment tailored for laptops up to 15.6 inches, featuring a secure clasp to keep your device safe from scratches. Plus, the backpack is equipped with a discreet anti-theft pocket at the back, providing extra security for your valuables. Elevate your daily commute and travel with this exceptional accessory!
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qinnxer-mens-stylish-computer-bag-pu-trendy-middle-high-school-college-students-laptop-leisure-multifinonal-travel-backpack</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Se69f436b575f4ba1a77c47306e6376e6F.webp?v=1724688747</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>31.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9371519058184</g:id>
      <g:title>Bravous 69</g:title>
      <g:description>Unleash Creativity: The Heartbeat of Innovation and Progress! Get ready to turn heads with our latest clog sandals. Combining soft, comfortable materials with a eva high-quality, non-slip sole, these clogs are designed for ultimate wearability. Our unique designs represent the latest in fashion innovation, making them a standout addition to your wardrobe.  
Exclusively from our online store.
SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: EVA
Sandal Type: Ankle-Wrap
Style: Concise
Origin: Mainland China
Occasion: Casual
Heel Height: High (5cm-8cm)



Note:Please buy according to the foot length,fat feet suggest buying a big size！


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-men-clogs-thick-platform-slippers-indoor-outdoor-slippers-couple-diy-cartoon-slides-garden-sandals-casual-beach-flip-flops</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024collection_15.png?v=1720286800</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450793074952</g:id>
      <g:title>Brussels</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our new in at our collection, crafted for those who value both style and functionality. With a clean, structured design and timeless appeal, this bag is perfect for professionals who require a sophisticated yet practical accessory.
It offers ample space for your laptop, documents, and all the essentials you need to keep your day running smoothly. Made from high-quality genuine leather, its durable and refined finish ensures it will stand the test of time while maintaining a polished, professional look. Ideal for those who appreciate classic design and efficient organization.


SIZE: 13.58 x 2.76 x 11.81 inches / 34.5 x 7 x 30 cm.

Material: PU Leather





                   

 
  

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/womens-simple-official-document-tote-bag-computer-bag-commuting-file-bag-niche-hand-bill-of-lading-shoulder-slung-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S658c9bb3d74d4baaaca0295f4ca63ed79.webp?v=1725208280</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>26.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9443532374280</g:id>
      <g:title>Busan</g:title>
      <g:description>Carry your essentials in style with our Small Retro Bucket Bag. With its trendy contrasting colors, 2024 high-end design, and spacious interior, this bag is perfect for your everyday needs. Don't miss out on this fashionable single shoulder crossbody bag!
Lining Material: POLYESTER
Main Material: PU







null
null


null
null


null
null


null
null


null
null

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/small-retro-contrasting-color-bucket-bag-for-women2024-new-high-end-tote-bag-large-capacity-fashionable-single-shoulder-crossbod</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/6_c58c12fb-2480-419f-a5a4-cb727ae34f73.png?v=1725023604</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450768957704</g:id>
      <g:title>CA-59 Luxury Sashes Spliced Sleeves 90% White Duck Down Woman Down Jacket Women Down Coats For Winter Women's Down Coats Clothes</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: NoEnName_NullPattern Type: PatchworkStyle: CasualOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongSeason: Autumn/WinterAge: MIDDLE AGEClothing Length: long（26+inch）Filling: White duck downMaterial: woolDown Weight: &lt;100gHooded: NoHign-concerned Chemical: NoneSleeve Length(cm): FullModel Number: 23CA-59Craft of Weaving: knitRelease Date: Autumn 2024Thickness: ThickDown Content: 55%Gender: WOMENWeight: 0.811gPlace Of Origin: China (mainland)Detachable Part: noneType: Asymmetric LengthDecoration: RuchedDecoration: CHAINSDecoration: SplicedDecoration: Adjustable WaistChoice: yessemi_Choice: yes</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/ca-59-luxury-sashes-spliced-sleeves-90-white-duck-down-woman-down-jacket-women-down-coats-for-winter-womens-down-coats-clothes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S0a7a44372d3b4803abc571bea3642a90h.webp?v=1725201324</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>153.70 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375035097352</g:id>
      <g:title>California</g:title>
      <g:description>Slip into summer with cozt Clogs! These fashion-forward mules feature a super soft and lightweight design that will keep you comfortable all day long. With a wrapped toe and waterproof construction, they're perfect for any outdoor adventure. Get ready to make a statement in these quirky and stylish clogs.


Upper Material: EVA


Heel Height: Flat (2 inch)

If your foot is a bit wide or you are on the borderline, choose the next size up.











</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mo-dou-thick-sole-summer-clogs-for-women-outdoor-mule-shoes-for-girls-fashion-wrapped-toe-slippers-waterproof-beach-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-13T150159.824.png?v=1720872141</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9444183113992</g:id>
      <g:title>California</g:title>
      <g:description>

Discover the ultimate blend of comfort, style, and innovation with our High-Quality Ultralight Backpack for Men &amp; Women! Crafted from premium anti-scratch Oxford polyester, this backpack offers unparalleled durability and a truly magical color that shifts with the light, making it as unique as you are. Not just stylish, it's 100% waterproof, ensuring your belongings stay safe in any weather. Inside, you'll find a secure, padded compartment designed specifically for laptops up to 15.6 inches, complete with a secure clasp to keep your device protected from scratches and impacts. Elevate your travel and daily commute with this must-have, one-of-a-kind accessory!




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/high-quality-men-ultralight-backpack-for-male-soft-polyester-fashion-school-backpack-laptop-waterproof-travel-shopping-bags-hot</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S762a6824b0254b12929745b32e3b6e09w.webp?v=1724688732</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>27.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9590809461000</g:id>
      <g:title>Cascade Cashmere</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience elegance and comfort with our luxurious Cashmere Dress. This exquisite piece features a flattering cinched waist that enhances your silhouette, offering a slimming effect that exudes effortless grace. The unique asymmetrical neckline adds a sweet and sophisticated touch, making it a standout in any wardrobe. Crafted from the finest cashmere, this dress feels incredibly soft against the skin and offers unparalleled comfort. Its versatile design transitions seamlessly from casual outings to special occasions, ensuring you stay chic and cozy wherever you go.
Material: Cashmere 30% - Wool 70%
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cascade-cashmere</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_59.png?v=1734549762</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554652266760</g:id>
      <g:title>Cascade Collar Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>This stylish and versatile long coat is the perfect blend of fashion and functionality, designed to keep you warm while making a bold statement. Featuring an asymmetrical button-up collar, it adds a touch of modern elegance and sophistication. The coat's full-length silhouette ensures maximum coverage for cold days, while the adjustable waist tie with a sleek cord belt flatters your figure and creates a customized fit. Crafted from high-quality, insulating materials, it provides exceptional warmth without compromising style. Ideal for both casual outings and formal occasions, this coat redefines winter fashion.

Material: Cotton Kashmire-White Duck down
Size: Please carefully consult the size chart


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cascade-collar-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Premium_5.png?v=1731772539</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>179.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370194673928</g:id>
      <g:title>Chaos</g:title>
      <g:description>Take your summer fashion to the next level with these Women Non-slip Platforms! With a thick 2,9inch/7.5cm sole and unique hole design, these sandals are perfect for fashion-forward ladies who like to spread chaos (in the best way possible). Step out in style and confidence with these beauties!
SPECIFICATIONS
Features:: anti-slip, soft, comfort, odorless
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Platform Height: 3 inch
Upper Material: EVA
Insole Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA



Material: Friendly Environmental EVA material, lightweight and durable.Non-Slip Sole: EVA non-slip sole and sole lines increase increase the friction between the shoes and the ground. showers, Camps, Outdoors, etc.Seasons: Summer, Spring, AutumnSize:35/36-39/40Colors: 3 colors for choice



         


         


      


About Shipment1.If you choose to ship from China, we ship by the AliExpress Standard Shipping2.Your order is generally shipped within 72h or 48h, please kindly be more patient to wait.3.Anything please feel free to let me know,we will solve it for you as soon as possible.About Service1. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. And we will reply in 24 hours except weekends.2. If any problems comes to you, please don't worry. You can contact us first. We promise we will try everything possible to help you.3. Please pay attention to the time difference between us. We work in China.About Feedback1.Your confirmation will be highly appreciated after receiving the items. Once you have received the product, hope you could leave us a positive feedback(4 or 5 stars).2.BEFORE you leaving the negative feedback. PLEASE contact us at first, and we can help you solve the problem.3.We strive to do better and make you feel satisfied!




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-summer-eva-non-slip-slippers-ladies-7-5cm-thick-sole-hole-garden-shoes-female-fashion-outdoor-beach-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_20_e142f9eb-a7e1-4c6a-9cfb-0f19ba87999e.png?v=1721161151</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9476761518344</g:id>
      <g:title>Chic Crop</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your wardrobe with this chic sleeveless cropped jacket, designed for the modern trendsetter. With its sleek lines and contemporary silhouette, this jacket is the perfect blend of sophistication and edge. Crafted from high-quality materials, it offers both style and comfort, making it an ideal layering piece for any season.
Material: Nylon - Polyester fiber
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.
Whether you pair it with a flowy dress for a fresh, feminine look or with tailored pants for a polished ensemble, this jacket effortlessly enhances any outfit. Its versatile design and striking details ensure you'll stand out in any crowd. Embrace a bold, fashion-forward style with this must-have addition to your collection!
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/chic-crop</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_42.png?v=1738582228</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533561143560</g:id>
      <g:title>Chic Switch Reversible Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this long, elegant, dual-sided down coat featuring a refined stand collar and a chic silhouette. Its reversible design offers you two stunning color combinations in one—perfect for those days when you just can't decide on the right shade to match your look. From classic outings to casual strolls, this coat seamlessly complements every occasion with its sophisticated style and versatility. Why settle for one look when you can have two in one?

Material: Nylon-Polyester

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/chic-switch-reversible-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Certificate_of_Completion_9.png?v=1731171320</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>36.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9513593045256</g:id>
      <g:title>ChicFit Piqué Cap</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into the latest fashion trend with this chic and sophisticated hat, meticulously crafted from premium piqué fabric. Its refined texture adds a unique touch of elegance, making it a must-have accessory for women with an eye for style. Designed to enhance your presence, this hat exudes a sense of prestige and confidence, perfect for those who appreciate haute couture.
Whether you're dressing up for a special occasion or adding a statement piece to your everyday look, this versatile hat effortlessly complements almost any outfit. Made for the modern woman who values both fashion and quality, it's a timeless addition to your wardrobe that seamlessly blends luxury with contemporary trends.
The cap's adjustable fit ensures it comfortably suits 99,9% of head sizes, offering both style and a perfect fit for almost everyone.


FABRIC: Cotton

COLOR: See details

SIZE: One Size (Αdjustment Cord)  
Head circumference: 22.05-23.62 inches (56-60 cm) ,
Hat depth: 4.33 inches (11 cm),
Brim width: 2.17 inches (5.5 cm).

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/chicfit-pique-cap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_5.png?v=1742498730</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386649256200</g:id>
      <g:title>Cibon</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into luxury with the all-new 2024 VdaGamas Collection. These chic and trendy flats are designed to add a touch of sophistication to any outfit. Crafted with premium PU leather, each pair promises not only style but also durability and comfort. Whether you're dressing up for a special occasion or elevating your everyday look, the VdaGamas flats are your perfect companion. Experience the blend of elegance and modern design that defines the 2024 VdaGamas Collection and transform your wardrobe with these exquisite pieces.
SPECIFICATIONS


Platform Height: 1.6 inch


Upper Material: PU


Insole Material: RUBBER



Inner material: PU


If you are not sure about  the number, beat it up one size

  

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2023-summer-womens-two-buckle-slippers-pu-leather-flats-sandals-for-women-retro-fashion-garden-mule-clog-slides-casual-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_63.png?v=1721330158</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9548378407176</g:id>
      <g:title>Classic Fit Turtleneck Sweater</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and stylish with this chic turtleneck sweater, designed for a more fitted and slightly shorter look than traditional oversized knits. Crafted from a soft, warm fabric, it features subtle side slits for ease of movement and a sophisticated silhouette. The turtleneck adds a touch of elegance, making it perfect for layering under coats or wearing on its own for a polished winter look. 
Material: 100% Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/classic-fit-turtleneck-sweater</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/35_7e1edbe6-3306-43ad-b5a5-143512ab94aa.png?v=1731246176</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370197065992</g:id>
      <g:title>Clog 21</g:title>
      <g:description>Step out in style with these Thick Bottom Sandals! The classic design and standard fit will have you feeling luxurious with every step. Perfect for any activitie, these sandals feature pearls and diamonds that you can DIY for a personalized touch. They're also versatile enough to be worn as clogs or water shoes. Upgrade your footwear game today!


Material: EVA


Heel Height: High (3,14inch)



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/thick-bottom-sandals-for-women-black-white-slippers-outdoor-fashion-pearl-luxurious-diamond-diy-garden-sandals-clogs-water-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_49.png?v=1721213271</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9373147496712</g:id>
      <g:title>Clog 323</g:title>
      <g:description>Put your best foot forward this summer with this Clogs. These baotou style slides feature a classic design and a comfortable fit, perfect for long hours on your feet. Whether you're at the beach, in the garden or at work, the soft non-slip sole will keep you feeling supported and stylish. 
SPECIFICATIONS


Upper Material: EVA


Heel Height: Med ( Up to 1,9 inch)


Insole Material: EVA













</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-summer-hole-shoes-women-baotou-outdoor-sole-beach-slides-home-outdoor-wear-comfortable-soft-sole-non-slip-garden-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sd6196e9a988040f282e1d5c165e282d1i.webp?v=1720431574</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554570641672</g:id>
      <g:title>CloudBurst Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay warm and stylish with this ultra-padded women's puffer jacket, designed for sporty yet chic looks. Featuring a generously filled design for maximum warmth, a sleek silhouette, and a functional hood to shield you from the elements, it’s the ultimate choice for winter adventures. Perfect for casual outings, outdoor activities, or layering over your favorite athleisure outfit, this jacket combines comfort and cutting-edge style effortlessly. Available in versatile colors to match any wardrobe.

Material: Polyester/Polyester Fiber
Size: Please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cloudburst-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_49.png?v=1738583145</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9594893173000</g:id>
      <g:title>ColorBlend Plaid Pullover</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover our new woolen women’s sweater featuring a timeless plaid design in stunning color combinations. This oversized, stylish casual piece is perfect for everyday wear or relaxed outings. Crafted from high-quality materials for warmth and softness, it’s a must-have for women who want to make an effortless style statement.

Material: Wool -30% - Acrylic +70%

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/colorblend-plaid-pullover</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_45_0902c442-18b2-48b2-8efb-62ab70e518c9.png?v=1738583450</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9469823320328</g:id>
      <g:title>Comunale Set. Tote Bag/Neseser</g:title>
      <g:description>Suede Classic Monochrome Bag Set
This elegant suede bag offers a timeless, monochrome design that effortlessly complements any outfit. With its spacious interior, it’s perfect for carrying all your daily essentials. The set includes a matching pouch, ideal for organizing smaller items like keys, makeup, or your phone. Whether you're heading to work or a casual outing, this classic bag set combines style with functionality for the modern individual.
SIZE: 14.7*12.2*5.1inch / 36*31*13cm
MATERIAL: POLYESTER / CASTOR
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/comunale-tote-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vdaga_24_d5d4537c-aa4b-4244-8135-0f34fcc21d7b.png?v=1726321419</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9531907342600</g:id>
      <g:title>Contrast Core Long Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover a stylish and versatile addition to your wardrobe with this long, sleeveless women's jacket. Designed with a cozy hood and a belt at the waist for a flattering silhouette, this jacket offers a unique touch with its contrasting inner lining. The inner color subtly peeks through, creating a striking look that sets this piece apart. Perfect for layering in cooler weather, this jacket combines practicality with contemporary style.

Material: Polyester - White duck down


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/contrast-core-long-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_52.png?v=1738590712</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>79.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9574453313800</g:id>
      <g:title>Cotton Cloud Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and stylish with this sporty, short-length cotton down jacket. Featuring a unique knit-like texture for a modern look, this jacket combines exceptional warmth with lightweight comfort. Its premium down filling ensures superior insulation, making it perfect for chilly days. Designed to be versatile and trendy, it’s a must-have piece for layering or wearing on its own. Ideal for everyday wear or outdoor adventures, this jacket is the perfect blend of functionality and fashion.
      Material:

Cotton 75% 
Polyester 25% 
White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cotton-cloud-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama.jpg?v=1733234794</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9589890908424</g:id>
      <g:title>Couture Crown Hat</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with our timelessly elegant women's hat, designed for those who appreciate sophistication and flair. Crafted with impeccable attention to detail, this chic accessory features a structured yet soft silhouette that complements any outfit. Whether paired with a tailored coat for a refined look or worn with casual outerwear for effortless glamour, this hat is the perfect blend of classic design and modern appeal. A must-have for women who value style and versatility in every season.

Material: Polyester
Size: One Size - Adjustable

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/couture-crown-hat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_41_39bb0623-2e7c-4169-ac25-35c3023f218d.png?v=1734464589</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>11.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533389537544</g:id>
      <g:title>Couture Grandeur Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>This women’s long down coat exudes timeless elegance and sophistication. Crafted to perfection, it features an exceptionally high collar that not only enhances its sleek silhouette but also offers superior warmth and protection against the cold. Filled with premium down, this coat is both lightweight and incredibly insulating, making it ideal for chilly weather. Its streamlined design and graceful length make it a standout piece that seamlessly combines luxury with modern style. Designed for those who appreciate uniqueness in every detail, this coat is an embodiment of refined taste and class.
Material: Acetate - White duck down
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/couture-grandeur-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_56.png?v=1738591861</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585150624008</g:id>
      <g:title>Cozy Luxe Turtleneck</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in effortless elegance with our oversized knit turtleneck sweater. Designed with a relaxed silhouette and long, cozy sleeves, this timeless piece is both stylish and versatile. The soft turtleneck adds warmth and sophistication, making it perfect for layering or wearing on its own during cooler days.
Material: Acrylic
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cozy-luxe-turtleneck</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winter_edi_21.png?v=1733918077</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9548374507784</g:id>
      <g:title>Cozy Side-Slit Turtleneck Sweater</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in cozy elegance with this long, relaxed-fit turtleneck sweater. Designed for style and comfort, it features side slits for effortless movement and a touch of sophistication. This sweater’s soft knit fabric and chic turtleneck make it perfect for layering or wearing on its own for a laid-back yet polished look. Ideal for pairing with jeans, leggings, or even skirts, it’s a versatile addition to any fall and winter wardrobe.
Material: 100% Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cozy-side-slit-turtleneck-sweater</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/28_43223dea-6b9f-4ae0-8c9a-e0355eef2090.png?v=1731244672</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9384339341576</g:id>
      <g:title>Crestar Platform</g:title>
      <g:description>Step up your comfort game with Crestar Platform Soft Eva Slippers! These slippers feature a super soft and cozy design that will make you feel like you're walking on a cloud. The platform adds a stylish touch while providing extra support. Perfect for wearing at home or on the beach, these slippers are non-slip and unisex, making them a must-have for any wardrobe.


Material: Eva





</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/crestar-platform-soft-eva-slippers-for-women-men-fashion-comfortable-unisex-home-sandals-bathroom-non-slip-slides-beach-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-16T222423.029.png?v=1721210148</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9371691974920</g:id>
      <g:title>Cuba Clogs</g:title>
      <g:description>Stepping forward in life is the only way to survive.. 
Versatile sandals feature an anti-bacterial material, perfect for all-day wear. Add your own unique touch with DIY decorations, and enjoy the thick bottom for added support. 


Exclusively at VdaGama.com

SPECIFICATIONS
With Platforms: Yes
Sandal Type: clogs
Occasion: Casual
Upper Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA
Fit: Fits smaller than usual. Please check this store's sizing info
Style: LEISURE
Lining Material: none
Insole Material: EVA



















</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-2024-summer-new-style-women-outer-sandals-ladies-casual-slippers-diy-decoration-thick-bottom-work-and-party-garden-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_20.png?v=1721159824</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9605322440968</g:id>
      <g:title>Cuff Signature</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience effortless style with this refined women's dress, designed to blend simplicity with sophistication. Ιts classic, streamlined silhouette ensures a timeless appeal. The highlight of this dress is the four signature buttons on the cuffs—an understated yet striking detail that adds a unique touch of character.

Material: Alasi

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cuff-signature</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_59.png?v=1738592683</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9510666862856</g:id>
      <g:title>Echelon Asymmetrical Longline Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your wardrobe with our luxurious sleeveless puffer vest, a perfect blend of sophistication and functionality. Crafted to complement any outfit with ease, this vest boasts a high collar and an elegantly tailored longline silhouette, exuding timeless style. A striking asymmetrical design subtly conceals the zipper beneath an overlapping panel, ensuring a sleek, uninterrupted look while providing enhanced wind protection for your chest.
Meticulously crafted from premium materials, this vest offers not only exceptional warmth but also an indulgent sense of comfort. Its versatile design makes it ideal for layering, effortlessly transitioning between casual and refined ensembles. Whether worn on a crisp morning stroll or as an elevated addition to your chic winter wardrobe, this piece epitomizes understated elegance and superior craftsmanship. A true statement of sophistication, this puffer vest is an essential for those with a discerning eye for style and quality.

Material: Polyester

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/echelon-longline-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_57_a7907ac1-1f92-4cf1-a7f8-0253b16a7e72.png?v=1738594005</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>43.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450773610760</g:id>
      <g:title>Eclipse Grandeur Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience unparalleled sophistication with our exquisitely chic hand-shoulder bag. Designed for the modern woman with a taste for timeless elegance, this bag features a stunning wooden handle that adds a unique and luxurious touch. Its sleek design and high-quality craftsmanship make it the epitome of refined style, ensuring you’ll make a statement of elegance wherever you go.

Size: 9.84*0.89*7inch / 25cmx2x18cm

Main Material: PU LEATHER              

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cloud-bag-bag-for-women-fashion-pleated-small-bag-wooden-handle-simple-tote-bags-for-ladies</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/23.webp?v=1726396930</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585474502920</g:id>
      <g:title>EdgeFlow Knit</g:title>
      <g:description>Unleash your style with a modern twist. This loose, long turtleneck sweater redefines comfort and elegance. Featuring unique, artistic cutouts, it adds a bold and contemporary edge to a classic design. Its relaxed fit offers effortless movement, while the high neckline brings a touch of sophistication. Perfect for layering or wearing as a statement piece, this sweater is a go-to for women seeking versatile and chic wardrobe staples.

Material: Acrylic

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/edgeflow-knit</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/60_52ce764a-bb63-41c1-a907-7b1e5b7548e9.png?v=1733938236</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9582397980936</g:id>
      <g:title>Elevé Quilted Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in ultimate warmth and effortless style with this luxurious women's down jacket. Featuring a loose-fit design for a relaxed, sporty look, this ultra-thick and cozy piece is perfect for chilly days. Its refined high collar and unique piqué-textured fabric set it apart, showcasing a high-fashion aesthetic that's both sophisticated and practical. A true statement of elevated craftsmanship, this jacket is a premium investment in comfort and elegance.
      Material:

Polyester
White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/eleve-quilted-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winteredi.png?v=1733762426</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587393855752</g:id>
      <g:title>Eloise Wool Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the perfect blend of elegance and comfort with this timeless wool dress. Featuring a classic turtleneck design and a relaxed fit that softly flows from the waist down, this piece offers a flattering silhouette for any occasion. Its cozy fabric keeps you warm during chilly days, while the luxurious texture feels incredibly soft against your skin. A must-have for effortless sophistication and everyday wearability.
Material: 100% Merino Wool
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/eloise-wool-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_69.png?v=1734215424</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450796777736</g:id>
      <g:title>Elta XL Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Get ready to take on the day with our new Shoulder Bag! Designed with premium Corduroy cotton, these bags offer a large, spacious capacity for all your daily essentials. Perfect for a day out or a trip to the store, the handy zipper ensures your belongings stay secure. Upgrade your fashion game with this stylish and practical bag now!`

SIZE: 18.90*15.35*6.3inch / Size: 37x16x46cm


Meterial: Cotton-Corduroy  /  Closure Type: zipper







</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/corduroy-shoulder-bags-new-women-fashion-leisure-college-style-shopper-multi-pocket-large-capacity-designer-handbags-totes-bags</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/33.webp?v=1726493354</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>27.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9532855681288</g:id>
      <g:title>Eterna Asymmetric Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace the changing season with sophistication in a jacket designed to make a statement. This elegant winter coat features a refined asymmetrical silhouette, complemented by a high Adjustable collar that unfolds to cover the entire head and distinctive fastenings that enhance its unique character. Crafted from premium, thick down for exceptional warmth, and fully waterproof for maximum protection, it’s designed to keep you both comfortable and impeccably stylish, no matter the weather. Step out in a look that redefines winter elegance.

Materials: Cotton - Polyester - White duck down
Size: One Size fits all




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/eterna-asymmetric-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Certificate_of_Completion_2_d3cadf96-72b0-4a3e-9c8f-ea8f3f5f17de.png?v=1731155722</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445288214792</g:id>
      <g:title>Eternal Allure</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the epitome of elegance with our Unick luxury leather tote bag, exquisitely crafted with a distinctive clemence pattern and intricate weave. Designed for the refined woman, this timeless piece boasts a spacious interior, offering both style and practicality. Whether for everyday use or special occasions, this exclusive tote enhances your wardrobe with unparalleled sophistication.

Material: Cowhide Leather


Size: 30*10*29cm 11.81*3.93*11.41inch


            


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fashion-women-new-luxury-leather-tote-bag-lady-designer-clemence-pattern-weaveing-one-shoulder-large-capacity-niche-tote-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S9c9a998d49f544638b33bb1b7aa59daa9.webp?v=1724763191</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9374907826440</g:id>
      <g:title>EVA</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into a world of ultimate comfort. These soft-soled sandals will transport you to a blissful state of relaxation, while the non-slip bottoms provide secure footing. Bring fashion and function together.
Top-rated shoes in this summer
Material: EVA
Fashion Element: light
Fit: Fits smaller than usual. Please check this store's sizing info
Insole Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA
Lining Material: none



Vinyl vinyl acetate sole
Stylish soft sole design:
EVA sole material, let your feet feel the feeling of stepping on the clouds, open toes to keep your feet breathable, will not sweat.
Lightweight and durable: 
Our cute and stylish slippers are highly crafted, comfortable for everyday use, and they are quiet on the floor because they are very lightweight.
Thick non-slip sole:
The thick padded sole makes them walk very steadily, and the EVA outsole with wavy texture gives you anti-slip protection and your every step is stable.
Multi-purpose:
suitable for indoor and outdoor use, especially on the beach, these shoes will give you very good feedback.







</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/comwarm-2024-summer-slippers-men-soft-bottom-indoor-home-platform-sandals-fashion-beach-shoes-couple-non-slip-bathroom-slides</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/OPTIMUS_3.png?v=1721159398</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>12.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9546734928136</g:id>
      <g:title>Evoke Loose-Fit Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay warm and stylish with this extraordinary women's long down jacket. Designed with a loose fit and striking asymmetrical cuts, it combines modern fashion with functionality, covering most of the body for ultimate warmth and comfort. The unique silhouette features a relaxed, flowing shape with a snug, knitted finish on the cuffs, adding a sophisticated touch. Crafted with premium down insulation, this coat is exceptionally warm, perfect for even the coldest winter days. Ideal for those who embrace distinctive style without compromising on coverage and coziness, this long jacket is a true winter essential.

Materials: Polyester-White Duck Down

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/evoke-loose-fit-down-coat-1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_5.png?v=1731156823</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370192183560</g:id>
      <g:title>Fabel</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing Fabel, the newest trendsetter of 2024. With its sleek and unique design, you'll be sure to turn heads wherever you go. Whether it's a day out with friends or a night walk, Fabel will have you feeling one-of-a-kind. Crafted with EVA material, these sandals offer an unparalleled walking experience, combining very soft comfort with advanced support. The antislip sole ensures secure footing on any surface, while the skin-friendly interior provides gentle, all-day wear. Elevate your style and enjoy exceptional comfort.
SPECIFICATIONS
Decoration: Big Smile Face,embroidery
Upper Material: EVA
Shoes Type: Modern Slippers
Insole Material: EVA
Item Type: slippers
Outsole Material: EVA
Lining Material: none


modname=ckedito

size :
(US 5-6) EU 35-36-------The sole length is 23cm, suitable for foot length 8,1- 8,6inch 21-22cm
(US 6.5-7.5) 37-38-------The sole length is 24cm, suitable for foot length 8,4-9 / 22-23cm
(US 8.5-9) 39-40-------The sole length is 25cm, suitable for foot length 9-9,5inch / 23-24cm
**Please choose the appropriate size according to your foot length, manual measurement.

**If your feet are WDE or thick, please choose one size larger, if you are not sure about the size, please contact us before 



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summer-womens-hole-shoes-thick-soled-perforated-shoes-eva-comfortable-garden-shoes-bao-toe-sandalswomens-baotou-hole-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_2025_2.png?v=1731082565</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9476824105224</g:id>
      <g:title>Fall Classic Knit</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this stunning, long sleeveless coat that perfectly blends elegance and comfort. Crafted with exquisite attention to detail, this knit piece wraps around your body and ties at the waist for a more feminine and sophisticated silhouette. A truly chic and timeless addition to your wardrobe, it effortlessly complements almost any outfit, making it a versatile choice for any occasion.
Material: Acrylic fiber
⚠ WARNING: This product can expose you to BPA
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.
Please note that the measurements provided in the size chart reflect the dimensions of the garment itself, not the body. When selecting your size, it is essential to measure yourself and leave enough room for comfort (+0.79-1.6inch 2-4cm).
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fall-classic-knit</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-09-20_152625.png?v=1726852252</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>16.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554853658888</g:id>
      <g:title>Fierce Ember Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Make a bold statement with this ultra-warm, long women's coat designed for the confident and fearless. With its striking design and edgy details, this coat combines comfort and style in the most daring way. The standout feature? A sleek leather belt at the waist that perfectly defines your silhouette, adding a touch of attitude to its fierce personality. Made to keep you warm during the coldest days, this coat is not just a fashion piece—it's a statement of power and confidence.

Material: Cowhide Leather-White duck down
Size: Carefully consult the size chart


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fierce-ember-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_-_2025-01-14T201633.011.png?v=1736878648</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>295.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445277925640</g:id>
      <g:title>Firenze</g:title>
      <g:description>“Extraordinary.” That’s the first word that comes to mind for anyone who sees this piece of art for the first time. Presenting the latest addition to our online store —a bag that transcends conventional design and sets a new standard in luxury and innovation, available exclusively through our online store. This exquisite piece is not just a bag; it is a statement of unparalleled craftsmanship, featuring a groundbreaking design that harmoniously blends form and function. The texture is incredibly refined, inviting to the touch, while the materials chosen are of the highest quality, ensuring durability and lasting beauty for years to come.

Dimensions: 14,2inch*10,24inch*4,33inch / 36*26*11cm
Material: Nylon/polyester/metal

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/36x26x11cm-seatbelt-new-style-women-bags-shoulder-tote-bags-women-messenger-bags-with-famous-seat-belt-designers-nylon-handbags</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_2025_3.png?v=1731082825</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9593451184392</g:id>
      <g:title>Flare &amp; Grace</g:title>
      <g:description>"Embrace your femininity with effortless style." This ultra-chic dress is tailored to flatter every curve while offering unparalleled comfort. Designed with a slimming silhouette in mind, it cinches perfectly below the bust, drawing attention to the smallest part of your waist, and gracefully flares out from the midsection for a forgiving, flowy finish. The sleeves echo the same design with a subtle flare at the cuffs, adding a touch of elegance and sophistication. Perfect for any occasion, this dress celebrates femininity while providing a slimming effect that enhances your confidence.
Materila: 97% Polyester 3% Spandex
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/flare-grace</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_37_6394b731-efba-4cbc-a1ac-628f1cbfebb5.png?v=1734904396</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450777182472</g:id>
      <g:title>Floncia</g:title>
      <g:description>This shoulder bag is as versatile as it is stylish. Made from premium genue leather, it's perfect for any occasion - whether it's a casual day out or a special event. The simple, yet elegant design makes it a must-have for any fashion-forward woman. Plus, the removable inner purse adds even more convenience and functionality!
Main Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Genuine Leather Type: Cow Leather
Lining Material: POLYESTER
Shape: Bucket
Colors:: brown, caramel, grey, dark grey
Size: 24*13*23 cm / 9.44*9.1*5.1inch


Colors:
brown, caramel, grey, dark grey











Recommendation:




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fashion-female-genuine-leather-shoulder-bags-women-handbag-solid-color-lady-bucket-messenger-bag-with-removable-inner-purse-new</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S8a811e0965b04bc18fa76b9d58ba8d93A.webp?v=1725203775</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450771644680</g:id>
      <g:title>Flora Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing Flora, all time clasic shoulder bag. Its simple yet elegant design exudes timeless sophistication. With a large capacity, it's perfect for your everyday essentials. Carry it as a shoulder bag or crossbody for a versatile and stylish look. Upgrade your wardrobe with this fashion-forward statement piece.

SIZE: 14.17*9.84*7.1inch / 36*25*18cm 
MATERIAL: PU LEATHER

















</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/vintage-pillow-design-pu-leather-boston-handbag-for-women-casual-large-capacity-shoulder-crossbody-bags-fashion-shopper-totes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vdaga-_1.webp?v=1726318212</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9584809607432</g:id>
      <g:title>Flora Wrap Cape</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this elegant knit wrap shawl, designed for both comfort and versatility. Featuring convenient loops at the waist for a secure tie, it offers a flattering fit that enhances your silhouette. Perfect for layering, this shawl can be worn effortlessly over any outfit or jacket, making it a must-have for all seasons. Whether you’re dressing up or staying cozy, this piece adds a touch of sophistication to your look.

Material: Acrilyc


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/flora-wrap-cape</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vdagama_18_0483cd04-3826-4a48-82ac-553674fb5ae6.png?v=1733858232</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9589879865608</g:id>
      <g:title>FlowForm Wool Sweater</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the ultimate combination of style and comfort with our signature oversized asymmetrical women's sweater. Made from 100% exceptionally soft premium wool, this standout piece is a cornerstone of our collection. Designed with a relaxed fit, it features draped shoulders and tapered cuffs that create a subtle contrast, elevating the look with an effortlessly chic vibe. Perfect for layering or wearing on its own, this sweater is as unique as it is cozy, offering unparalleled versatility for your wardrobe.

Material: 100% Wool
Size: One Size-Fits All



 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/flowform-wool-sweater</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_57_3bbc8fc5-2c2f-43e5-baf6-1f5c3bde7342.png?v=1734546113</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9471366955272</g:id>
      <g:title>Fmc-47 Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>
This exceptional bag combines elegance, style, and versatility, making it perfect for every outfit and occasion. Its well-thought-out dimensions provide ample space, while maintaining a sleek and sophisticated look. Designed for practicality and ease of use, it features:

Two large, independent exterior pockets
Multiple interior compartments for organized storage
A detachable strap for crossbody wear
Made from highly durable, scratch-resistant synthetic fabric
100% waterproof for all-weather protection

This bag is the perfect choice for those seeking a stylish, functional, and long-lasting accessory.




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fmc-47-black</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/completion-_15__1.webp?v=1726599546</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587768754440</g:id>
      <g:title>Frost Hug Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>A statement of modern sophistication. Wrap yourself in style and unparalleled warmth with this exceptional sleeveless down dress. Designed to flatter with a waist-cinching tie, this unique piece combines elegance and comfort, keeping you cozy during even the coldest days. Its versatile design makes it easy to layer over almost any outfit—whether you're wearing a sleek turtleneck, a light sweater, or evening wear. This standout piece offers a chic solution for winter dressing, effortlessly blending fashion and functionality. Perfect for those who want to make a bold, sophisticated statement while staying exceptionally warm.

Material:
Polyester  
White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/frost-hug-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_84ca9466-111b-436e-9394-b47439df8749.png?v=1734277650</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>129.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9586066555144</g:id>
      <g:title>Frost Luxe Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your winter wardrobe with this short down puffer jacket, designed to provide unparalleled warmth and style. Featuring a luxuriously oversized fox fur hood, it offers exceptional protection against the cold while adding a bold, sophisticated touch. The high collar, when the hood is down, creates a sleek shield against icy winds, ensuring maximum comfort and coziness.
With its cinched waist design, this jacket flatters your silhouette, offering both functionality and elegance. Perfect for brisk city walks or casual outings, this piece combines practicality with a chic, contemporary look. The premium down filling guarantees lightweight insulation, while the statement hood adds a glamorous edge.
       Material:

Fabric: 100% Polyester
Fill in: +95% White duck down
Hood: Fox Fur

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/frost-luxe-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_50.png?v=1734012940</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585997873416</g:id>
      <g:title>FrostGuard Fox Fur Parka</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay warm and stylish this winter with our luxurious long down jacket, designed for ultimate comfort and elegance. This coat features an oversized, thick, and cozy hood made from premium fox fur, offering unparalleled warmth and a touch of sophistication. The adjustable waist tie enhances your silhouette, adding a feminine touch while ensuring a perfect fit. Crafted with high-quality down insulation, this jacket is your go-to choice for staying cozy without compromising on style.

Material: 
Fabric: Polyester 100%
Fill in: White duck down +95%
Fox Fur

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/frostguard-fox-fur-parka</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_47_43b1c237-0902-4c26-94af-6e503e8c0a5e.png?v=1734003255</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>195.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445286183176</g:id>
      <g:title>Genuine Leather Weave Women Shoulder Bags Solid Vintage Underarm Bag Small Ladies Handbag Luxury Real Cow Leather Crossbody Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: UnishowShape: SatchelsHandbags Type: Shoulder BagsTypes of bags: Shoulder &amp; Crossbody BagsOrigin: Mainland ChinaMain Material: GENUINE LEATHERGenuine Leather Type: Cow LeatherClosure Type: zipperHardness: SOFTExterior: noneStyle: vintageModel Number: UHB12341Lining Material: POLYESTEROccasion: VersatileGender: WOMENPattern Type: KnittingNumber of Handles/Straps: twoInterior: Cell Phone PocketInterior: Interior Zipper PocketDecoration: noneItem Type: Handbags
 [xlmodel]-[custom]-[8888] 
 
  100% Genuine leather women bag small retro underarm shoulder bag fashion knitting female crossbody bag real cowhide leather lady handbag
  Size:25*7*14 cm
  Material: Genuine leather
  Structure: 1 main compartment ,1 inner zipper pocket ,1 slot pocket
  Luxury import genuine leather ,handmade knitting ,retro simple design
  2 straps ,1 leather strap ,1 fabric strap .can wear as shoulder bag or crossbody bag 
  
  
  
  
 


 [xlmodel]-[photo]-[0000] 
 
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
  
 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/genuine-leather-weave-women-shoulder-bags-solid-vintage-underarm-bag-small-ladies-handbag-luxury-real-cow-leather-crossbody-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Ha5ff6071f2de483cbc9c9ad0c469bd3cc.webp?v=1724763099</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>51.66 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9548344787208</g:id>
      <g:title>Gift Card</g:title>
      <g:description>Looking for a thoughtful yet flexible gift? Our gift cards are the perfect solution for friends, family, and loved ones who enjoy stylish fashion with a personal touch. Available in various amounts, our gift cards let recipients choose exactly what they want from our collection of chic bags, elegant outerwear, and versatile accessories. Upon purchase, each gift card delivers a unique code, either sent directly via email or displayed instantly, making it quick and easy to redeem. Show someone you care with a gift that lets them style it their way!</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/gift-card</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/20_00_8.png?v=1731239773</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>10.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9511801061640</g:id>
      <g:title>Glam Waist Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>We dare you to find a more chic jacket on the market. Our sleeveless long puffer vest is the epitome of modern elegance. Featuring a seamlessly integrated waist belt, it cinches to perfection for a tailored, flattering fit. The belt's refined metallic detail adds a touch of luxury, elevating the design to a whole new level. With its sleek silhouette and sophisticated craftsmanship, this vest is a standout addition to any stylish winter wardrobe.
Material: Polyester-Cotton
🔍Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart. 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/glam-waist-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_48.png?v=1731170079</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9580246597896</g:id>
      <g:title>GlamMatte Winter Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Designed for discerning women who appreciate refined style, this premium down jacket redefines winter fashion. Its sophisticated waist-tie design complements the feminine silhouette, while the matte crêpe-like textured fabric adds an understated yet distinctive charm. Perfect for those who value luxury and individuality, this jacket embodies the essence of modern sophistication and embraces the latest trends with subtlety and grace. 

Material:
Cotton 75% -
Nylon 25% -
White duck down (fill in) 90+%

 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/glammatte-winter-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_-_2025-01-09T224323.258.png?v=1736455632</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585127260424</g:id>
      <g:title>Golden Embrace Cardigan</g:title>
      <g:description>Indulge in the ultimate sophistication with our premium 100% cashmere cardigan—a true masterpiece of luxury and timeless elegance. Known as "Soft Gold" and revered as the "King of Fibers," cashmere offers unmatched softness, warmth, and durability, making this cardigan an investment in comfort and style. 
Its exquisite texture is as soft as silk, while its natural warmth wraps you in cozy comfort on chilly days.
Designed for the discerning woman who values quality and sophistication, this cardigan is more than just a wardrobe staple—it’s a statement of understated luxury that will last for years to come.

Marerial: 100% Cashmere 

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/golden-embrace-cardigan</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_59.png?v=1734207379</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>510.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450777084168</g:id>
      <g:title>Handbags Women Messenger Bags Famous Designer Women Genuine Leather Handbags Luxury Ladies Hand Bags Shoulder Sac Composite Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: POOLOOSHandbags Type: TotesTypes of bags: Handbags &amp; Crossbody bagsMain Material: GENUINE LEATHERGenuine Leather Type: Cow LeatherLining Material: POLYESTERShape: BucketPlace Of Origin: GUANG DONG ProvincePlace Of Origin: SHAN DONG ProvinceOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongHardness: SOFTPattern Type: PatchworkInterior: Interior CompartmentInterior: Cell Phone PocketInterior: Interior Zipper PocketInterior: Interior Slot PocketDecoration: noneExterior: noneOccasion: VersatileClosure Type: zipperGender: WOMENStyle: fashionModel Number: QSL-0889Number of Handles/Straps: SingleHandbags Women Messenger Bags Famous Designer Women Genuine Leather Handbags Luxury Ladies Hand Bags Shoulder Sac Composite BagMaterial: High quality cowhide genuine leatherOpen Method: zipperNote 1: Due to the difference between different monitors, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item.Note 2: With the difference in the measurement method, please allow 1-3cm in size deviation.Note 3: 1 inch=2.54cm, 1cm=0.39inch</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/handbags-women-messenger-bags-famous-designer-women-genuine-leather-handbags-luxury-ladies-hand-bags-shoulder-sac-composite-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/HTB1tEVRIhWYBuNjy1zkq6xGGpXaV.webp?v=1725203727</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>76.69 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9644552257800</g:id>
      <g:title>Hikari Textured Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace Effortless Elegance with a Japanese-Inspired Jacket
Discover a fusion of timeless minimalism and contemporary style with our Japanese-inspired lightweight jacket. Designed for modern women who appreciate effortless sophistication, this short-length piece features delicately rolled-up sleeves and exquisite stitched details that add a touch of artistry to the fabric.
✔️ Lightweight and breathable – perfect for transitional weather✔️ Elegant stitched patterns for a refined, handcrafted look✔️ Rolled-up sleeves for a chic, relaxed touch✔️ Polyster 50% - Polyester fiber 50%
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/hikari-textured-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_10e0929b-de82-45f8-9870-cd6133a0ad5f.png?v=1738260983</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370192904456</g:id>
      <g:title>Hugh Hefner</g:title>
      <g:description>Revolution in Clogs. 
Ιntroducing our 2024 collection of clogs, designed to redefine comfort and style. Made with high-quality, soft EVA material, they promise a cozy fit. The non-slip sole guarantees stability and security. Unique and modern designs, for anyone looking to stay ahead in fashion.

Material: Eva


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mens-slippers-soft-and-comfortable-non-slip-wear-resistant-indoor-and-outdoor-ventilate-thick-bottom-shoes-for-men-unisex-new</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Winter_Collection_29.png?v=1730377700</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9550490861832</g:id>
      <g:title>Iconic Layer Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this one-of-a-kind women’s hooded sleeveless jacket, designed for those who dare to stand out! Featuring unique cuts that add a touch of bold sophistication, this jacket combines functionality with high-fashion appeal. Perfect for layering over your favorite sweaters or tops, it’s crafted to keep you warm while showcasing your sense of style.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/iconic-layer-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/82_253fa024-5d34-4494-a68c-f84ebe125cbd.png?v=1731439081</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>53.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9593571049736</g:id>
      <g:title>Infinity Flare Trousers</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with our high-waisted bell-bottom pants, designed to make a bold statement. Featuring a slim, figure-hugging fit at the waist and hips, these pants gradually flare out into wide, dramatic legs, creating an elegant silhouette that flows like a maxi skirt from afar. Perfect for those who love to blend modern sophistication with a touch of retro flair, these unique trousers are crafted for women who embrace individuality and timeless fashion.
You can choose the length that suits you best: ankle-length, regular, or extra-long. For photography purposes, the model is wearing the extra-long version.

Material: Polyester

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/infinity-flare-trousers</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_35.png?v=1734899501</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450796515592</g:id>
      <g:title>Izabela</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with our Tote Bag Ladies 2024 New Autumn/winter! This high-grade, niche design offers a spacious interior, perfect for your everyday needs. Embrace the new season with its stylish look. Make a statement and stand out from the crowd. Get yours now!

SIZE: 14.9*11*9inch / 38*28*23cm
Material: PU Leather








</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/tote-bag-ladies-2024-new-autumn-winter-high-grade-niche-design-large-capacity-retro-commuter-handbag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/11inch_28cm_7.png?v=1730034359</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375134843144</g:id>
      <g:title>Jarden</g:title>
      <g:description>Get ready to impress with our new arrival, unique design, perfect for any outdoor activitie. The thick sole provides anti-slip protection, while the soft sole ensures comfort. Available in solid colors, These shoes are a must-have for all women who want to make a statement in fashion, not just follow it!
VdaGama 2024 Collection.

SPECIFICATIONS
Brand Name: VdaGama
Heel Height: Low +1.2inch
With Platforms: Yes
Sandal Type: clogs
Upper Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA
Closure Type: hook &amp; loop
Fashion Element: Platform
Insole Material: EVA
women's shoes Summer 2024
casual shoes: shoes women


Choose the size according to your foot length.

Please note that the fit of this particular model is somewhat narrow. Therefore, if you are uncertain between two sizes, such as 7 or 7.5, it is preferable to choose the next size up.





US Size 5 = Foot Length 22.1-22.5cm (8.7-8.9 inches)US Size 5.5 = Foot Length 22.6-23.0cm (8.9-9.1 inches)US Size 6 = Foot Length 23.1-23.5cm (9.1-9.3 inches)US Size 6.5 = Foot Length 23.6-24.0cm (9.3-9.4 inches)US Size 7 = Foot Length 24.1-24.5cm (9.5-9.6 inches)US Size 7.5 = Foot Length 24.6-25.0cm (9.7-9.8 inches)







</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-summer-new-two-wear-beach-hole-shoes-thick-sole-anti-slip-cool-slippers-outdoor-soft-sole-solid-color-womens-slippers</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Winter_Collection_30.png?v=1730378407</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>37.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445275599112</g:id>
      <g:title>JCM</g:title>
      <g:description>Indulge in the sophistication of JCM, with its luxurious chocolate-colored exterior and spacious interior. Designed to provide ample space for all your belongings, this piece will elevate your style and add an air of exclusivity to your wardrobe. Experience the art of fashion with JCM.   </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/jnmc-womens-coffee-color-hand-woven-design-fashion-daily-travel-handbag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/13_55479572-87ab-42c6-91ae-175a2c8e70e9.png?v=1724787379</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445275894024</g:id>
      <g:title>Jenna Rouze</g:title>
      <g:description>Unleash your inner fashionista with our JNMC Women's Plain Pure Hand-woven Shoulder Handbag 2024. Each bag is carefully handcrafted with a unique and playful design, making it the perfect addition to your everyday going out ensemble. With its spacious and stylish design, this bag is sure to bring a touch of joy to your wardrobe.   
Dimension: 11.41inch *  4.33inch * 7.27inch





</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/jnmc-womens-plain-pure-hand-woven-shoulder-handbag-2024-the-latest-bohemia-suitable-for-everyday-going-out</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/15_bce9de09-35f1-49b4-b751-70d46add9e16.png?v=1724788708</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>79.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370151977224</g:id>
      <g:title>Joy Clog</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into summer with these joyfully designed, anti-slip EVA slippers. The perfect choice for your outdoor adventures, these fashion-forward slippers feature a thick bottom for added comfort and a trendy Baotou style. Get ready to make a statement!
Material: Eva
Size: Choose one size up

SPECIFICATIONS
Outsole Material: EvStyle: LEISURE
Fit: Fits smaller than usual. Please check this store's sizing info
Heel Type: Flat with
Upper Material: EVA
Insole Material: EVA
Outsole Material: EVA
Lining Material: none
With Platforms: Yes


mod
size：









</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summer-women-slippers-fashion-thick-bottom-hole-shoes-eva-slippers-anti-slip-baotou-slippers-outdoor-beach-sandals-slippers</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sf878ab3b2dce43f5938dfa93088c92ddk.webp?v=1720196109</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450777608456</g:id>
      <g:title>Joy Tote |Set</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing Joy—the ultimate fusion of style and functionality. Crafted for the modern woman, this elegant set includes not one, but two beautifully designed bags. The main bag features a sleek, minimalist design with ample capacity to hold all your essentials, ensuring you stay organized and chic on the go. Additionally, a matching smaller bag is included, perfect for your cosmetics or smaller items. Effortlessly stylish and comfortable to carry, Joy is the must-have accessory that elevates your look with timeless sophistication.

 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/leftside-fashion-leather-tote-bag-for-women-2023-tend-female-simple-large-high-capacity-shoulder-side-bag-handbags-and-purses</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Au_26.png?v=1726769715</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386218160392</g:id>
      <g:title>Julia</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this Brand Buckle Strap Sandals. Featuring a chic buckle strap design, these Romanesque-inspired sandals add a touch of sophistication to any summer ensemble. The thick bottom provides comfort and support, making them the perfect choice for daily wear. Step into luxury with these elegant and exclusive sandals.

SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: artificial leather
Insole Material: RUBBER
Sandal Type: GLADIATOR
Outsole Material: PU
Lining Material: PU
Closure Type: SLIP-ON
Heel Height: Med (2 inch)





 

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/womens-shoes-2024-brand-buckle-strap-womens-sandals-romanesque-summer-daily-sandals-women-thick-bottom-shoes-ladies-zapatos-1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_2025_4.png?v=1731084690</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>37.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9503103975688</g:id>
      <g:title>Knitted Wonder Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our 2024 Knitted Women's Tote Bag – where style meets functionality. This large, chic tote boasts a fresh, contemporary design perfect for the modern woman. Handcrafted with intricate knitting patterns, it blends timeless elegance with a trendy flair. Spacious enough to carry all your essentials, yet stylish enough to complement any outfit, this tote is ideal for everyday use or a casual day out. Its durable yet soft texture ensures long-lasting quality, making it a must-have accessory for 2024. Elevate your wardrobe with this versatile and fashionable piece!

Material: Polyester fabric
Dimension: 14.94*14.56*2.36inch

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/knitted-wonder-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_2.png?v=1731084740</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>24.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9600087064840</g:id>
      <g:title>Korean Chic Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>This oversized, relaxed-fit down jacket is the epitome of effortless style and comfort. Featuring a chic open Korean-style collar and button closure, it exudes a casual yet modern aesthetic. The turned-up cuffs add a subtle touch of sophistication, making it perfect for laid-back outings or everyday wear. Made with lightweight yet warm materials, this jacket is easy to wear and ideal for layering over your favorite outfits. Embrace cozy, relaxed vibes while staying stylish all season long.

Material: Polyster - White duck down +90%


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/korean-chic-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_67_6ed91433-b8a0-414b-bf9a-db9bb3ebc235.png?v=1738600316</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554729369864</g:id>
      <g:title>Korean-Flow Maxi Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Make a bold fashion statement this season with this ultra-long, oversized coat, inspired by the chic and minimalist aesthetics of Korean street style. Designed for comfort and elegance, this coat features a modern, flowing silhouette that exudes effortless sophistication. Perfect for layering, it pairs beautifully with both casual and formal outfits. Its standout design is tailored to catch the eye, making it the ultimate statement piece for trendsetters. Whether strolling through the city or attending a winter gathering, this coat ensures warmth, style, and a touch of contemporary luxury.

Material: Polyester-Cotton-White duck down
Size: One Size fits all

 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/k-flow-maxi-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Premium_8.png?v=1731779052</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>179.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375034573064</g:id>
      <g:title>Krav Maga</g:title>
      <g:description>Booomm! That's the sound that makes this Clog, when arrived in the market! The latest in footwear fashion. With a unique design and exclusive style, these Clogs are just perfect!

Maretial: Eva
1.6inch thick sole









If your foot is a bit wide or you are on the borderline, choose the next size up.








</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/thick-soled-raised-hole-shoes-2024-summer-new-comfortable-internet-celebrity-anti-slip-couple-eva-sandals-for-external-wear</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_28.png?v=1721159304</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9644791103752</g:id>
      <g:title>Kyoto Breeze Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace effortless elegance with this Japanese-style quilted jacket, designed for light warmth and everyday versatility. With delicate stitched details and a relaxed, short-length fit, it blends traditional aesthetics with modern comfort. Perfect for layering in mild weather, this jacket adds a refined, minimalist touch to any outfit.
Material: Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/kyoto-breeze-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_9_bf3a0110-0505-496b-b6bd-69b1fbd249d9.png?v=1738270369</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9578555900168</g:id>
      <g:title>Kyoto Charm Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Timeless Elegance: Japanese-Inspired Long Coat"
Step into sophistication with this stunning long coat, crafted for women who embrace elegance with a touch of uniqueness. Designed with oversized Japanese-style buttons as the centerpiece, this coat exudes minimalistic charm and cultural flair. Its structured silhouette and premium wool-blend fabric ensure warmth and comfort without compromising on style. Perfect for elevating everyday outfits or making a statement during special occasions.
Features:

Oversized Japanese-style buttons for a bold aesthetic
Material: Nylon (Matt) - White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/kyoto-charm-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_69_8471e555-2629-4a9e-b579-ede691423527.png?v=1738604458</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>139.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533422338312</g:id>
      <g:title>Landmark Down Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>This women’s down jacket is a masterpiece of refined elegance and functional design, setting a new standard in outerwear. Its streamlined silhouette, coupled with a high, enveloping collar, creates a look that is both timeless and modern. Filled with the finest down, this jacket delivers unmatched warmth without compromising on style. Every detail is crafted to perfection, from the precision stitching to the flattering cut, making it the ultimate statement piece for cold weather. This coat is not just an addition to your wardrobe; it's a design milestone that embodies sophistication and luxury in every stitch.

Material: Polyester - White duck down
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/landmark-down-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_47_cad801e6-bb4b-4150-aabf-9c8b94ec0c62.png?v=1735423418</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9469845930248</g:id>
      <g:title>Leather Neck Strap</g:title>
      <g:description>Stylish Leather Neck Strap with Magnetic Ends
This versatile and stylish leather neck strap is the perfect accessory for keeping your essentials close at hand. Designed primarily for sunglasses and eyeglasses, it also works for other small items you need to carry. The strap hangs comfortably around your neck, featuring leather tabs with internal magnets on the ends. These magnetic ends easily attach to cases or other items, providing a secure and fashionable way to keep your accessories within reach. A must-have for anyone who values both style and practicality.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/leather-neck-strap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vdaga_26.png?v=1726323188</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>9.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450792354056</g:id>
      <g:title>Lorena</g:title>
      <g:description>This sophisticated women's handbag embodies high-end elegance with a unique and distinctive asymmetrical design. Perfect for formal occasions, it exudes refined style while offering practicality. Crafted from premium vegan leather, this bag combines luxury with a modern, eco-conscious approach. Its sleek lines and impeccable finish make it the ideal accessory for any woman seeking a statement piece that effortlessly complements her polished wardrobe.


Item Material:PU LeatherLining Material: PolyesterSize 36cm*6.5cm*31cm  / 14.2in*2.6in*12.2in

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/stylish-womens-bag-pu-leather-solid-color-design-oval-shoulder-bag-soft-handle-handbag-shopping-trip</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sb1bd43ae416244fcb7093ac41f13f9405.webp?v=1725208118</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9582346207496</g:id>
      <g:title>Louvre Maxi Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover an effortlessly stylish and versatile long down coat designed for women who value both fashion and functionality. Featuring a chic stand-up collar that buttons securely for added warmth, this coat is perfect for elevating your look on formal outings while seamlessly pairing with sporty or casual outfits. Lightweight yet cozy, it’s the ideal piece to keep you warm and on-trend all season long.

Material:
Cotton 55% 
Polyester 45%
Fill in: White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summit-style-maxi-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_40_f3d5a74b-4be9-4d64-b690-6f4805ab4d9d.png?v=1735075255</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>129.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9556210352392</g:id>
      <g:title>Luminous Luxe Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Turn heads this winter with our long glossy down coat, designed to make a bold fashion statement while keeping you warm. Featuring a sleek, shiny finish and a flattering waist tie belt, this coat accentuates your silhouette for an effortlessly chic look. The exquisite detailing, from its bold accents to the luxurious texture, makes it the perfect choice for those who love to stand out. Insulated with premium duck down, it offers superior warmth and comfort, ideal for both casual outings and glamorous winter nights.
Material: Polyester-Velvet-White duck down
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/luminous-luxe-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_16.png?v=1731948977</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>129.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554613993736</g:id>
      <g:title>Luxe Haven Fur-Trimmed Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>The epitome of classy winterwear, this premium long down coat is designed for women who appreciate timeless elegance and exceptional quality. Crafted with luxurious down filling for unparalleled warmth, it features a stunning fur-trimmed hood and delicately fur-lined cuffs for a touch of sophistication. Intricate stitching and refined details add a chic, tailored finish, making it the perfect choice for upscale outings or cold-weather soirées.


Hat and Sleeve Details: Rabbit Fur

Polyester Fiber (30D 380T High-Density Anti-Drill Fabric)Outer Fabric: 


Composition: 100% Polyester Fiber



Lining Fabric: Polyester Fiber

Filling Material:  90% White Duck Down

Colors Available: Beige, Black


Size: Carefully consult the size chart.



 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/luxe-haven-fur-trimmed-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_62.png?v=1738605683</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>190.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9443531227400</g:id>
      <g:title>M34 Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with our versatile Tote Bag for Women. With its sleek design and spacious interior, this nylon shoulder bag is perfect for work, travel, and shopping. The secure zipper keeps your belongings safe while the solid color adds a touch of elegance. Effortlessly complement any outfit and occasion with this underarm bag.







 
Feature: 
1. Premium Quality and Comfort: Indulge in luxury with this exquisite tote bag crafted from durable nylon fabric. Not only does it offer exceptional durability, but it also provides a comfortable and smooth feel when held. Experience the perfect blend of style and comfort as you carry this bag with confidence and elegance.
2. Perfect Size: This shoulder bag is 460.00 x 310.00 x 180.00 mm/18.11 x 12.2 x 7.09 inch, providing ample space for a wallet, phone, glasses, keys, and other small items. 
3. Versatile and Stylish Design: Elevate your fashion game with this practical handbag that effortlessly combines fashion-forward elements with simplicity. Its timeless design ensures it complements any outfit, making it a versatile accessory for various occasions. Whether you're heading to work, a social gathering, or a casual outing, this handbag will effortlessly enhance your style and make a statement. Embrace the perfect blend of fashion and functionality with this must-have accessory.
4. Versatile and Functional: This satchel purse is designed to cater to your diverse needs, making it the perfect companion for a wide range of activities. Whether you're going shopping, on a date, commuting to work, traveling, enjoying a vacation, attending a party, or focusing on your professional endeavors, this clutch purse has got you covered. 


            













</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/tote-bag-for-womens-nylon-large-capacity-shoulder-bag-with-zipper-solid-color-underarm-bag-for-work-travel-shopping-shopper-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/5_c32432d4-d341-4169-8fa2-a69fcf1d5628.png?v=1724779049</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450795925768</g:id>
      <g:title>Mabel</g:title>
      <g:description>Indulge in luxury with our MABEL Handmade Woven Leather Shoulder and Hand Purse. Crafted from 100% premium leather, this chic and stylish bag is available in a variety of unique colors, allowing you to make a statement wherever you go. The red suede and bucket tote design add a touch of elegance, making it perfect for both shopping and everyday use. Elevate your style with MABEL, the ultimate blend of craftsmanship and sophistication.




 





</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mabula-handmade-woven-leather-female-fashion-shoulder-purse-red-suede-woman-bucket-tote-bag-elegant-shopping-ladies-hobo-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S9216e638fdf14e009d9ab7f28d451053O.webp?v=1725209504</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375131074824</g:id>
      <g:title>Macho</g:title>
      <g:description>Ultimate comfort! Summer Clogs, with a thick insole and cozy, close toe design, these slip-ons will make you feel like you're walking on clouds (literally). Available for both men and women, these macho and stylish slippers are just perfect. Try them out now!


Material: EVA


Heel Height: Low (1,2inch)







modname=ckeditor                     



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summer-clogs-slipper-for-women-men-new-fashion-thick-insole-platform-slippers-with-buckle-cozy-home-close-toe-slipprers-mules</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S08685e6d8b5341c5841245af34c8b716a.webp?v=1720613511</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9547982536968</g:id>
      <g:title>Majesty Longline Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Once again, we break the mold in fashion with this elegant, longline women's coat. Designed with a classic, robe-style waist tie, it redefines sophistication, offering a blend of structure and grace. This coat doesn’t just elevate your look; it elevates you. Slip it on, and you instantly embody a refined presence, exuding a confidence and elegance that makes you feel like the best version of yourself. Perfectly balanced between timeless style and modern edge, this piece is crafted for those who value luxury with every step.

Material: Polyester-White duck down
Model: Alian
Height: 5'9" (176 cm)
Measurements: 32.3" / 23.2" / 33.9" (82 / 59 / 86 cm)
Weight: 101.4 lbs (46 kg)
Model is wearing size: S

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/majesty-longline-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_2.png?v=1731153519</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>179.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386342777096</g:id>
      <g:title>Malena</g:title>
      <g:description>Rock your summer look with this New in Sandals! Feature a high heel and platform design, making them perfect for all-day and night wear. Slip into the thick-soled Roman-inspired design for a trendy yet comfortable fashion statement. Elevate your shoe game and step into summer with these chic and playful sandals, the ultimate blend of fashion and comfort.


Platform Height:  (+2,5 inch)


Sole Material: RUBBER

Size: We encourage customers, if their foot is thick or they are on the borderline, to choose the next size up.



 




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2023-summer-new-womens-sandals-outer-wear-fashion-casual-slip-toe-thick-soled-roman-slippers-platform-sandals-woman-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Winter_Collection_31_f66a4abe-a0ce-47dc-ac94-0ff69c1e0bdd.png?v=1730379688</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9372619669768</g:id>
      <g:title>Mamos</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing VdaGama's newest arrival. Stylish Women's Platform Sandal with slip-resistant sole, are perfect for the beach or any summer event. With an adjustable buckle, they offer both fashion and function. Don't miss out on the latest addition to your summer wardrobe!


With Platforms: Yes


Upper Material: EVA


Outsole Material: EVA









</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/kidmi-womens-platform-sandals-summer-slippers-fashion-non-slip-beach-sandals-2024-summer-women-flip-flops-adjustable-buckle-1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Winter_Collection_33.png?v=1730380379</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>16.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386503274760</g:id>
      <g:title>Marine Clog</g:title>
      <g:description>Indulge in luxury with our Women's Light And Soft Thick-soled EVA Sandals. Crafted with a new arrival design and a sturdy platform, these sandals offer both style and stability. Perfect for any outdoor adventure or casual occasion, these non-slip sandals are a must-have for any fashion-forward woman.


Platform Height: 0-3cm


Material: EVA

We encourage customers, if their foot is thick or they are on the borderline, to choose the next size up.

 
 


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/womens-light-and-soft-thick-soled-eva-sandals-casual-slippers-outdoor-white-non-slip-simple-baotou-fashion-womens-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S2a1ccc00ae21405d9248f87be94a7d1dO.webp?v=1721321693</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.50 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9381729042696</g:id>
      <g:title>Mary Frith Sandal</g:title>
      <g:description>



Our Best-Selling Sandals: Comfort and Style Combined
Step into a world of unmatched comfort and style with our best-selling Sandals. Designed to be super soft, anti-slip, and noiseless, these clogs are the epitome of practical elegance and everyday luxury.
Why Our Classic Clogs are a Best Seller:


Classic Design: Timeless and versatile, our Classic Clogs effortlessly complement any outfit, making them a staple in every wardrobe.

Super Soft Comfort: Made with ultra-soft materials, these clogs provide a cushioned, cloud-like feel with every step, ensuring maximum comfort all day long.


Anti-Slip Technology: Engineered with advanced anti-slip soles, these clogs offer exceptional traction and stability on any surface, keeping you safe and secure.

Noiseless Steps: Walk confidently and quietly with our noiseless design, perfect for any setting, from home to work and everywhere in between.

Durable and Reliable: Built to last, our Sandals maintain their comfort and style even after extensive wear, making them a reliable choice for daily use.

Perfect for Every Occasion
Whether you're at home, at work, or out for a casual day, our Classic Clogs are the ideal choice. Their timeless design and superior comfort make them suitable for any occasion, ensuring you look and feel your best. Shop now and step into the ultimate in comfort and style!






Platform Height: 1,2 inch


Material: EVA









sell well








</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/buckle-thick-platform-slippers-women-summer-beach-eva-soft-sole-slides-sandals-woman-indoor-bathroom-anti-slip-cloud-slipper</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Winter_Collection_34.png?v=1730381811</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>15.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375033688328</g:id>
      <g:title>Mary Jane</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing the new Mary Jane Shoes, a perfect blend of style, comfort, and versatility. These shoes feature a charming bowknot detail that adds a playful touch to any outfit. The thick sole not only provides added height but also ensures a comfortable and stable wear, making them ideal for all-day use.
Designed to pair seamlessly with skirts, these Mary Jane shoes are a must-have addition to any wardrobe. Stay ahead of the fashion curve with this trendy design that doesn't compromise on comfort. Elevate your footwear collection with these chic and functional shoes, perfect for any occasion.
SPECIFICATIONS



• Versatile Toe Shape :Featuring an unconventional toe shape, these shoes add a unique touch to any outfit while remaining comfortable and stylish.

• Rubber Upper Material :The rubber upper material of these shoes offers a soft and flexible feel, ensuring a comfortable fit for all-day wear.

• All-Match Design :With their all-match design, these shoes can be paired with a variety of outfits, making them a versatile addition to any wardrobe.

• Thick Bottom Skirt Single-layer Shoes :The thick bottom skirt design and single-layer construction of these shoes provide additional support and stability, ensuring a secure walk or stand.




     
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/black-soft-cute-bowknot-mary-jane-shoes-womens-versatile-thick-bottom-matching-skirt-single-shoes-2023-new-jk-style</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-10T183809.572.png?v=1720625922</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375035490568</g:id>
      <g:title>Mary Jane Clog</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing Mary Jane's Clog summer, your new best friend! Cassy and cute, these non-slip EVA slippers are just perfect. Simply slip on and go with the adorable bowknot design. Enjoy comfort and style in one cute package.
SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: EVA
Season: Summer
Fashion Element: light
Outsole Material: EVA
With Platforms: Yes
Style: Concise
Insole Material: EVA

Important Notice:
1、Our size is manufactore's size, please choose according to 'shoe size' and 'foot length' in the size chart.




If your foot is a bit wide or you are on the borderline, choose the next size up.












</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mo-dou-wrapped-toe-summer-slippers-for-women-indoor-outdoor-non-slip-eva-slippers-for-girls-cute-bowknot-sandals-for-women</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Winter_Collection_38.png?v=1730383252</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>14.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9381705941256</g:id>
      <g:title>MATRIX</g:title>
      <g:description>Redefine Your Walking Experience with Our Expertly Designed Clogs
Experience unparalleled comfort and performance with our expertly designed clogs, guaranteed to transform the way you walk. Engineered with advanced features such as anti-slip and anti-bacterial properties, these slippers are a testament to years of innovative design and craftsmanship.


Unmatched Walking Experience: Our clogs are crafted to provide an exceptional walking experience, thanks to the expertise of our design team. Every step feels light, comfortable, and supported.

Advanced Design: With years of design innovation behind them, these clogs offer a superior fit and unparalleled comfort. The ergonomic design ensures optimal support and reduces foot fatigue.

Anti-Slip Technology: Stay secure on your feet with our cutting-edge anti-slip soles. These clogs provide excellent traction on various surfaces, keeping you safe and stable wherever you go.

Anti-Bacterial Properties: Enjoy the peace of mind that comes with our anti-bacterial materials, which help keep your feet fresh and hygienic, even after long hours of wear.

Durable and Stylish: Combining durability with contemporary style, these clogs are perfect for any occasion, from casual outings to long walks. Their sleek design makes them a versatile addition to any wardrobe.

Perfect for Every Occasion
Whether you're exploring the city, taking a leisurely stroll, or running errands, our expertly designed clogs ensure you do it all in comfort and style. The advanced features make them ideal for daily wear, providing the support and protection your feet deserve.
Redefine Your Steps
Take a step into the future of footwear with our clogs. Experience the perfect blend of cutting-edge technology, innovative design, and unmatched comfort. Redefine the way you walk and enjoy every step.


Insole Material: EVA


Heel Height: Low (1.2 inch)


We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summer-beach-slippers-luxury-brand-men-women-fashion-outdoor-indoor-eva-soft-flip-flops-male-thick-serrated-sole-anti-slip-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_5.png?v=1731085431</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370193494280</g:id>
      <g:title>MD 45</g:title>
      <g:description>New age Explosive Style Flip Flops! These anti-slippery, brave platform sandals are not only fashionable but also feature a thick bottom for extra comfort and support. Perfect for both indoor and outdoor wear, these flip flops offer a trendy and practical option for any occasion. Upgrade your summer footwear game today!


Material: EVA

We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.






1Measurement In CM



US size
Europe Size
Heel To Toe(in cm)
CN Size


6
38
24
38


6.5
39
24.5
39


7
40
25
40


8
41
25.5
41


8.5
42
26
42


9.5
43
26.5
43


10
44
27
44


11
45
27.5
45


12
46
28
46


13
47
28.5
47


14
48
29
48



Size Recommendation Standard Size




Kind reminder: Due to slight color and brightness differences in shooting lighting, computers, mobile phones, and other devices, please refer to the actual product.

Eva slipper,Home slippers,Slippers for men,Comfortable men's slipper,Slippers for home,Slippers for home man,Slippers for men,Slippers home,Slippers indoor house,Slippers men,Slippers men's home,

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/explosive-style-flip-flops-for-men-anti-slippery-cute-platform-fashionably-men-sandals-thick-bottom-suitable-indoor-and-outdoor</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025.png?v=1731081662</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375130288392</g:id>
      <g:title>MENS 11</g:title>
      <g:description>The perfect footwear. Simple, cozy, and as soft as a pillow. With a breathable design, and stylish look, these shoes are the ultimate choice for water sports and wading. Keep your feet cool and dry while looking your best.
Material: Bamboo fiber
Gender: Unisex
sizePlease choose size according to the foot length FOR EUROPE PLEASE NOTE THAT:Size 34-35 = foot length 22.0cm   Size 36-37 = foot length 23.0 cm     Size 38-39 = foot length 24.0cm     Size 40-41 = foot length 25.0 cm     Size 42-43 = foot length 26.0 cm     Size 44-45 = foot length 27.0 cm     Size 46-47 = foot length 28.0 cm     Size 48-49 = foot length 29.0 cm</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mens-eva-garden-hole-shoes-water-sports-and-water-wading-shoes-outdoor-leisure-breathable-bag-toe-sandals-and-slipper</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S596ef7afb26448b7a541767e84376aedS.webp?v=1720613468</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>13.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9584757276936</g:id>
      <g:title>Merino Luxe</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience unmatched elegance and comfort with this long women's cardigan, crafted from 100% premium Merino wool. 
This heavy-knit piece offers unparalleled warmth and comfort, making it an essential addition to your wardrobe.
Key Features:


Superior Softness: The fine Merino fibers provide a gentle touch against the skin, ensuring maximum comfort without any itchiness.


Exceptional Warmth: Designed to retain body heat, this cardigan is perfect for cooler climates, keeping you cozy throughout the day.


Durability: Merino wool is renowned for its resilience, ensuring this cardigan remains a staple in your collection for years to come.


Natural Breathability: The inherent properties of Merino wool allow for excellent moisture-wicking, keeping you dry and comfortable.


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/merino-luxe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/winteredi_11.png?v=1733851693</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9549424492808</g:id>
      <g:title>Metro Comfort Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay effortlessly stylish this season with our modern long coat, designed with a casual flair and thoughtful details. Featuring a cozy hood and accentuated side pockets, this coat blends functionality with a sleek silhouette, perfect for everyday wear. Crafted for the woman who values both comfort and contemporary style, it’s a wardrobe staple that’s as versatile as it is chic. Embrace the colder days with a look that’s effortlessly put-together.
Material: Polyester-Polyester fiber
 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/metro-comfort-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_-_2025-01-09T222115.448.png?v=1736454392</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450771317000</g:id>
      <g:title>Milan</g:title>
      <g:description>This chic leather Shoulder/handbag is a must-have for any fashion-forward female. Made with 100% genuine leather, its luxury weave design adds a touch of cute to any outfit. Perfect for everyday use, this versatile bag can be worn as a shoulder or crossbody bag. Upgrade your style game with this solid color messenger tote!

Dimensions: 7.48*5.12*2.36inch / 19*13*6cm 
Materials: Cow Leather &amp; Cotton


Interior: Cell Phone Pocket


Interior: Interior Zipper Pocket


100% Cow Leather Luxury Weave Women Handbag New Genuine Leather Shoulder Crossbody Bag Female Solid Color Messenger Fashion Tote</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/100-cow-leather-luxury-weave-women-handbag-new-genuine-leather-shoulder-crossbody-bag-female-solid-color-messenger-fashion-tote</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S08e54511707a42f5a40a27d48b7c7a250.webp?v=1725201565</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9372566946056</g:id>
      <g:title>ML 45</g:title>
      <g:description>Looking to break away from the ordinary? Yoy are in the right place. This Clogs are the epitome of cutting-edge design, ensuring you stand out and turn heads everywhere you go. With their ultra-soft construction, you'll feel like you're walking on clouds, making all-day wear a breeze. These sandals don't just keep up with the trends—they set them. Get ready to gather attention and make a statement with every step.
Material: EVA






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summer-man-sandals-lightweight-home-beach-sandals-women-slippers-outdoor-quick-dry-flat-soft-eva-hole-shoes-women-slippers</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S02c8800695184044af0a47303938281bN.webp?v=1720359959</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9647307882760</g:id>
      <g:title>Monarc</g:title>
      <g:description>The word extraordinary is reserved for creations that transcend the ordinary, redefine expectations, and exist in a league of their own. This sleeveless down jacket is exactly that—a masterpiece of high fashion, sculpted for the modern woman who seeks sophistication in every detail.
Crafted from matte and textured jacquard fabric, it boasts an exquisite interplay of fine ribbed stripes and embossed tonal polka dots, forming a mesmerizing visual texture that shifts with movement. The avant-garde silhouette, marked by intricate, sculptural cuts, transforms it from a mere garment into a statement—one that whispers luxury yet demands attention.
Filled with premium down insulation, it wraps you in warmth without compromising its featherlight feel. Every stitch, every contour speaks of craftsmanship and artistic vision, creating an iconic piece that defies trends and embraces timeless allure.
Ordinary was never an option.
Material: Polyester Fiber - White duck down
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/monarc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_15.png?v=1738438581</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370186121480</g:id>
      <g:title>MR 10 Clog</g:title>
      <g:description>Get ready to turn heads with our latest clog sandals. Combining soft, comfortable materials with a high-quality, non-slip sole, these clogs are designed for ultimate wearability. Our unique 2024 designs represent the latest in fashion innovation, making them a standout addition to your wardrobe.


Upper Material: PVC


Insole Material: PVC

We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/metasch-mens-and-womens-breathable-thick-slipper-lightweight-beach-shoes-ins-summer-couples-slides-hole-shoes-baotou-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_1.png?v=1720273429</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>24.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450796908808</g:id>
      <g:title>Navigator Luxe Series</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style and functionality with our Haute Couture Cowhide Leather Backpack. Crafted from the finest first-layer cow leather, this luxurious backpack is the epitome of sophistication—perfect for business or travel. Designed with multiple compartments for optimal organization, it features a specially reinforced interior pocket to keep your laptop secure. The classic design exudes a serious and refined elegance, making it the ultimate accessory for the discerning professional. Upgrade your everyday look with this timeless piece of luxury.


First Layer Cowhide Leather Backpack Men's Fashion Business Large Capacity High School Student Bag Travel Backpack Laptop Bags










</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/first-layer-cowhide-leather-backpack-mens-fashion-business-large-capacity-high-school-student-bag-travel-backpack-laptop-bags</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sdb58196f58fc4fc1b8b5d9a297c970cdI.webp?v=1725209876</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445291819272</g:id>
      <g:title>Nepal XL Tote</g:title>
      <g:description>Indulge in luxury with our Extra Large Bag for Women. Handcrafted from genuine cowhide leather, it's the ultimate choice for the stylish and sophisticated woman. With its large capacity and unique design, this shoulder bag is both practical and a statement piece. Elevate your wardrobe with our vintage-inspired handbag.


Main Material: Genuine Leather (Cow Leather)

Lining Material: Polyester
Design &amp; Shape:

Shape: Casual Tote

Pattern Type: Patchwork

Style: Casual

Hardness: Soft
Interior Features:
Cell Phone Pocket
Interior Zipper Pocket
Closure:

Type: Zipper

Dimensions:


Size: 20 x 7.87 x 11.41 inches (51 x 20 x 29 cm)






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/extra-large-bag-for-women-genuine-leather-shoulder-bag-vintage-luxury-cowhide-handbag-big-tote-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S9cbf37161ef946ceae12c7c9675143747.webp?v=1724763442</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445289623816</g:id>
      <g:title>New Arrivals Genuine Leather Knitted Bags Lady Trend Cow Leather Handbags Women Shoulder Bags S4359</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: NoEnName_NullMain Material: GENUINE LEATHERGenuine Leather Type: Cow LeatherPlace Of Origin: ZHE JIANG  ProvincePlace Of Origin: ZHE JIANG  ProvinceOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: ZhejiangMaterial Composition: Genuine LeatherModel Number: S4359Shape: PillowGender: WOMENItem Length: 23cmItem Type: WAIST PACKSStyle: CasualStrap Drop: 20cmPattern Type: SolidMaterial: Genuine Cow LeatherFashion Knitted Style BagsSize: 23cm * 5.5cm * 15cm
  

       

  
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/new-arrivals-genuine-leather-knitted-bags-lady-trend-cow-leather-handbags-women-shoulder-bags-s4359</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S712c032751664cd081d641d93416db88w.webp?v=1724763250</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>91.75 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445286576392</g:id>
      <g:title>New Men Clutch Bag Microfiber Leather Women Woven Fashion Brand Simple Envelope Wallet Designer Large Capacity Zipper Purse</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: NoEnName_NullOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: GuangdongLining Material: POLYESTERMain Material: PUShape: ClutchStyle: fashionOccasion: partyPattern Type: KnittingModel Number: 1026Interior: Interior Slot PocketExterior: noneClosure Type: zipperDecoration: nonePlace Of Origin: China (mainland)Hardness: SOFTGender: UnisexCN: Guangdong



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/new-men-clutch-bag-microfiber-leather-women-woven-fashion-brand-simple-envelope-wallet-designer-large-capacity-zipper-purse</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Scb84e48b2d714180b6bb990874551dafB.webp?v=1724763112</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.42 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9591670178056</g:id>
      <g:title>Noir Élite Leather Hooded Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Class comes from classy, and this luxurious leather coat is the ultimate expression of prestige and sophistication."Designed for women with impeccable style and a taste for the extraordinary, this long leather coat redefines chic elegance. Falling just below the knee, it combines timeless design with modern luxury. The premium leather finish exudes opulence, while the tailored silhouette flatters the figure effortlessly. The addition of a hood adds a touch of contemporary flair, making it both fashionable and functional for colder days.
This statement piece is more than a coat—it's a signature of your unique style. Perfect for upscale events or elevating your everyday look, it’s the ideal choice for women who embrace their confidence and prestige.


Material: Premium genuine leather
White duck down +95%



 
 
 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/noir-elite-leather-hooded-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_-_2025-01-14T203652.938.png?v=1736879884</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>199.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587879379208</g:id>
      <g:title>Noire Élégance Wrap</g:title>
      <g:description>Style is a reflection of your inner essence. This luxurious long down coat redefines elegance with an impeccable blend of timeless sophistication and distinctive design. Crafted for women who appreciate individuality, it features a dual-material composition that harmonizes contrasting textures and aesthetics—smooth, silky sheen meets tactile richness—creating an eye-catching masterpiece that exudes refinement.
The coat’s innovative double-hood design adds a layer of bold yet practical versatility, perfect for facing winter's chill in style. A waist-cinching belt provides a flattering, feminine silhouette, allowing you to showcase poise and confidence with every step. Its generous length not only ensures exceptional warmth but also elevates its presence, making it impossible to blend in with the ordinary.

Material: 
Fabric: Polyester
Fill in: White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/noire-elegance-wrap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_12_80db7b18-fb6e-4a17-a021-2db424925f65.png?v=1734300141</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>249.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9532966240520</g:id>
      <g:title>Nordic Luxe Insulated Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace the height of winter fashion with this exceptionally warm, long down coat. Designed with a high, thick collar for added protection against the cold, this coat is both stylish and functional, wrapping you in luxurious warmth. The sleek silhouette and premium down filling make it a must-have for the season, combining elegance with top-tier insulation. Ideal for those who seek a blend of sophistication and warmth, this coat is set to become your go-to piece for the winter — a timeless addition that captures the latest trend in fashion-forward outerwear.
Material: Polyerter
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.

 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/nordic-luxe-insulated-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_72_e3c052bc-04da-4c0a-adeb-c31bc334a43e.png?v=1738607158</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>159.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9591567417608</g:id>
      <g:title>Nova Oversized Knitwear</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience effortless style and comfort with our oversized wool turtleneck tunic sweater.Crafted for women who love a relaxed yet chic aesthetic, this tunic sweater doubles as a cozy dress. Its high-quality wool blend ensures warmth and softness, perfect for cooler days. The loose, oversized fit flatters all body types while allowing freedom of movement, and the classic turtleneck design adds a touch of timeless sophistication. Dress it up with boots and a belt for an elevated look, or pair it with leggings and sneakers for a laid-back vibe.


Material: 100% Australian wool 

Fit: Relaxed, oversized

Features: Turtleneck, longline design, soft texture

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/nova-oversized-knitwear</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VscodaGama.png?v=1734628786</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9609944498440</g:id>
      <g:title>Nuvessa Luxe Cashmere Top</g:title>
      <g:description>Like the legendary Midas touch, this luxurious women’s V-neck crossover top transforms your everyday style with the unmatched softness of cashmere. Designed in an elegant Korean-inspired silhouette, it drapes beautifully, offering both timeless sophistication and modern minimalism.
Crafted from ultra-lightweight, premium-quality cashmere, this top feels incredibly gentle against the skin, making it perfect for all-day wear. Its meticulous stitching and flawless tailoring speak to the highest level of craftsmanship, ensuring a refined look and exceptional durability.

Material: Cashmere +30% - Wool -70%

 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/nuvessa-luxe-cashmere-top</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_68.png?v=1738779387</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>93.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9647383281928</g:id>
      <g:title>Obscura</g:title>
      <g:description>



A statement of modern sophistication, this sleeveless quilted down vest blends minimalist luxury with versatile styling. The sculpted silhouette, refined hood, and adjustable side slit with button closure create a seamless balance of elegance and edge. Perfectly tailored for effortless layering, it’s a timeless essential for the woman who moves with style.
 



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/obscura</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_36.png?v=1738775727</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9372588474632</g:id>
      <g:title>Old fashion</g:title>
      <g:description>Old-time classics sandals, feature a super soft insole for a truly heavenly feel with every step. With arch support built in, you'll feel like you're walking on clouds. Slip these on and experience the ultimate comfort for your feet..


Platform Height: 1.6inch


Upper Material: EVA

We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.

















































</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/pallene-fashion-summer-sandals-women-thick-insole-eva-clogs-slippers-with-arch-support-soft-beach-flip-flops-new-original-slides</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S2a319f932401410896eaf9efe20047b02.webp?v=1720362655</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370192642312</g:id>
      <g:title>Optimus</g:title>
      <g:description>Inspired by the most advanced human-centered design, Transformen has created the most innovative and comfortable slippers for the year 2024. These slippers redefine relaxation, ensuring every step is a blend of style and unparalleled comfort.
We encourage customers who are not 100% sure of their size to choose the next size up.




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fashion-summer-couple-style-toe-wrap-sandals-platform-non-slip-flip-flop-for-men-women-outdoor-beach-shoes-mens-home-slippers</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S7dde59f947464491a3f5320b9824510ez.webp?v=1720198745</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9548121506056</g:id>
      <g:title>Opulence Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in the ultimate blend of elegance and warmth with this luxurious women's coat. Crafted for those who appreciate both style and comfort, this coat boasts a unique, sophisticated design that stands out effortlessly. With its plush, cozy interior and tailored silhouette, it’s more than just outerwear—it’s a statement piece. 

Material: Polyeaster
White duck down


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/opulence-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_62.png?v=1735424104</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>139.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9582435991816</g:id>
      <g:title>OverEase 3/4 Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Effortlessly chic and versatile, this oversized women’s jacket with 3/4 sleeves is the ultimate layering essential. Designed for ease and style, it pairs seamlessly with everything in your wardrobe, from casual denim to sleek dresses. Wear it solo for a statement look or layer it over another coat for added warmth and a bold, fashion-forward vibe. Perfect for transitional weather or those moments when you want comfort and elegance in one piece, this jacket redefines effortless dressing.
Material: Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/overease-3-4-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_60.png?v=1734210332</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370150142216</g:id>
      <g:title>Oxforde Platforme</g:title>
      <g:description> 




Introducing the Epitome of Style and Comfort—our Latest Super Soft platform Clogs. Elevate your fashion game with these stunning shoes, perfect for adding extra height without sacrificing an ounce of comfort. Crafted for those who understand that true art needs no explanation, these clogs are more than just footwear; they’re a statement. With unparalleled comfort designed to last, you'll experience a blend of innovation and elegance with every step. Discover the latest in fashion and redefine your style with our extraordinary clogs.





SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: EVA
Heel Type: Flat with
Item Type: slippers
Fashion Element: Platform
Department Name: ADULT
Outsole Material: EVA
With Platforms: Yes
Style: retro
Insole Material: EVA
We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.





</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/eva-casual-platform-slippers-women-flats-house-designer-shoes-girls-retro-fashion-summer-sandals-ladies-elegant-beach-footwear</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S0a66b39fcfb8484d9a9a0f892c508ee6w.webp?v=1720195981</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9444180754696</g:id>
      <g:title>Palermo</g:title>
      <g:description>Add a dash of quirkiness to your winter wardrobe with our Women Quilted Tote Handbag. Designed with a fluffy down texture and large capacity, this handbag will elevate your style and hold all your essentials.


Main Material: PolyesterClosure Type: zipperSize: 390*290*95mm/15.35*11.42*3.74inch

,           </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-quilted-tote-handbag-large-capacity-brand-designer-casual-winter-shoulder-bag-fluffy-down-luxury-purses-shiny-for-female-1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/54.webp?v=1726751492</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>21.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9472613744904</g:id>
      <g:title>Papillon Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your evening look with this one-of-a-kind bow-shaped handbag. Crafted to make a bold statement, its sculpted design mimics the elegance of a perfectly tied bow, ensuring all eyes are on you. The delicate handle offers both sophistication and comfort, allowing you to carry it effortlessly.
Its compact yet spacious size makes it the ideal accessory for an evening out—just enough room for all your essentials without compromising style. Whether paired with a classic cocktail dress or a chic modern ensembe, this bag is designed to stand out. Prepare to turn heads with every step.

SIZE: 11.41*11.02*6.29inch / 29*28*16cm
MATERIAL: Polyester Fabric / Nailon


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/papillon-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_edit.png?v=1731675792</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9548109054216</g:id>
      <g:title>Paramount Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Forget the world’s chill—this coat wraps you in unmatched warmth, making winter feel like a distant memory. This reinforced coat is crafted to endure even the lowest temperatures, with premium down insulation, a refined high collar, and a sleek, windproof shell that keeps the elements at bay. Engineered for warmth without compromise, this is sophistication in every stitch. Winter’s got nothing on you!

Material:
Fabric: Polyester
Fill in: White duck down


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/paramount-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_52.png?v=1735423736</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>249.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386303717640</g:id>
      <g:title>Pari</g:title>
      <g:description>Upgrade your shoe game with our New French Women's Shoes! The cute design features a convenient hook and loop closure and a quirky platform for added height. These versatile shoes will add a touch of French flair to your daily look. (Plus, they're totally unic-- I mean, unique!)
VdaGama 2024 Exclusive Collection
SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: PU/CANVA
Heel Height: Med (- 2inch)
Insole Material: EVA
Lining Material: none




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/new-french-womens-shoes-hook-and-loop-casual-platform-fashion-comfortable-simple-hundred-wind-daily-girls-mary-jane-retro-shoes-1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_6.png?v=1731085658</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450796876040</g:id>
      <g:title>Plezir</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our 2024 Spring Collection! This small yet high capacity tote bag is perfect for any commute, with a classic and easy-to-wear design in a retro frosted finish. Upgrade your style with this must-have accessory!

SIZE: 9.45*8.66*6.3inch / 24*22*16cmial: Leather
Material: Leather



 

 
  

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-spring-summer-new-frosted-small-and-high-end-high-capacity-retro-commuter-handheld-one-shoulder-tote-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sb3438b413c934cf99af6315f703c9305F.webp?v=1725209849</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>79.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9582742733064</g:id>
      <g:title>Polar Belle</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience the perfect blend of warmth, elegance, and sophistication with our premium long puffer coat. Designed to withstand the harshest winter days, this coat features a luxuriously soft hood trimmed with faux fur, a belted waist for a tailored fit, and a timeless silhouette that exudes refinement. Crafted for both comfort and style, it is the ultimate choice for women seeking a statement piece that doesn’t compromise on functionality. Elevate your winter wardrobe with unparalleled sophistication.
Material: Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/polar-belle</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_26.png?v=1733776800</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554820595976</g:id>
      <g:title>Polar Luxe Maxi Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Defy the cold and embrace luxury with this ultra-warm, oversized coat that truly "turns winter into summer." Designed with a generously flowing silhouette, it combines maximum comfort with bold, elegant style. The extra-long length ensures full-body coverage, making it the ultimate shield against chilly winds, while the adjustable waist tie adds a flattering shape to its voluminous design. Perfect for those who love a touch of eccentric sophistication, this coat is as eye-catching as it is practical. Whether you're strolling through snow-covered streets or attending a winter soirée, this coat is your go-to for unbeatable warmth and standout style.

Material: Polyester-White duck down




 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/polar-luxe-maxi-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_98_bdcf3a01-3ae5-4b80-b5cd-28a2b1d71fce.png?v=1736707251</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>190.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533629432072</g:id>
      <g:title>Prestige Piqué Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the elegance of this exquisite high-couture coat, crafted from premium piqué-textured fabric that adds sophistication to its timeless design. With its long length and distinguished high collar &amp; hood, this coat is exceptionally warm, enveloping you in both comfort and style. Perfect for formal occasions, it enhances any outfit with an air of authority and refined taste, making it an essential addition to the wardrobe of those who value classic luxury.
Materials: Polyester - White duck down
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/prestige-pique-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_56_e799cbee-c0b9-4817-aa12-4bf64920e0a4.png?v=1735423838</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>159.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9614306869512</g:id>
      <g:title>Pure Bliss Cashmere Sweater</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in unparalleled softness with this relaxed-fit women's knit sweater. Designed with wide long sleeves and delicate embossed patterns, it offers an effortlessly chic look while providing maximum comfort. Crafted from premium-quality cashmere, it’s incredibly lightweight, breathable, and gentle on the skin. Perfect for layering or wearing solo, this sweater feels as luxurious as it looks.

Material: Cashmere 30% - Wool 70%
Size: One Size: Length: 24.02in, Sleeve Length: 22.44in, Bust: 47.24in.





Important Notice:Please keep in mind that this is a one-size product, so the fit may vary depending on your body type. The model in the photos is 5'4" tall, weighs 99 lbs, and has measurements of 30.7" / 26" / 33.1" (Bust/Waist/Hip). We recommend using these details as a reference before making your purchase to better understand how the sweater might fit you.




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/pure-bliss-cashmere-sweater</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama-2025-01-14T155633.719_d7577d6c-69f2-45c6-a001-c3c6b364830d.png?v=1736874943</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9589161853192</g:id>
      <g:title>Pure Form Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Crafted for the modern woman who values understated sophistication, this coat embodies minimalism at its finest. Made from premium Cashmere, it offers a soft touch and an impeccably tailored fit that flows effortlessly with every step. Its clean lines and classic silhouette ensure it never goes out of style, while the attention to detail—subtle seams, a structured collar, and a flawless drape—elevate it to a wardrobe essential. Perfect for any occasion, this coat is the ultimate blend of simplicity, class, and enduring elegance.
Material: Cashmere 10% - Wool 90%
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/pure-form-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_31_b4403109-b20d-440c-b899-7fa7292de90b.png?v=1734385386</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9555911966984</g:id>
      <g:title>Radiant Ruby Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay effortlessly warm and stylish this winter with our long red down coat, designed to combine elegance and functionality. Featuring a high, thick collar and a cozy detachable hood, this coat offers ultimate protection against the cold while maintaining a chic silhouette. Its vivid and striking red color adds a bold touch, making it a true showstopper. With spacious pockets, it's perfect for keeping your hands warm or carrying essentials on the go. This coat is your must-have for embracing cold days with confidence and flair.

Materials: Polyester-White duck down
Model information: Height: 69.29 in-Bust: 32.28 in-Waist: 23.23 in-Hips: 33.86 in-Weight: 101.4 lbs-Size Worn: S ​

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/radiant-ruby-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_13_c67e29f9-ad37-43d0-a4f2-9bb10363c3d5.png?v=1731940904</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9648296231176</g:id>
      <g:title>Rebel Down Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>A statement piece that defies fashion norms.
Break free from the ordinary with this bold, asymmetrical down puffer vest, designed for those who dare to stand out. Featuring striking, avant-garde cuts, an elevated high collar, and extended shoulder coverage, this vest reshapes the classic puffer silhouette with a fearless, fashion-forward edge.
Its sculptural design plays with proportions, creating a look that is both powerful and effortlessly chic. The asymmetrical structure adds movement and fluidity, while the structured shoulders bring a modern, architectural feel. Designed for style visionaries, this vest turns every outfit into a runway moment.

Material: White duck down - Polyester

Key Features:
✔ Daring Asymmetrical Cut – A fresh take on modern fashion✔ Extended Shoulder Design – A bold, structured look✔ Sleek High Collar – Adds drama and elegance✔ Ultra-Warm Down Filling – Lightweight yet insulating✔ Fashion-Forward Appeal – Designed to turn heads
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/rebel-down-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_54_2a6fb445-4a47-488d-9760-219185c5d9c8.png?v=1738523487</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9444315398408</g:id>
      <g:title>Refined Statement Blazer</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your wardrobe with our Women's Long Sleeve Double-Breasted Blazer, a perfect blend of elegance and sophistication. Designed with a timeless silhouette and crafted from luxurious fabric, this blazer is ideal not only for the office but also for any formal occasion where you want to make a lasting impression. Its versatile design seamlessly transitions from business meetings to evening events, making it a must-have for the autumn and winter seasons of 2024. Whether you're heading to a professional setting or a refined gathering, this blazer ensures you stand out with effortless style.
Materials: Premium acetate fabric (cationc), Spandex.
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.
Important Sizing Information
Please note that the measurements provided in the size chart reflect the dimensions of the garment itself, not the body. When selecting your size, it is essential to measure yourself and leave enough room for comfort (+0.79-1.6inch 2-4cm).
We recommend adding a few extra centimeters to your body measurements to ensure that the item will fit comfortably, especially when it comes to items like blazers and jackets that require some additional room.
If you are unsure about which size to choose, please do not hesitate to reach out to us for assistance.




    



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-long-sleeve-double-breasted-formal-blazer-gay-khaki-office-ladies-female-business-work-wear-jacket-for-autumn-winter-2023</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/0522b23775d94828ea1078f98cfd8d18.jpg?v=1731666307</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>79.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445291032840</g:id>
      <g:title>Regal Allure</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing the latest masterpiece in women's fashion—a handbag that stands as a true testament to design brilliance and aesthetic excellence. This meticulously crafted accessory features an intricate and stunning design that effortlessly captures attention, making it the focal point of any ensemble. Yet, its allure is not just in its eye-catching appeal; it exudes a timeless class and sophistication, instantly elevating the status of its bearer. Newly released, this design is the epitome of modern luxury, constructed from the finest quality split leather. It's not just a bag; it's a statement of prestige and elegance.
Lining Material: POLYESTER
Main Material: Split Leather


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/relwaver-women-messenger-bags-cowhide-split-leather-bag-for-women-2024-autumn-winter-fashion-flap-party-small-chic-crossbody-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/7.87inch_5.png?v=1724866948</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9372588441864</g:id>
      <g:title>Repose</g:title>
      <g:description>
















Solid Steps, Boundless Horizons.
Step into a new realm of comfort with our ultra-soft slippers that redefine walking. Designed with the perfect blend of luxury and practicality, these slippers promise an experience like no other.
Key Features:


Anti-Slip Sole: Stay secure with our specially designed anti-slip sole, ensuring every step you take is safe and stable.

Noiseless Walk: Experience the bliss of silent movement. Nobody will hear you coming as you glide effortlessly across any surface.

Ultra Soft Feel: Feel like you’re walking on clouds. Our slippers offer unmatched comfort that will make you take a moment to believe it’s real.

Anti-Bacterial Protection: Keep your feet fresh and healthy with our built-in anti-bacterial properties, providing a clean and hygienic environment for your feet.

Why Choose Our Slippers?
From the moment you slip them on, you’ll know these are not just any slippers. The unparalleled softness and comfort make every step feel like a dream. The noiseless design lets you move quietly, while the anti-slip sole gives you the confidence to walk without worry. Plus, with the anti-bacterial feature, your feet stay protected all day long.
Redefine Your Walking Experience
You’ll never want to take them off once you’ve tried them. These slippers provide a comfort level that is truly beyond anything you’ve ever experienced. It’s time to redefine the way you walk – step into a pair and feel the difference.
Experience the unmatched comfort and luxurious feel of our ultra-soft slippers. Your feet will thank you!









































SPECIFICATIONS
Outsole Material: EVA
With Platforms: Yes
Platform Height: 1.7inch
Insole Material: EVA




【Summer Slide】: Featuring a cloud slide and an open shoulder strap for enhanced breathability, these thick sole slides are very lightweight, waterproof, buoyant, unique design and versatility make it any summer leisure activity.

【Unmatched comfort】: These recovery sliders feature a 1.7-inch (approx. 4.3 cm) soft EVA midsole with excellent shock absorption and excellent cushioning, making every step feel like walking on a cloud.
【Arch Support】: Shevalues orthopedic sandals are designed with deep heel cups and wavy arch support to reduce stress, improve gait, and relieve foot pain such as plantar fasciitis and swollen feet.
【Durable and non-slip】:The sturdy sole that does not slip easily even if it is wet provides good grip and protection, and can be firmly stepped on on the pool, shower or beach on a smooth floor, making it ideal for use.
【Care &amp; Cleaning】: To keep these foam slippers in top condition, wipe stains with water or a damp cloth, keep out of direct sunlight, and avoid shrinkage in high temperatures.




































</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/pallene-fashion-thick-bottom-slippers-women-summer-soft-cloud-slippers-with-arch-support-beach-shoes-sandals-home-bathroom-slide</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_45.png?v=1721212259</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>16.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450767483144</g:id>
      <g:title>Riviera Handmade</g:title>
      <g:description>Handmade, piece by piece, a truly unique masterpiece. Handcrafted with meticulous attention to detail, this bag is made from the finest premium leather, offering unmatched durability and timeless elegance. Its sleek, geometric design sets it apart from the ordinary, making it the ultimate statement piece for the discerning woman on the go. With a lifetime guarantee, this exceptional bag is more than just an accessory—it's a symbol of superior quality and individuality. Say goodbye to bulky totes and embrace the unparalleled sophistication of RIVIERA.

SIZE: 10.82*10.43*1.5inch / 27.5*26.5*4cm
MATERIAL: Leather - First layer cowhide




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/jogujos-new-2021-messenger-bag-womens-geometric-sling-bags-famous-brand-female-large-capacity-totes-sac-femme-bolsas-feminina</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_5_813db55b-d2a9-4544-afe2-507abaa964bd.png?v=1731599448</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9381731533064</g:id>
      <g:title>Roma</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your footwear game with our latest Leather Seria, exclusively at VdaGama Collection. Crafted from premium cow leather, these Roman-style sandals epitomize both elegance and durability. Designed with a revolutionary anatomic footbed, they promise unparalleled comfort for all-day wear, making them the ideal choice for those who refuse to compromise on style or comfort.
Why Choose the VdaGamas Leather Seria?


Premium Quality: Made from the finest cow leather, these sandals are built to last while maintaining their sleek appearance.

Anatomic Design: The innovative footbed provides exceptional support and comfort, adapting to the natural contours of your feet.

Timeless Style: Inspired by classic Roman designs, these sandals blend historical elegance with modern sophistication.

All-Day Comfort: Perfect for any occasion, from a casual day out to an evening gathering, ensuring your feet feel as good as they look.

Take a step in the right direction with the Leather Seria. Embrace a progressive style, superior comfort, and premium quality that will keep you conquering the day in style. Discover the difference at VdaGama Collection today!

SPECIFICATIONS
Brand name: VdaGama
Upper Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Heel Type: Flat with
Lining Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Lining-Genuine Leather Type: pigskin
Outsole Material: RUBBER
With Platforms: Yes
Platform Height: 1.2 inch
Occasion: Casual
Closure Type: buckle strap
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Back Counter Type: Front &amp; Rear Strap
Insole Material: PU
COLOR: BLACK
SOLE: RUBBER
PACKING: 30*18*10CM
UPPER: LEATHER
G.W: 1.8KG
LINING: PIGSKIN
INSOLES: PU
PLATFORM: 3CM

SIZE CHART







</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-more-comfortable-leather-platform-sandals-foot-bed-breathable-leisure-roman-women-sandals-girls-platform-sandals</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/H6cc93aa27d2e41ebab63cd554fd2e1b0S.webp?v=1720976265</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450769645832</g:id>
      <g:title>Roma Tote</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience timeless elegance with our Premium Leather dbag. Designed with a simple yet incredibly sophisticated style, this bag is the epitome of class. Its ideal size makes it the perfect accessory to complement any outfit, while the spacious interior provides ample room to keep all your essentials organized. Featuring a magnetic closure, it combines convenience with refined aesthetics. This handbag is crafted for women of discerning taste who appreciate understated luxury and impeccable design. It’s more than just a bag—it’s a statement of elegance for those who truly know style.

Material: Genuie Leather
Size: 11,71*11,71*4.72inch / 30*30*12cm 


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/leather-tote-bag-large-capacity-womens-bag-2024-new-fashion-commuter-premium-sense-cowhide-shoulder-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_3_e7b61b8b-a605-4e80-8e5c-26a8fb8d402f.png?v=1731599276</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9447932854536</g:id>
      <g:title>Roxan</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing a truly unique shoulder bag crafted from 100% premium leather, offering a luxurious appearance, exquisite texture, and exceptional durability. This 2024 design is so distinct that it’s impossible to go unnoticed. Not only is it incredibly stylish, but it also boasts remarkable ergonomics, ensuring that despite its relatively compact size, it can comfortably hold all your essentials. This bag is the epitome of elegance and practicality, making it an indispensable accessory for the modern fashion-conscious individual.


• Vintage Maillard Design :The bag features a vintage Maillard design, combining classic elegance with modern style, making it a perfect accessory for any outfit.

• Genuine Leather Material :Crafted from genuine leather, this bag offers durability and a luxurious feel, ensuring long-lasting use.
• All-match Shoulder Bag :This versatile all-match shoulder bag can be paired with various outfits, making it an essential accessory for the trendy woman in 2024.

• Portable Pillow Bag :Designed as a portable pillow bag, it provides convenience and style, perfect for commuting or casual outings.
• Crossbody Strap :Equipped with a single crossbody strap, this bag offers flexibility in carrying options, providing both shoulder and crossbody convenience.
 
SIZE: 8.86inch*5.52inch*4.72inch


          </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/vintage-maillard-style-womens-shoulder-bag-2024-trendy-versatile-genuine-leather-crossbody-handbag-pillow-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/23.6_8.png?v=1724948121</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9401602638088</g:id>
      <g:title>Running Mobile Phone Arm Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your running experience with our luxurious Running Mobile Phone Arm Bag. Designed for ease and comfort, this waterproof armband keeps your phone secure and dry while giving you the freedom to listen to your favorite tunes with the head phones exit feature. Stay cool and stylish with the anti-sweat material. Compatible with iPhone and Anroid.
Features:Universal Phone Size: Never leave your phone behind with the secure armband that can hold your phone with a case on.( 4-7inch Cell Phone )Lifestyle design: The discreet, stylish design makes this the perfect phone holder for an active lifestyle.comfortable: The comfortable material hugs your arm like no other armband you've used before.        </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/running-mobile-phone-arm-bag-phone-armband-bag-waterproof-armband-jogging-case-holder-non-slip-sports-pouch-for-iphone-samsung</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S825d64f914054f6597c3c40f6a1e996c8.webp?v=1722517706</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>7.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9372589261064</g:id>
      <g:title>Savage</g:title>
      <g:description>This Men's leather sandals are the ultimate in modern fashion, exuding prestige and unmatched style with every step. Crafted from high-quality leather, combine luxury with functionality, making them the epitome of innovation. Featuring a non-slip sole, they provide safety and stability, while their classy design enhances your elegance and sophisticated look. Perfect for any occasion, these sandals are the ideal choice for the discerning gentleman.
VdaGamas 2024 Collection
SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Occasion: Casual
Outsole Material: RUBBER



SIZE:
We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/men-black-leather-sandals-with-thick-soles-and-no-tie-up-cuffs-trendy-comfortable-open-toe-outdoor-anti-slip-beach-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sacb46a5066424be896169c6ca1dff445u.webp?v=1720362736</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9609901965576</g:id>
      <g:title>Scarfinity Short Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style this winter with a truly unique women’s down jacket, blending high-fashion design with effortless wearability. Featuring a chic matte fabric that exudes understated elegance, this jacket is designed to stand out. Comes with detachable oversized scarf—thick, long, and versatile—allowing you to create multiple sophisticated looks. The slightly cropped length enhances its modern silhouette, making it a perfect companion for urban adventures or elegant evenings. This jacket isn’t just outerwear—it’s a bold fashion statement for the contemporary woman.
Key Features:

Material: White duck down - Cotton




Detachable Oversized Scarf: Ultra-stylish, thick, and long; wear it in multiple ways for a custom look.

Matte Fabric Finish: A rare, elegant texture that adds a luxe touch to any outfit.

Slightly Cropped Length: Perfectly balanced to offer both warmth and a modern silhouette.

High-Fashion Craftsmanship: Superior quality and attention to detail for a premium feel.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/scarfinity-short-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vascodagama-2025-01-11T184922.397.png?v=1736615170</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>199.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9511838843144</g:id>
      <g:title>Sculpted Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>We bring you a puffer jacket that stands out from the rest with its sleek, modern design. Slightly longer than the average, this sleeveless jacket strikes the perfect balance between style and practicality. Instead of a traditional belt, it features a discreet internal elastic waistband, ensuring a snug and flattering fit without compromising on comfort. Its minimalist silhouette and refined details make it a stylish choice for the fashion-forward, offering a unique twist on the classic puffer. Effortlessly chic and unmistakably different..
Material: Cotton-Polyester
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.

B
 
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sculpted-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2_1cf2c960-d54f-423d-9bdc-a8060367e484.png?v=1731674650</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>37.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386373185800</g:id>
      <g:title>Sensuale</g:title>
      <g:description>Get ready to show off! These chic knee-high stockings feature a lace mesh and ruffle design, perfect for adding a touch of kawaii cuteness to any outfit.
SPECIFICATIONS

Material: POLYESTER
Material: SPANDEX
Material: nylon
Obscene Picture: No
Pieces: 2pcs
Hign-concerned Chemical: None
Craft of Weaving: TAT
Thickness: Thin






























</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/lolita-girls-long-socks-women-stockings-sexy-lace-mesh-fishnet-stockings-ruffle-socks-jk-kawaii-cute-knee-socks-stockings-women</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sac73541452e6413496bd46692b540952M.webp?v=1721314183</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>7.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9476848222472</g:id>
      <g:title>Serenity Cardigan</g:title>
      <g:description>Timeless Classic Knit Cardigan
Elevate your wardrobe with this elegantly crafted cardigan, designed for those who appreciate both sophistication and comfort. Made from high-quality, soft-knit fabric, this cardigan offers a perfect balance of warmth and style. Its clean, minimalist design features a tailored fit, refined buttons, and subtle detailing, ensuring a polished and timeless look. Ideal for layering over your favorite shirts or blouses, this versatile piece transitions effortlessly from business meetings to casual evenings. Available in a range of neutral tones, this cardigan is a must-have for anyone seeking a classic yet contemporary wardrobe staple.
Material: Cotton
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.
Please note that the measurements provided in the size chart reflect the dimensions of the garment itself, not the body. When selecting your size, it is essential to measure yourself and leave enough room for comfort (+0.79-1.6inch 2-4cm).
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/serenity-cardigan</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-09-20141109.png?v=1726837297</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9381730779400</g:id>
      <g:title>SF 11</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover Comfort and Style with Our New Solid Closed-Toe Clogs
Introducing our latest addition – the Solid Closed-Toe Clogs, designed to offer unmatched comfort and non-slip support. Perfect for the beach, casual outings, or simply relaxing at home, these clogs are a must-have in every men or woman's wardrobe.
Why You'll Love Our Solid Closed-Toe Clogs:


Non-Slip Support: Engineered with a specialized non-slip sole, these clogs provide superior traction and stability, ensuring you stay steady on your feet in any environment.

Cloud-Like Comfort: Featuring a cushioned footbed that cradles your feet, these clogs make you feel like you're walking on clouds, no matter how long your day lasts.

Versatile Style: The sleek, closed-toe design combines practicality with modern aesthetics, making these clogs perfect for both beach trips and casual outings.

Durable Construction: Made from high-quality, durable materials, these clogs are built to withstand daily wear and tear while maintaining their stylish appearance.

Easy to Wear: Slip them on and off with ease, thanks to their convenient design that doesn't compromise on comfort or support.

Perfect for Every Occasion
Whether you're heading to the beach, running errands, or enjoying a leisurely stroll, our Solid Closed-Toe Clogs are your go-to choice for effortless style and comfort. The closed-toe design ensures your feet stay protected, while the breathable materials keep them cool and comfortable.
Step into Comfort
Elevate your everyday footwear with clogs that offer the perfect blend of functionality and fashion. Experience the difference with our Solid Closed-Toe Clogs and enjoy every step you take.
Shop now and treat your feet to the ultimate in comfort and style!
SPECIFICATIONS
Fashion Element: Platform
Platform Height: 1.2 inch
Heel Type: Flat with
Upper Material: EVA
Outsole Material: PU
Lining Material: none
Heel Height: Med 
With Platforms: Yes


About the choose of size.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/lucyever-summer-outdoor-hole-shoes-for-women-2024-solid-closed-toe-clogs-beach-slippers-woman-eva-non-slip-cloud-slides-female</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Se3d68b1776214033aebb7ec1414cee4dQ.webp?v=1720976240</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>15.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9443549249800</g:id>
      <g:title>SF-79 Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing the latest addition to our 2024 Collection: the stylish and versatile Tote Bags! Designed with a focus on sport and sleek, contemporary style, this nylon shoulder bag is the perfect companion for any occasion. With a spacious interior, it's ideal for all your essentials, whether you're heading to the gym, the office, or a weekend getaway. Plus, it's 100% waterproof and machine washable, making it as practical as it is chic. Elevate your everyday look with this must-have accessory—order yours today and experience the perfect blend of modern design and functionality!
SPECIFICATIONS


Main Material: nylon


Lining Material: POLYESTER


Style: Japan Style


Decoration: Criss-Cross


Gender: Unisex


Closure Type: zipper


Exterior: none

SIZE: 13.8* 13.4*7.1inch 

Size：35*34*18cm




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/versatile-ins-hot-style-casual-tote-bags-functional-package-high-capacity-nylon-shoulder-bag-handbag-valise-sf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/AUTUMN_COLLECTION_18.png?v=1728570777</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>23.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9476680122632</g:id>
      <g:title>Short sleeve Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace the season with this uniquely designed women's fall blouse, featuring an ultra-modern aesthetic that stands out in any wardrobe. Crafted with wide 3/4 sleeves, this piece brings both comfort and style, perfect for layering or wearing on its own. The loose, relaxed fit allows for effortless movement, making it ideal for both casual outings and chic occasions. Elevate your autumn look with this statement piece that combines contemporary fashion with everyday wearability.
Material: Nylon - Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/short-sleeve-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_74_0aab9b1a-58a7-479e-a1f2-5e06ab7d6bc3.png?v=1738609965</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>31.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585217896712</g:id>
      <g:title>Sienna Oversized Knit</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace effortless comfort with our relaxed-fit wool turtleneck sweater. Perfectly crafted for chilly days, this sweater combines classic style with modern ease. The soft turtleneck provides extra warmth, while the relaxed silhouette drapes beautifully for a flattering and cozy fit.
Made from high-quality wool, it’s lightweight yet insulating, making it an ideal choice for layering or wearing solo. Whether paired with tailored pants for a polished look or jeans for casual outings, this versatile piece is designed to elevate your wardrobe with timeless elegance.

Material: Wool

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sienna-oversized-knit</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_65.png?v=1738610456</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>59.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9554784583944</g:id>
      <g:title>Sierra Belted Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay cozy and chic this winter with this long, fitted down coat, a perfect blend of warmth and modern elegance. Crafted with premium down filling, it provides exceptional insulation while maintaining a sleek, streamlined silhouette. Featuring a unique double-layered collar and a functional hood, this coat offers added protection against the elements. The adjustable waist tie enhances your figure, adding a touch of sophistication to its practical design. Ideal for both urban adventures and winter escapes, this coat is a must-have for anyone seeking comfort and style in the coldest weather.

Material: Cotton-Duck down-Polyester



</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sierra-belted-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_75_731ca056-700b-443f-8978-a2be972aab21.png?v=1738610824</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585588404488</g:id>
      <g:title>Silhouette Luxe Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>Effortlessly elegant and endlessly flattering. This women’s dress features an elastic waist designed to enhance your silhouette and create a slimming effect. Made from premium-quality wool, it feels luxuriously soft against the skin, offering unparalleled comfort. Perfect for any occasion, this timeless piece combines warmth, style, and functionality, making it a must-have for women who value both sophistication and ease.

Material: 100% Merino Wool

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/silhouette-luxe-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_71.png?v=1734292333</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>89.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375319818504</g:id>
      <g:title>Sinaloa</g:title>
      <g:description>Wow! That's the expression when someone sees this piece of art for the first time. A blend of innovation, creativity, and comfort, we proudly introduce our latest and finest shoe: Sinaloa. Named after the  vibrant City of our neighbor Country.
VdaGama Exclousive 2024 Collection.

SPECIFICATIONS
Brand Name: VdaGama
Upper Material: microfiber
Toe Shape: round toe
With Platforms: Yes
Heel Type: Square heel
Fashion Element: Platform
Outsole Material: RUBBER
is_handmade: Yes
Insole Material: PU
Fit: Fits smaller than usual. Please check this store's sizing info
Lining Material: PU
Closure Type: hook &amp; loop
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2024-black-square-heels-round-toe-platform-mary-janes-shoes-women-pumps-spring-summer-lolita-hook-loop-leisure-footwear</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_33.png?v=1721210594</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9376446972168</g:id>
      <g:title>Sinaloa Modesto</g:title>
      <g:description>Step up your style game withthe latest arrivals from the Sinaloas Collection!
Featuring a trendy platform design and soft leather for ultimate comfort, you'll be making a statement wherever you go. Don't miss out on this hot, new addition to your wardrobe!
VdaGama 2024 Collection.

SIZE
We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.

 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2023-new-jk-big-head-shoes-soft-girl-little-leather-shoes-dull-black-lolita-style-thick-bottom-sponge-cake-mary-jane-for-women</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S84511848d5ad47e185a5ae614f0fde976.webp?v=1720706545</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9376164905224</g:id>
      <g:title>Sinaloa Platfore</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing the latest in chic footwear - our Shallow Mouth Round Toe Shoes!, these unique and stylish shoes are sure to turn heads. With a cozy fur lining and slip-on design, they offer both comfort and fashion in one. Don't miss out on this one-of-a-kind addition to your shoe collection. Sinaloa Serie.
VdaGamas 2024 Collection

SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: PU
Toe Shape: round toe
Season: Summer/Spring/Autumn
Occasion: Casual
Closure Type: hook &amp; loop
Outsole Material: RUBBER
Insole Material: PU
Lining Material: PU
SIZE
We encourage customers who have doubts or are on the borderline to choose the next size up.










</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/shallow-mouth-round-toe-shoes-on-heels-loafers-with-fur-casual-female-sneakers-2023-fashion-womens-clogs-platform-new-slip-on-m</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_52.png?v=1721215399</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>39.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9548384305416</g:id>
      <g:title>Sleek Knit Turtleneck</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your layering game with this chic cropped pullover sweater. Perfect for wearing over a shirt or tee, it adds warmth and style without the bulk. This sweater’s cozy knit and shorter length make it a versatile piece that’s easy to pair with blouses, high-waisted jeans, or skirts. Its relaxed fit offers comfort and a modern silhouette, while the timeless design and soft fabric make it an essential for any wardrobe. Whether you're dressing up for work or going casual, this pullover adds a sophisticated finishing touch to your outfit.
Material: Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sleek-knit-turtleneck</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/47_f233b3ea-6929-4509-9456-5322b95d8b61.png?v=1731247891</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9590710894856</g:id>
      <g:title>SnowGlow Wrap</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay warm and stylish with our unique Puffer-Style Hat-Scarf Combo. Designed for ultimate winter protection, this chic accessory seamlessly combines a cozy hat and an integrated scarf. Its innovative design keeps your head, ears, neck, and chest shielded from the cold, ensuring you stay comfortable and elegant even in the harshest weather. Crafted with a modern puffer style, it’s lightweight yet incredibly insulating—perfect for everyday wear or outdoor adventures. Elevate your winter wardrobe with this must-have, versatile accessory that redefines functional fashion.
Material: Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/snowglow-wrap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_cc3f3f26-53eb-47ca-8845-6993ee5b4d3a.png?v=1734544698</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>12.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9590555312392</g:id>
      <g:title>SnugEdge Shawl</g:title>
      <g:description>Stay stylish and warm with this unique women’s woolen scarf-sleeve accessory. Designed like a sleeveless turtleneck that extends to the chest, this chic piece redefines versatility. Its irregular design, complete with a side slit, adds a modern edge to any outfit. Perfect for layering over a coat or wearing solo, it brings both warmth and extra flair to your look. Whether you're heading out for a cozy winter stroll or dressing up for a night out, this fashion-forward piece is a must-have for elevating your cold-weather wardrobe.

Material: 100% Wool
Size: OneSize

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/snugedge-shawl</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_51_b90fcccf-57ad-428b-bda5-afa7d7e11889.png?v=1734532284</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>18.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9586380505352</g:id>
      <g:title>Sofina Relaxed Cashmere Midi</g:title>
      <g:description>The Ultimate Cashmere Dress – Effortless Elegance in Every Thread"Do you believe in the power of understated luxury? Are you looking for a wardrobe essential that feels as good as it looks? Meet the Cashmere Dress, your new go-to piece for every occasion.
Crafted from the finest pure cashmere &amp; wool, this dress is a testament to effortless sophistication. With its ultra-soft, buttery texture that feels like a second skin, it offers unmatched comfort and style. Designed with a relaxed fit, it effortlessly flatters all body types while ensuring complete freedom of movement.
Whether you're dressing up for a dinner party, running errands, or enjoying a cozy evening at home, this versatile dress seamlessly adapts to your day. Its minimalist elegance makes it perfect for layering with accessories or wearing as a standalone statement.
Features:

Made from premium cashmere for ultimate softness and luxury
Relaxed silhouette for a stylish yet comfortable fit
Versatile design, ideal for both casual and formal settings

Material: Cashmere 10% - Wool 90%

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sofina-relaxed-cashmere-midi</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_85.png?v=1736690293</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>119.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9574746882312</g:id>
      <g:title>Soft Glam Crop</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with our Glam Jacket, a chic and cozy addition to your wardrobe. Designed with a lightweight, short-cut silhouette, this jacket perfectly blends contemporary fashion with plush comfort. Ideal for layering during cooler days, its soft faux fur texture adds a touch of luxury to any outfit. Pair it effortlessly with jeans for a casual look or a dress for a night out.
Key Features:

Lightweight and warm
Modern cropped design

Perfect for day-to-night styling
Material: Polyester

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/soft-glam-crop</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGamaGouna.jpg?v=1733248495</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>10076935520520</g:id>
      <g:title>Solea Linen-Look Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your spring wardrobe with this ultra-modern linen-style jacket crafted from premium Ramie fabric – a luxurious, breathable material known for its cool, lightweight feel and exceptional durability. This collarless piece blends effortless sophistication with a relaxed silhouette, offering a timeless balance of class and sportiness. Its refined texture and airy design make it perfect for warm-weather days when you want to look polished yet feel comfortable. Whether you're dressing up or down, this jacket delivers understated elegance with a contemporary edge.
Key Features:

High-quality Ramie fabric – naturally cool, breathable, and strong
Collarless, relaxed fit for a modern, versatile look
Perfect blend of classy and sporty style

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/solea-linen-look-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Outer_fabric_100_polyester_Lining_fabric_100_polyester_Inner_lining_100_polyester_Filling_90_white_duck_down_10_feather_4o_a3b358eb-636c-4e41-ade0-d198e183c141.png?v=1742403310</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450772791560</g:id>
      <g:title>Sophia Grandeur</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with the JIOMAY Fashion Tote Bag. This luxurious designer handbag is made of high-quality PU leather, featuring a unique round amber acrylic handle for a touch of elegance. With enough space for all your essentials, this bag is perfect for both everyday use and special occasions. Elevate your fashion game with Sophia Grandeur !


Size: Length: 37cm (14.57in) Thickness: 6cm (2.36in) Height: 11.5cm (4.53in)Fabric: PUColor: White, Black







Product details display







</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/jiomay-fashion-tote-bag-luxury-designer-handbags-high-quality-pu-leather-cloud-bag-special-round-amber-acrylic-handle-purse</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/29_8cac9d14-f602-4151-bd72-da099aeca9b9.png?v=1725369189</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450792616200</g:id>
      <g:title>Sorel Clasic</g:title>
      <g:description>Upgrade your style with this Crossbody Bag! With its fashion-forward design, this bag is just perfectl. The large capacity will accommodate all your essentials, making it convenient for on-the-go use. Ergonomic and versatile, this bag is a must-have for any fashionista.
SIZE: 9.45*7.89*2.55inch / 24*20*6.5cm
MATERIAL: PU LEATHEAR







c
























</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/pu-leather-fashion-design-crossbody-bags-for-women-summer-travel-shoulder-bags-large-capacity-handbags-and-purse-armpit-hobo-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/3_23e12097-b0af-455f-95cd-b5be51f81d25.webp?v=1726256211</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445294801160</g:id>
      <g:title>Southan</g:title>
      <g:description>Give your outfit a touch of class with the Cobbler Legend 2024 shoulder bag. Made from genuine premium leather, this bag is both luxurious and durable. Stay organized with its multiple pockets, perfect for everyday use. Elevate your style with this soft, retro-inspired shoulder messenger bag!

SIZE: 11.41*7.48*4.33inch

Material: Genuie Leather





 





Genuine leather






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/cobbler-legend-2023-new-genuine-leather-handbag-womens-shoulder-messenger-bags-ladies-purse-designer-luxury-female-soft-retro</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/27_7d15e1ea-3c5a-4226-96ed-33d95de78a9d.png?v=1725364979</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>60.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9580793987336</g:id>
      <g:title>Sovereign Matte Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Redefine winter sophistication with this premium women’s coat, designed for those who appreciate elegance and distinction. Made from a unique matte "gauffré" fabric, its textured finish creates a refined and contemporary look that effortlessly stands out.
The asymmetrical button closure with oversized buttons and a chic high collar adds a touch of modern artistry to this timeless piece. Perfectly tailored to flatter the silhouette, this coat is a testament to exceptional craftsmanship and luxurious quality.
Versatile yet striking, it seamlessly complements both casual and formal outfits, making it an essential addition to the wardrobe of accomplished, stylish women. For those who demand nothing but the finest, this coat is more than an outerwear piece—it’s a statement of class and success.


Material: 70% Cotton, 30% Spandex
Fill in: 90+ White duck down

Colors: Apricot, Light Coffee, Black


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sovereign-matte-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vdagama_11_a531dc1f-8131-44f5-9e5f-4430284fbb5f.png?v=1738774749</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9396469596424</g:id>
      <g:title>Stella</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our new EVA Slippers, designed with a unique and stylish flair that effortlessly combines fashion and comfort. Featuring a sole as soft as a pillow, these slippers will cradle your feet in unparalleled comfort. Perfect for both casual wear and lounging around the house, our EVA Slippers offer a luxurious upgrade for your everyday footwear. Experience the perfect blend of style and comfort with our exquisitely designed EVA Slippers.
Material: Eva
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/eva-slippers-womens-new-fashion-slippers-outside-flat-with-casual-home-slipper-soft-sole-comfortable-sandals-women-ladies-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-28T141219.644.png?v=1722165223</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>14.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445276451080</g:id>
      <g:title>Stormraven</g:title>
      <g:description>This England Style Oversize Tote Bag is anything but ordinary! Stand out from the crowd with its unique design. With multiple pockets and large capacity, this luxury designer handbag is both functional and fashionable. Escape from the standard and make a statement with this 2024 new addition.
SPECIFICATIONS
Lining Material: Synthetic Leather
Shape: Casual Tote
Main Material: PU
Size: 21.65 inches*12.99 inches*4.72 inches / 55cm*33cm*12cm




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/england-style-oversize-tote-bags-for-women-luxury-designer-handbag-purse-2024-new-in-pu-multiple-pockets-large-capacity-shoulder</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2_0bb44ab4-c97f-4fd2-93d8-74c5e3b402e6.png?v=1724773312</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9585491968264</g:id>
      <g:title>Strata Chill Pullover</g:title>
      <g:description>Redefine your wardrobe with effortless sophistication. This loose, long turtleneck sweater stands out with its unique and artistic cutouts, blending contemporary design with everyday wearability. Its relaxed silhouette ensures maximum comfort, while the high neckline exudes modern elegance. Whether layered or worn as a statement piece, this versatile sweater is perfect for women who love fashion-forward, standout styles.

Material: Acrylic
Size: One Size fits all


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/strata-chill-pullover</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/67.png?v=1733938791</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>26.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9593467601160</g:id>
      <g:title>StreetEase Tracksuit</g:title>
      <g:description>"Effortless Style Meets Everyday Comfort." This stylish tracksuit set combines a sporty look with modern design elements. The hoodie features oversized front pockets for functionality and flair, while the matching jogger pants offer a sleek yet relaxed fit, perfect for any activity. Made with high-quality, soft fabric, this set is ideal for workouts, casual outings, or lounging in style. Whether you're on the go or keeping it cozy, this tracksuit ensures you look effortlessly chic while staying comfortable.

Material: Spandex-Polyester


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/streetease-tracksuit</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vascodagama_70.png?v=1734881955</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9514284876040</g:id>
      <g:title>Styla Mid-Length Waistcoat</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our 2024 New Women's Vest, a standout addition to your autumn and winter wardrobe. This sleeveless jacket combines style and practicality, featuring a unique fabric texture reminiscent of piqué that adds an elegant touch to your look. Its mid-length design offers a flattering, loose fit, while the added hood provides extra warmth and a chic, laid-back vibe. This vest also stands out with its double flap pockets—one vertical with a button closure and one horizontal—adding both a unique design element and exceptional practicality. This thoughtful detail enhances its functionality, making it perfect for carrying essentials while maintaining a sleek, stylish appearance. Perfect for layering over your favorite outfits, this vest gives you both comfort and style, making it an essential piece for the colder seasons. Its relaxed silhouette enhances your look effortlessly, offering a stylish twist to casual outerwear.
Main Material: Polyester
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/styla-mid-length-waistcoat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_49.png?v=1731170382</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370207224072</g:id>
      <g:title>Sueno Sandal</g:title>
      <g:description>Step into a world of comfort.These clogs will make you feel like you're walking on clouds. Perfect for a day at the beach or a casual stroll, these sandals offer unparalleled comfort and style. 

SPECIFICATIONS
Sandal Type: clogs
Style: Concise
Fashion Element: Platform
Outsole Material: EVA
Lining Material: none
Heel Height: Med (1.2-1.9 inch)
Upper Material: EVA
Insole Material: EVA
Note:Please buy according to the foot length,fat feet suggest buying a big size！Mark Size 40-41(Sole label）：Fit "39-40" EUR Size =(suitable for 24.5cm-25.0cm foot)Mark Size 42-43(Sole label）：Fit "41-42" EUR Size =(suitable for 25.5cm-26.0cm foot)Mark Size 44-45(Sole label）：Fit "43-44" EUR Size =(suitable for 26.5cm-27.0cm foot)
















</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/qyckaby-summer-quality-sandals-male-slippers-casual-clogs-shoes-garden-sandals-mens-beach-slippers-outdoor-sneakers-diy-cartoon</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_31.png?v=1721160305</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>25.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375131336968</g:id>
      <g:title>Suez</g:title>
      <g:description>Step Ahead or Fall Behind. Embrace the Future with Every Step
Introducing Kioto, a design that breaks boundaries not only in style but also in comfort and usability. Experience it yourself and you'll get it!

Material: Eva


SIZE

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-boken-shoes-slippers-garden-flat-sandals-platform-sandals-summer-sandals-2024-sneakers-outdoor-flip-flops-home-clogs</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024-07-11T201618.318.png?v=1720718198</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>22.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445287395592</g:id>
      <g:title>Suez</g:title>
      <g:description>Bit by bit, the bag is filled—much like this handcrafted leather masterpiece, meticulously stitched together piece by piece. Though it took a little extra time, the result is nothing short of exceptional. This bag boasts a unique design, top-tier quality, and a spacious interior with multiple large compartments, perfectly balancing style and functionality. It stands as a testament to the art of fine craftsmanship, offering elegance and practicality for those who value attention to detail.
Dimentions: 17.7inch*9,44inch*6.7inch / 45*14*24 cm(L*W*H)
Main Materials: Genuine leather, Natural first layer cowhide, Real fur
Lining: Cotton
Vasco da Gama Collection 2024






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/organizers-designers-handmade-genuine-leather-woven-womens-tote-bag-weekend-outdoor-luxury-real-cowhide-large-capacity-handbags</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/23.6_9.png?v=1724952784</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>239.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386372432136</g:id>
      <g:title>Summer Thin Socks Stockings</g:title>
      <g:description>Japanese inspired striped knee socks. Designed for the fashion-forward woman, these lightweight and breathable stockings are a perfect addition to any summer outfit. Their unique hollow out mesh design adds a chic touch while keeping your legs cool and comfortable.
SPECIFICATIONS
Material: COTTON
Material: POLYESTER
Material: SPANDEX
Pieces: 2pcs
Hign-concerned Chemical: None
Thickness: Thin
Model Number: Stockings
Pattern Type: Striped


 

                   


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/summer-thin-women-long-socks-stockings-hollow-out-mesh-breathable-knee-socks-japanese-style-striped-girls-knee-socks-stockings</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S9ec7945d9f184b19a24f70fc129a5fd7V.webp?v=1721314130</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>7.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9514360373512</g:id>
      <g:title>Suno Luxe Down Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>



Introducing an exceptionally unique women's white duck down vest, designed to captivate attention with its distinctive draped silhouette and elegant fastening. This piece stands out for its refined, chic aesthetic, offering a sophisticated twist on the classic puffer style. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, the vest boasts impeccable tailoring and superior quality materials, ensuring both comfort and luxury. Its remarkable design and high-end construction make it a statement piece, perfect for those seeking a more formal, polished look that is sure to turn heads wherever you go.

Material: Fill in: 90% white duck down 10% Feather
Fabric: 100% Polyester 
Size: One Size


 




</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/velora-luxe-down-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_54.png?v=1731172054</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9386396614920</g:id>
      <g:title>Svegliati adesso</g:title>
      <g:description>Indulge in luxury! Made of signature leather, these one of a kind sandals are designed to make a statement. The thick bottom flat heel and round open toe add a touch of elegance to any outfit, makes it the perfect choice for any woman who knows how to choose..

SPECIFICATIONS
Upper Material: GENUINE LEATHER
Upper-Genuine Leather Type: Cow Leather
Closure Type: buckle strap
Outsole Material: RUBBER
Insole Material: Full Grain Leather
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Lining Material: GENUINE LEATHER






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/black-genuine-leather-thick-bottom-flat-heel-sandals-2023-summer-new-platform-hollow-women-sandals-silk-round-open-toe-shoes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_58_20ab59ad-5401-48fd-89de-3d5fb08f8c31.png?v=1721317446</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>83.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9612672139528</g:id>
      <g:title>Tailored Allure Blazer Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your style with this sophisticated blazer dress designed for bold, confident women. This longline blazer transforms into a chic dress, featuring a unique front closure that adds a modern twist to a timeless silhouette. The sleek tailoring is enhanced by strategically placed cutouts, offering an edgy yet elegant look.

Material: Polyester fiber 75% - Viscose 25%


 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/tailored-allure-blazer-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama-2025-01-13T215038.136.png?v=1736798241</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9378629419272</g:id>
      <g:title>Thai Slipper</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our King of Comfort - a cloud-like experience for your feet! Super soft and thick soles provide ultimate comfort while walking, without a single sound. Perfect for both men and women, these anti-slip, non-slip slippers are a must-have for every home.
Material: EVA
🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.








</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/fashion-women-summer-soft-slippers-thick-platform-bathroom-home-men-indoor-non-slip-anti-slip-female-cloud-cushion-slides</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_38.png?v=1721158136</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>14.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9593505349896</g:id>
      <g:title>The Chic Tie Dress</g:title>
      <g:description>"Lightweight Elegance for Every Occasion."This stylish dress features a flattering tie-waist design that accentuates your silhouette with effortless charm. Crafted from lightweight, breathable fabric, it’s perfect for all-day comfort. Its versatile style transitions seamlessly from casual daytime outings to more formal occasions, making it an essential addition to any wardrobe. 

Material: Polyester 97% - Spandex 3%

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-chic-tie-dress</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/7_e727c8c8-8290-4168-95bb-6e7ee4f0e445.png?v=1736700933</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9648068657416</g:id>
      <g:title>The Contour Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>A bold statement in contemporary fashion.
Dare to stand out with this short, sleeveless puffer vest, a piece that redefines outerwear with its artistic design and sculptural silhouette. Unlike traditional vests, this masterpiece features intricate stitched detailing, a curved, asymmetrical front closure, and expertly crafted paneling that creates a sleek yet dynamic look.
The unconventional cut and architectural lines make this vest a true work of fashion-forward design. Each stitched detail adds depth and dimension, highlighting the unique craftsmanship that sets it apart. The asymmetrical button closure follows a fluid, curved path, enhancing the edgy yet sophisticated aesthetic.
Size: One Size ( Consult the Size Chart )
Material Composition:


Outer Fabric: 100% Polyester

Lining Fabric: 100% Cotton

Filling: 100% Polyester

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-contour-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_42_dacdb103-7a8b-48e7-8149-7140c37a2a5c.png?v=1738514586</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587911491848</g:id>
      <g:title>The Empress Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Crafted from a harmonious blend of high-quality fabrics, this lightweight coat offers a striking visual appeal that sets it apart from the ordinary. Its thoughtful design—featuring a tie-waist belt, intricate details, and a statement hood—combines practicality with effortless elegance. Perfect for transitional weather, it provides comfort without unnecessary bulk, making it ideal for layering. Whether you're strolling through the city or attending a special event, this refined and stylish design ensures you'll stand out with understated sophistication.

Material:
Fabric: Polyester - Cotton
Fill in: White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-empress-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_26_e5f4d6c2-70f4-41fa-b7c6-eb69bca93dd3.png?v=1734304712</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>145.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587818660104</g:id>
      <g:title>The Glacier Flow Skirt</g:title>
      <g:description>Redefining winter elegance, this skirt is a masterpiece of innovative design, offering a fresh and unique take on cold-weather fashion. Τhis high-waisted, long down skirt is designed to keep you exceptionally warm while exuding sophistication, this statement piece features a unique silhouette that effortlessly enhances your figure. The innovative design allows for seamless layering over almost any outfit, making it a versatile addition to your winter wardrobe. Whether paired with a cozy knit sweater, a sleek turtleneck, or even a fitted jacket, this skirt transforms any look with its modern, chic appeal. Its waist-cinching design adds structure, while the exceptional warmth ensures comfort during even the chilliest days. A true standout for women who value style and functionality in one.

Material:
Fiber: Polyesteric 
Fill in: White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-glacier-flow-skirt</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_5_8ac7b857-6ae3-4c8d-bdfc-12946e55d6f1.png?v=1734289057</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>129.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9582315012360</g:id>
      <g:title>The Kensington Plaid Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Wrap yourself in unparalleled warmth and timeless style with this premium down-filled women's coat. Designed for both comfort and sophistication, this long everyday coat transitions effortlessly to more formal settings. Featuring chic plaid details on the cuff edges and collar, it adds a touch of classic elegance to its modern design. The high, buttoned collar offers extra protection against chilly winds while elevating the overall look. Perfect for cold winter days, this coat is a must-have for the modern woman who values functionality and refined style.
Features:


Exceptional Warmth: Insulated with high-quality down for maximum comfort in cold weather.

Elegant Plaid Accents: Subtle yet stylish plaid details on the cuffs and collar.

Functional Design: High collar that buttons up for added warmth and versatility.

Versatile Length: Long silhouette that pairs beautifully with casual and formal outfits.

Material: Polyester - White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-kensington-plaid-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_11_19741a68-3cad-47bd-86e7-33a87d8380e4.png?v=1733749653</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>159.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9648115319048</g:id>
      <g:title>The Loft Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>Timeless warmth, effortless style.
This sleeveless down puffer vest is designed for those who seek maximum warmth without compromising on style. Crafted with premium down filling, it offers exceptional insulation, making it an essential piece for colder days.
The high collar provides extra protection against chilly winds, while its thick, padded structure ensures unbeatable comfort and coziness. Featuring a classic, minimalist design, this vest is effortlessly versatile—perfect for layering over sweaters, hoodies, or even lightweight tops for transitional weather.

Material: White duck down - Polyester

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-loft-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_49_eee17a3c-fd28-4e90-a020-bdbcdb28c9f6.png?v=1738519221</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9647998599432</g:id>
      <g:title>The Luxe Oversized Shirt-Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Designed for the modern woman who values both style and ease, this oversized shirt-coat dress is the perfect blend of relaxed fit and refined elegance. Crafted from high-quality breathable cotton, it drapes beautifully while offering a structured yet effortless look.
Its long, flowing silhouette exudes confidence, while the subtle tapering at the sleeves adds a touch of tailored sophistication, balancing the oversized design with a hint of definition. Versatile and timeless, this piece can be worn as a statement coat, a chic dress, or a stylish layering essential—perfect for any occasion.

Material: Cotton 70% - Polyester fiber 30%
Size: One Size ( Consult the Size Chart )

✔ Premium Cotton Fabric – Soft, breathable, and perfect for all-day wear✔ Oversized Fit – Designed for a relaxed yet stylish drape✔ Elegant Tapered Sleeves – Subtle detailing for a sophisticated touch✔ Versatile Design – Wear it as a coat, dress, or layering piece✔ Timeless &amp; Chic – A wardrobe essential for effortless elegance

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-luxe-oversized-shirt-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_35.png?v=1738777657</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>57.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533410541832</g:id>
      <g:title>The Pinnacle Puffer</g:title>
      <g:description>A pinnacle of design innovation, this coat redefines modern outerwear with bold lines and a striking silhouette. Crafted as a true masterpiece, it combines avant-garde asymmetry with the warmth and comfort of premium down filling. The high collar and elongated cut add both sophistication and exceptional warmth. But what truly sets this coat apart is its unique versatility—it can be worn upside down, transforming its shape and look, offering endless styling possibilities. This isn’t just a coat; it’s a statement of luxury and distinction, a wardrobe essential for those who dare to stand out with elegance and creativity.

Material: Acetate - Whit duck down
Size: One size - Fits all

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-pinnacle-puffer</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_65_458d4bcf-b965-4f74-a19f-646d9846e2d7.png?v=1735424215</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>139.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9647932801288</g:id>
      <g:title>The Polka Breeze Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>This lightweight, oversized, and elegantly long windproof coat is a celebration of retro-inspired fashion with a modern twist. Designed for women who love timeless elegance, its flowy silhouette drapes beautifully, offering both comfort and sophistication.
Crafted from breathable, wind-resistant fabric, it provides just the right amount of coverage for breezy days while maintaining a relaxed, airy feel. The playful polka dot pattern adds a touch of vintage glamour, making it a standout piece that pairs effortlessly with both casual and dressy looks.

Material: Acrylic
Size: One Size ( Consult the size chart )

✔ Ultra-lightweight &amp; Windproof – Ideal for transitional weather✔ Oversized Fit – Effortless drape for a relaxed, comfortable feel✔ Classic Polka Dot Design – A timeless yet playful touch✔ Longline Silhouette – Elegance meets versatility✔ Effortless Layering – Perfect for styling over any outfit

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-polka-breeze-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_33_a0a66fc5-200f-4e2c-a28e-a16f9829d56d.png?v=1738504079</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>37.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9647840231688</g:id>
      <g:title>The Retro Breeze Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Effortless style meets everyday functionality with this lightweight, relaxed-fit windproof coat. Designed for modern women who appreciate classic aesthetics, this long, fabric overcoat offers a perfect blend of retro charm and contemporary comfort.
With its flowing silhouette, wide statement pockets, and a minimalist yet elegant structure, this coat is an ideal layering piece for transitional weather. Crafted from breathable, wind-resistant fabric, it provides just the right amount of protection without feeling heavy. The loose fit allows for effortless movement, while the refined details evoke a sense of vintage sophistication.

Material: Acrylic-Polyester
Size: One Size ( Consult the size chart )

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-retro-breeze-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_20_b6a30048-655e-4798-b64c-e24ef76723f3.png?v=1738496953</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9589117387016</g:id>
      <g:title>The Seraphine</g:title>
      <g:description>True Masterpiece – the epitome of design and craftsmanship. This long women's coat redefines elegance with an extraordinary focus on detail, featuring intricate button accents at the back that make it truly one of a kind. Crafted from wool &amp; pure cashmere, it delivers an unparalleled sense of luxury—soft to the touch, effortlessly warm, and exquisitely refined.
Every element of this coat speaks to timeless sophistication: from its flowing silhouette that flatters every movement to the meticulously tailored finish that ensures perfection in every stitch. This Signature design transcends trends, offering an exclusive statement piece for women who value artistry, comfort, and individuality.

Material:
Cashmere 10%
Wool 90%

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-seraphine</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_29.png?v=1734381421</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9587852017928</g:id>
      <g:title>The Vanguard Hybrid Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>This signature hybrid dress-coat is a vision from the future, brought to life for the modern woman seeking warmth, style, and innovation.”
Combining the best of a dress and a puffer coat, this sleeveless masterpiece is designed to offer both elegance and practicality. The luxurious down-filled construction provides exceptional warmth, while its unique features—velcro strap shoulders, side zippers, and easy-to-open clip closures—make it as effortless to wear as a jacket. Whether styled as a standalone dress with a blouse or shirt underneath, or layered over other outfits for added cold-weather protection, this versatile piece redefines winter fashion. Its sleek silhouette and functional design ensure you stay chic and cozy, no matter how low the temperature drops.

Material:
Fabric: 100% Premium Polyester
Fill in: White duck down

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/the-vanguard-hybrid-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/VascodaGama_7_82a90f8f-01ee-4ca8-8c9a-0120a7262a73.png?v=1734294187</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>149.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9590735503624</g:id>
      <g:title>ThermaStyle Beanie</g:title>
      <g:description>Embrace the cold in style with our Puffer-Style Hat—a cozy and fashionable solution for winter days. Designed to provide exceptional warmth, this lightweight yet highly insulating hat shields your head and ears from the chill. With its sleek, modern puffer design, it’s the perfect blend of comfort and sophistication, making it an essential accessory for any winter outfit. Whether you’re exploring the
Material: Polyester
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/thermastyle-beanie</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_58_9ca46842-8128-4353-ba75-9fb8faedad0f.png?v=1734546217</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>13.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9534000791816</g:id>
      <g:title>Tuscany Down Coat</g:title>
      <g:description>Discover the essence of elegance with this luxurious women's down coat, crafted to make a statement at every occasion. Featuring a detachable buttoned scarf collar, this long, refined coat brings together sophistication and a timeless, stylish edge. Perfect for those who appreciate unique, high-quality pieces, this coat embodies a classic yet modern appeal.

Materials: Polyester - White duck down

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/tuscany-down-coat</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_50_68002993-8f1f-40b0-806b-eba789fd29c6.png?v=1735423838</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>169.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9514370531592</g:id>
      <g:title>Urban Breeze Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing the Latest in Fashion – Our New Arrival Sleeveless Women's Jacket!
This ultra-modern and stylish sleeveless jacket is the freshest addition to our collection, embodying the latest trends straight from the fashion world. Designed with a relaxed, loose fit, it offers a casual, sporty vibe that’s perfect for everyday wear. The jacket is incredibly lightweight and comfortable, making it the ideal choice for those who value both style and ease.

Detachable hood

Material: Nylon-Polyester

The sizes for this product are indicative and correspond to the model featured in the photos. The model is 66.53inch tall and weighs 143lbs. In the images, she is wearing a size X-Large. Please refer to this information as a guide when selecting the appropriate size for yourself.

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/urban-breeze-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_55.png?v=1731172487</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9533581230344</g:id>
      <g:title>Urban Icon Hooded Leather Jacket</g:title>
      <g:description>Make a bold statement with this ultra-stylish oversized leather jacket, crafted to exude confidence and contemporary edge. With a mid-length cut and a sleek hood, this jacket combines modern street style with timeless elegance. Perfectly suited for both casual and dressed-up looks, it’s the ultimate layering piece that brings a touch of chic attitude to any outfit. This jacket isn’t just a look—it’s an experience in effortless style and comfort.
Materials: Lambskin - White duck down

 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/urban-icon-hooded-leather-jacket</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/WinterCollection_9.png?v=1730194521</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>190.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9513603268872</g:id>
      <g:title>Urban Womans Cap</g:title>
      <g:description>This cap perfectly balances style and comfort, making it the ultimate accessory for any casual look. Designed with a minimalist yet chic vibe, it seamlessly complements every outfit, from laid-back weekend wear to more polished, everyday ensembles. Crafted with care, its versatile design ensures that it’s a go-to piece for any occasion, adding a subtle touch of cool to your style.
Material: Polyester
Size: One Size, adjustable.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/urban-womans-cap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_62.png?v=1731242542</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>13.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9549171360008</g:id>
      <g:title>Vasco Winter Chic</g:title>
      <g:description>We told you so: at Vasco da Gama, we don’t follow trends; we set them. Introducing our exquisite Paffer-style handbag, a versatile winter statement piece that seamlessly transitions from shoulder to hand with its removable strap. Crafted for the woman who values uniqueness, this bag combines bold design with winter-ready materials. Perfect for any occasion, it’s more than an accessory—it’s an expression of style and elegance. Make a statement this season with a bag that’s truly one-of-a-kind.

Material: Polyester
Dimensions: 12.99*1.96*17.7inch

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/vasco-winter-chic</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/vasco_da_gama_74.png?v=1735317976</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9532000338184</g:id>
      <g:title>Velora Fur Trimmed Vest</g:title>
      <g:description>Extraordinary! That’s the word that comes to mind when someone first lays eyes on this piece of art. This luxurious long women’s coat is a masterpiece of elegance and warmth, featuring a sumptuous fur-lined hood that exudes sophistication. Designed with exquisite details, like chic side buttons and a waist-cinching drawstring, it perfectly balances style and functionality. Every detail, from the tailored silhouette to the refined accents, makes this coat stand out, ensuring you stay cozy and stylish through the coldest days. A truly timeless addition to any wardrobe!

Materials: 100%  Polyester - Feather (fill)

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/elegance-fur-trimmed-vest</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Vasco_da_Gama_57_37b40e5e-cede-47b7-b71e-1df82f194695.png?v=1735424004</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>69.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450796286216</g:id>
      <g:title>Velvet Chic bucket</g:title>
      <g:description>



Introducing our groundbreaking 2024 Bucket Tote Bag! Crafted from luxurious faux suede and simulated genuine leather, this designer handbag sets a new standard in sophistication and style. With an exceptionally spacious interior and a secure exterior pocket for your phone, you'll never miss a call or have to search through your bag at the last minute. The versatile shoulder strap makes it perfect for any occasion, while the high-quality materials and exquisite design reflect the finest in contemporary fashion. Elevate your wardrobe this fall with our latest must-have accessory!
* Main material: Faux Suede, lining: synthetic leather*Size: 14.56 inches*11.8 inches*8.26 inches / 37cm*30cm*12cm









</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/faux-suede-bucket-tote-bag-for-women-luxury-designer-handbag-purse-2024-new-in-simulated-genuine-leather-large-capacity-shoulder</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2025_4_2e5d3420-645f-4661-acfe-8ae26028db8d.png?v=1731599274</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9445290246408</g:id>
      <g:title>Velvet Shoulder Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our new in, 2024 Unick design, a luxurious addition to your wardrobe. Handcrafted from premium velvet and woven leather, this shoulder bag is perfect for the discerning fashionista. Complete your look with this exclusive designer clutch bag.


Lining Material: POLYESTER

Material: PU Leather


Decoration: Criss-Cross

Dimensions: 7.28*3.93*2.16inch / 18.5*10*5.5cm 








</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/new-fashion-velvet-bags-women-weaven-handbag-shoulder-crossbody-bag-woven-luxury-leather-brand-designer-clutch-bolsa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/autumn_collection.png?v=1727112468</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>33.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450773479688</g:id>
      <g:title>Venezia</g:title>
      <g:description>



A true gem! Possibly one of the most unique and beloved additions to this year’s collection, this chic accessory needs no introduction. It speaks for itself. With its elegant design and refined charm, this bag is perfect for those who appreciate both style and sophistication. Exceptionally unique and stylish, it's a timeless piece that will add a touch of grace to any outfit.

MATERIALS: LEATHER COWHIDE

SIZE: 11.42*9.5*3.15inch / 29*25*8cm 






</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/sweetbox-2023-womens-bag-luxury-brand-designer-fashion-soft-genuine-leather-crossbody-sling-messenger-small-tote-bag-for-female</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/27.webp?v=1726412512</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>99.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9586414387464</g:id>
      <g:title>VentureWrap</g:title>
      <g:description>Your Go-To Windbreaker with Timeless StyleEffortlessly blending style and practicality, this zip-up windbreaker features a sleek stand-up collar for extra protection against the elements. Lightweight and ultra-convenient, it folds easily to fit into your bag, making it perfect for life on the go. Its versatile design complements nearly any outfit, ensuring you stay chic and comfortable, rain or shine.
Material: Polyster
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/venturewrap</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/90_OFTOTALFILLWEIGHT_10.png?v=1734034015</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>19.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9444312744200</g:id>
      <g:title>VersaStyle Winter Tote Bag</g:title>
      <g:description>Elevate your winter wardrobe with our 2025 Fashion Space Bale Handbag. Designed for both style and practicality, this luxurious tote features multiple pockets to keep your essentials organized with ease. Its casual yet chic design makes it the perfect accessory for any outfit, whether you're dressing up or keeping it relaxed. With a zipper closure and soft feather padding, this bag seamlessly blends fashion and function, making it your go-to for the fall and winter seasons. Effortlessly sophisticated and versatile, it's a must-have addition to your collection.

Material: Nailon-Cotton
Size: 10.63*9.8*5.9inch / 27*25*15cm








</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/2022-fashion-winter-space-bale-handbags-women-cotton-totes-bags-down-feather-padded-lady-shoulder-crossbody-bag-sac-a-main-femme</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/12.svg?v=1731695719</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>49.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9510647202056</g:id>
      <g:title>Vivid Sleek</g:title>
      <g:description>We don't follow fashion, we create it. Introducing our new autumn sleeveless puffer jacket, a unique design that sets you apart from the rest. Featuring distinctive cuts, this piece boasts armholes that sit slightly lower than traditional sleeveless styles, adding a modern twist. The jacket is complemented by a subtly high collar, providing both style and warmth. Elevate your wardrobe with this standout piece that blends functionality and fashion effortlessly.

Material: Polyester

🔍 Before selecting a size, please carefully consult the size chart.


</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/vivid-sleek</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Instagram_46.png?v=1731169597</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.00 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9375107416328</g:id>
      <g:title>VooDoo</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience a fresh take on footwear with the new Voodoo Clogs Shoes! Featuring a unique design and non-slip sole, these unisex sandals offer both comfort and style for men and women. Say goodbye to boring sandals and step into new vibes with Voodoo!
SPECIFICATIONS
VdaGama
Back Counter Type: Back Strap
Fashion Element: light
Fit: Fits smaller than usual. Please check this store's sizing info
Platform Height: 5cm
Hign-concerned Chemical: None
Upper Material: EVA
Insole Material: EVA
Occasion: Casual
Sandal Type: clogs
Outsole Material: EVA
With Platforms: Yes

Important Notice:
1、Our size is manufactore's size, please choose according to 'shoe size' and 'foot length' in the size chart,if your foot is wide or thick, add about 0.01inch to your foot length before choosing.
If your size is 8.5 but your foot is a bit wide or you are on the borderline, choose the next size up.










</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/mo-dou-spring-summer-big-toe-clogs-shoes-for-unisex-thick-sole-outdoor-sandals-for-women-soft-non-slip-slippers-for-men</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/2024_collection_40.png?v=1721210926</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9370197655816</g:id>
      <g:title>Waterproof Shoe Cover</g:title>
      <g:description>Confidence is just preparation in disguise — when you're ready for anything, even the rain can't shake you. To be prepared is one of the most important keys to success, and protecting your shoes from unexpected weather is no exception.
Waterproof Shoe Covers, Made from premium TPE material, these overshoes are designed for long-lasting durability. With a convenient button closure, they are portable and easy to store in your bag, ensuring you're ready for any weather.
Key features:


Non-slip sole for added safety on wet surfaces

Washable for extended use and freshness

Durable TPE material for long-lasting protection

Lightweight and portable, perfect for carrying in your bag

Easy to wear with a button closure for quick, secure fitting
Size Tips : If your shoes are Irregular with Extend Edge or some Big Boots, please take 1 size UP.















NEW STYLES ARE AS BELOW









 </g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/shoe-waterproof-cover-men-women-rain-shoes-new-blue-overshoes-washable-portable-big-open-tpe-shoe-cover-button-durable-galoshes</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/21.webp?v=1728638273</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>9.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450772660488</g:id>
      <g:title>women bag 2023 new PU Bucket Fashion Women Solid Semicircular Shoulder Bags handbag Euro-America style purse phone bag</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONSBrand Name: mdodskeOrigin: Mainland ChinaCN: ZhejiangLining Material: nylonMain Material: PUPlace Of Origin: ZHE JIANG  ProvincePlace Of Origin: ZHE JIANG  ProvinceShape: BucketOccasion: VersatileExterior: Open PocketClosure Type: haspDecoration: noneHardness: SOFTGender: WOMENPattern Type: SolidInterior: No PocketStyle: fashionmaterial quality: pu

Size:width 17cm,high 13cm,thcikness 8cm










</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/women-bag-2023-new-pu-bucket-fashion-women-solid-semicircular-shoulder-bags-handbag-euro-america-style-purse-phone-bag</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sc53c972676734f4e8bbefa7d155bc4e59.webp?v=1725201920</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>17.24 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9376450904328</g:id>
      <g:title>Women's Shoes Platform Round Toe Female Footwear Modis Casual Sneaker Loafers With Fur Clogs Dress 2024 Moccasin Summer Slip-on</g:title>
      <g:description>SPECIFICATIONS
VdaGama
Upper Material: CANVAS
Toe Shape: round toe
Hign-concerned Chemical: None
Season: Spring/Autumn
Occasion: Casual
Closure Type: SLIP-ON
Item Type: flats
Outsole Material: RUBBER
Insole Material: PU
Fit: Fits true to size, take your normal size
Lining Material: PU

</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/womens-shoes-platform-round-toe-female-footwear-modis-casual-sneaker-loafers-with-fur-clogs-dress-2024-moccasin-summer-slip-on</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Se22c2fc2fd4a49dbb9eb2cebf660e844i.webp?v=1720706797</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>20.23 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9401585074440</g:id>
      <g:title>Yoga/Running Woman Shorts</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our versatile and luxurious Yoga Shorts for the modern, active woman. With a 2 in 1 design and anti-sweat technology, these shorts offer maximum comfort and performance during your workouts. The perfect blend of style and functionality, they will elevate your fitness game and keep you looking chic and fresh.
</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/yoga-shorts-women-fitness-top-spandex-neon-elastic-running-workout-short-leggings-for-ladies-gym-sport-shorts-fitness-sportwear</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/Sc04093759bf24ed8aac2b94f8b2184edh.webp?v=1722516471</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>14.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9450792485128</g:id>
      <g:title>Zuren</g:title>
      <g:description>Introducing our new corduroy baker boy newsboy hat - the stylish and fresh addition to your autumn and winter wardrobe! Adjustable for a perfect fit, this soft and warm cap will keep you cozy without sacrificing style. A must-have for trendy and leisurely women and girls.
Material: Corduroy Cotton
Size: One Size. Stretchable/adjustable.







</g:description>
      <g:link>https://vdagama.myshopify.com/products/new-autumn-and-winter-adjustable-soft-warm-peaked-cap-corduroy-womens-girls-baker-boy-newsboy-hat-women-warm-leisure-caps-new</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/1484/1352/files/S5dd72318812f479987ef75da3465bff98.webp?v=1725208146</g:image_link>
      <g:availability>out of stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>13.90 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Vasco da Gama</g:brand>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>